<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<sentences>
  <sentence id="1">
    <text>This is the best game of all time</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="2">
    <text>Really fun and awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="3">
    <text>I got the update and it turns off when it lods</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="4">
    <text>This update is plain bad. It's one thing to make the levels challenging but to make them near impossible with no real reward, well, that misses the point entirely. I didn't finish Bad Piggies and won't be finishing this either.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="5">
    <text>I love the angry birds collection and have them all, except for angry piggies which I will buy later</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="angry birds collection" to="33"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="6">
    <text>It said there is a new pink bird in the birthday level but I have not seen it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="7">
    <text>Needs a restore purchase button.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="8" term="restore purchase button" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="8">
    <text>Bought the eagle awhile ago and now can't get it back.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="9">
    <text>Well worth the price.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="10">
    <text>Awesome game!  Addicting and fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="11">
    <text>Still five stars!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="12">
    <text>Where's the last level?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="13">
    <text>Fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="14">
    <text>looks bad on iphone 5 its stretched</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="15">
    <text>I wasn't even able to load the first level before crashing. Brilliant.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="16">
    <text>!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="17">
    <text>Why try to change it, if it didn't need to be changed to begin with?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="18">
    <text>The new levels are awful, and completely away from the traditional &quot;Angry Birds&quot; gameplay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="19">
    <text>But, that is what they made the other Angry Birds Games for!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="20">
    <text>I have to agree with many other reviewers.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="21">
    <text>The traditional gameplay is one of the things that make this game great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="22">
    <text>It WAS Great fun!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="23">
    <text>The regular gameplay was just fine.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="24">
    <text>What they should have done, was create a whole different game for these new kinds of gameplay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="25">
    <text>Hopefully, it is beyond clear to them, that not too many people enjoy these new levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="26">
    <text>You will end up with panic disorder, racing to get the egg away from the bad piggies, in their impossible to destroy contraptions and an impossible to control bird!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="27">
    <text>I get that they want to &quot;spice&quot; up the game a bit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="28">
    <text>Furthermore, we do hope you take our reviews seriously, and do your absolute best not to flub up any more levels on a game that was great just the way it was!!  ??????
?????????????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="29">
    <text>It's more of a frustration, than enjoyment.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="30">
    <text>Well Rovio, hopefully you have the same person who came up with these awful new levels, reading our fabulously accurate reviews, so they get the hint that it stinks??!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="31">
    <text>AND, it WAS Fun for ALL ages too!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="32">
    <text>The Mighty Eagle?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="33">
    <text>Awesome!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="34">
    <text>So for a great game, I give you 5 stars.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="35">
    <text>I love this awesome game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="36">
    <text>I love the entire Angry Birds series!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="37">
    <text>Keep it up!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="38">
    <text>Please fix issue for iPhone - every time I'm playing the game and a phone alarm, incoming call, text, etc pops up (which I hit the snooze or ok button) the sound then goes off the game and the only way to fix it is to reboot phone). Please help!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="39">
    <text>Had for over a year and still play it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="40">
    <text>Chuck speeds</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="41">
    <text>Ok.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="42">
    <text>Definitely a step in the wrong direction, enough to make me write my first review ever in hopes that you do not continue with this version of AB. Lets just pretend this never happened and go back to our old ways, ok?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="43">
    <text>I love Angry Birds, but hate the new feathers levels.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="33" term="new feathers levels" to="52"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="44">
    <text>This is Gerch's favorite app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="45">
    <text>Gerch loves to see how many reindeer dragons she can fit in her park to match her favorite reindeer sweater - Love Gerch *o*</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="46">
    <text>Constant pop ups trying to sell &quot;super birds&quot; that don't really do much take away the pleasure of the game.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Constant pop ups" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="47">
    <text>Sad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="48">
    <text>I think the time has come to delete my old pals A Birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="49">
    <text>It is quite annoying.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="50">
    <text>Awsome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="51">
    <text>You want to go back to find more points.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="52">
    <text>I love this game a lot!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="53">
    <text>I love this update but change how pigs look in the other episodes</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="54">
    <text>So my 5 year old plays this game and when we were at the fair he was beating pigs. And pretends like all eggs are his bloody precious and try's to strangle my wife when she makes scrambled eggs.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="55">
    <text>Great game worth the dollar</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="56">
    <text>Since the last update this game crashes constantly and is unplayable.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="57">
    <text>iPhone4S</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="58">
    <text>Having to wait until the last bird poofs away gets tiresome.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="59">
    <text>I love Angry Birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="60">
    <text>However, the reset time after the last effort is very irritating.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="13" term="reset time" to="23"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="61">
    <text>I wish I could have given it no stars for the review.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="62">
    <text>Very disappointed in these levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="63">
    <text>I guess I'm back to waiting for new normal levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="64">
    <text>I've gotten three stars on three levels and played all day.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="65">
    <text>What a waste of time.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="66">
    <text>The tapping and aiming is so frustrating.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="tapping and aiming" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="67">
    <text>Thanks for raising my hopes and then crushing it with this crap</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="68">
    <text>This most recent update is awful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="5" term="most recent update" to="23"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="69">
    <text>It pretends to be angry birds but it isn't.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="70">
    <text>I am hoping Rovio gets the message and sticks to adding regular levels in the future.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="71">
    <text>I have all the angry birds games and love new levels.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="42" term="new levels" to="52"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="72">
    <text>I find it frustrating to play and not fun at all.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="73">
    <text>My phone crashed and when I reinstalled everything, I no longer had the Mighty Eagle which I had already purchased.  I want my eagle back!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="74">
    <text>Very very good</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="75">
    <text>Make sure you check out the other Angry Birds games.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="76">
    <text>This game is really cool.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="77">
    <text>I like it and I think people will enjoy it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="78">
    <text>(The reason my nickname is Scribblenaustin is because I really want Scribblenauts Unlimited for Christmas)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="79">
    <text>More levels?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="80">
    <text>This game is really addicting i play ot like every day, i think though this game gets way more attention than needed!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="81">
    <text>???? ????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="82">
    <text>Can other birds have mighty feathers?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="83">
    <text>Wonderful game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="84">
    <text>I confirmed to update this game 5 days ago.   Has just barely started installation. Wth</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="85">
    <text>So,how can you come out with a game where the good guys are so weak and slow compared to the bad???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="86">
    <text>I use this game to pass time!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="87">
    <text>I am on 16-8!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="88">
    <text>This game is amazing!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="89">
    <text>Ruined my favorite game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="90">
    <text>New one isnt fun at all.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="91">
    <text>Fun to spend time</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="92">
    <text>Addictive!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="93">
    <text>Great graphics and the physics engine is dead-on!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="graphics" to="14"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="23" term="physics engine" to="37"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="94">
    <text>Good game and make bad piggies free please</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="19" term="bad piggies free" to="35"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="95">
    <text>?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="96">
    <text>Why are pigs stealing eggs??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="97">
    <text>....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="98">
    <text>Stupid, repetitive, boring game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="99">
    <text>Why do birds even need a slingshot, can't they just fly anyway???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="100">
    <text>This game is perfect for all you boring people out there.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="101">
    <text>Save your money for gameloft.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="102">
    <text>Don't buy.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="103">
    <text>Why are they green??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="104">
    <text>.... It's the same on every level.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="105">
    <text>So many questions...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="106">
    <text>I love angry birds but this new level is really unpleasant and confusing.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="28" term="new level" to="37"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="107">
    <text>Once the bugs were fixed it runs great and I never have a dull moment waiting in line, when I'm on break at work, or riding in the car.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="108">
    <text>Some have complaints but I think it's pretty addicting!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="109">
    <text>Latest version totally shuts down my music when opening this to play. Fix this!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="110">
    <text>I like it but all the updates make it hard to beat</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="111">
    <text>Still mono...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="112">
    <text>I love all of the games. So does my 4 yr old son. He's better than a lot of adults are. I play on my 3rd gen iPod touch. I just wish this thing could go past iOS 5. I'm always looking forward to updates tht include new levels. Keep it up Rovio!!! You guys are the kings of the gaming world!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="113">
    <text>Still good game and I also like the cartoons. My kids love them.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="114">
    <text>Awesome Game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="115">
    <text>It is basically a completely different game. One that is more frustrating and annoying. I really don't like the time pressure!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="116">
    <text>Great iPhone game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="117">
    <text>I love this game, it's so irresistible I can't put it down!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="118">
    <text>The &quot;Red's Mighty Feather&quot; update has completely turned me off to Angry Birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="119">
    <text>The &quot;Red's Mighty Feathers&quot; levels are frustrating, poorly designed, and just not fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="120">
    <text>The mechanics are completely different, the strategy/problem-solving aspect is totally gone, and if your shot is so much as a pixel off from what the developers apparently intended, you essentially fail and have to restart the level.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="121">
    <text>I bought this game to injoy a game the old fashion way, not cheep my way out of the levels</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="122">
    <text>It is a fine game intill all of the ads comes and blocks the screen, and the new powerups are not smart.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="77" term="new powerups" to="89"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="123">
    <text>Says to update, but won't! Updated 10 other apps in one minute, but this one won't even begin updating after 5 minutes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="124">
    <text>love the game. So much fun. But it is not fair that in Ham 'Em High , we have to log onto facebook and like you, because we paid for the app, so we should get the levels, and some of us don't have a facebook account, i paid for the app, I should get the levels. I would like you guys on facebook but i can't because i dont have a facebook account. I brought the mighty eagle on my ipod but it didn't transfer to the app on my iPhone. So buy once unlimited use is a lie.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="125">
    <text>Players who want to play would have bought it earlier.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="126">
    <text>Birdies are awesome!!!!!!!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Birdies" to="7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="127">
    <text>I think it would be cool if you added a level creator where you could make levels and share them with friends.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="40" term="level creator" to="53"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="128">
    <text>I really like the new levels.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="18" term="new levels" to="28"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="129">
    <text>Time just flies when your having fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="130">
    <text>Bird does NOT go where I tap the screen in the new levels. It seems to either lock onto a pig, or shoot horizontally no matter where I hit the screen. Not playing again without an update</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="131">
    <text>not the one i know and love</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="132">
    <text>Why do I have to wait so long to get past the ad for [whatever the ad is for-I refuse to pay attention to it since I paid for the app]. I might as well play a game that doesn't penalize me for playing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="133">
    <text>The new update has a huge bug that causes some of the missions to have the targeting locked on a certain point no matter where you press. This is game breaking.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="134">
    <text>Can't wait for more levels and hopefully a boss level with King Piggy</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="135">
    <text>Are the best yet....love the new gameplay and goals...totally awesome.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="46" term="goals" to="51"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="29" term="new gameplay" to="41"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="136">
    <text>Add icould support to the game so your purchases and records can be save so when ever you want to delete and download the game again thank you</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="4" term="icould support" to="18"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="137">
    <text>Best game app ever! Second to none!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="138">
    <text>Seems the new ones only take speed. Accuracy is more challenging to me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="139">
    <text>Not to mention, you took the original music away! ??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="140">
    <text>Really wish there was an option to keep the original tune or not!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="141">
    <text>Sorry Rovio-------this new level just doesn't do it for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="142">
    <text>I waited 2 hours in order to get this app. What a rip off!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="143">
    <text>BEST APP UPDATE EVA!!!!!!! Lol</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="144">
    <text>This is the best game!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="145">
    <text>While I like the gist of the concept, the levels get harder with the moving target and set you up at an unfair advantage.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="146">
    <text>Not worth the update.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="147">
    <text>The new version is not good.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new version" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="148">
    <text>You also don't get any additional tools to gel fight the pigs and you find yourself quickly going over your quota of shots by level 6.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="149">
    <text>+1 for trying a new idea but its not fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="150">
    <text>Not enjoying the new update.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="151">
    <text>I thought I paid .99 to remove ads but apparently they're back. This is completely unfair Rovio.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="152">
    <text>??Some people are so annoying they are like is boring, is this a scam?, etc. I love this game?? and why would you want the same game on more then one of your iPod, iPad, iPhone??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="153">
    <text>Love the new level! Can't stay off it! Keep up the good work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="154">
    <text>I love it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="155">
    <text>I am a big fan!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="156">
    <text>I am having a blast with this new update!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="30" term="new update" to="40"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="157">
    <text>Thank you!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="158">
    <text>If they were going for the &quot;New Coke&quot; effect it worked. It is back to real angry birds and is better then ever.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="159">
    <text>Please bring back the trajectory line or at least make it to where you can turn it on or off.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="22" term="trajectory line" to="37"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="160">
    <text>That's one of the thing I loved about the game before and why it's been a while since I've played it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="161">
    <text>I have all of then except Rio.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="162">
    <text>I love the fact the both Star Wars has then but not sure why you got rid of them on the original and seasons.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="163">
    <text>Go download bamboo wallet and use the code AC1789176. Thx (???)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="164">
    <text>This is my favorite game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="165">
    <text>Dear Angry Bird team, me and and a group of people had been discussing the matter of writing to you about an idea of the same Angry Birds concept but in the Marvel super hero perception, the same as Angry Birds Star Wars but Marvel. Please take our concern. 
Thank you for reading.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="166">
    <text>I like angry birds cause it's cool</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="167">
    <text>Not even worth one star.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="168">
    <text>&quot;Red's Mighty Feathers&quot; is WAY too difficult!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="5" term="Red's Mighty Feathers" to="30"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="169">
    <text>Rovio needs to fix the game and get rid of the new levels, or else they're going to lose a lot of fans and the franchise is going to fail!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="170">
    <text>I appreciate a good challenge, but this is just ridiculous!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="171">
    <text>Do NOT download this game because Rovio has ruined the game that we've come to love, and if you have the game, don't update it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="172">
    <text>Angry Birds used be a fun and addicting game, and now the latest update has absolutely RUINED the game!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="58" term="latest update" to="71"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="173">
    <text>The newest levels are literally IMPOSIBLE to complete and are flat out frustrating!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="newest levels" to="17"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="174">
    <text>Thank you for making this game so so cool LOL!!!!!!WOW!!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="175">
    <text>Better beans</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="176">
    <text>Not compatible</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="177">
    <text>It was great!!! Then it was updated and I was super excited!! The levels looked awesome!! But I can't play them, not any levels, even the ones I already beat.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="178">
    <text>I have not encountered any problems so far with this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="179">
    <text>This new level is really disappointing it is not fun, I missed the original game I'm playing it just to get over with it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="5" term="new level" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="180">
    <text>Angry birds went from 5 stars to 1 star.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="181">
    <text>Too bad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="182">
    <text>I felt like I lost my interest in Angry Birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="183">
    <text>Glad the designers listened to the fans.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="184">
    <text>It's not working for my iPod fourth gen. It doesn't even let me get to the actual gameplay</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="185">
    <text>Fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="186">
    <text>Why change a good thing?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="187">
    <text>I can't get passed the first level because it crashes</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="27" term="first level" to="38"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="188">
    <text>Keep it up Rovio!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="189">
    <text>The fans made it #1, not Apple.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="190">
    <text>Another update!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="191">
    <text>The game is number 1 for a reason.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="192">
    <text>Glad that the developers keep up on the apps.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="193">
    <text>The update is great and the retina display is a welcomed addition.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="194">
    <text>Suwu game #1</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="195">
    <text>This games is a family favorite.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="196">
    <text>Simply addicting! Thanks to bug fix, much much better!!!! 6/5 stars!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="197">
    <text>I love playing this on my iPhone</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="198">
    <text>I updated this app. When I opened this app, it erased all my data. I will never play this app again</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="199">
    <text>I used to enjoy it but now with Bad piggies and next it is more and more difficult to get 3 stars, it is not fun anylonger; stay away from it, specially the red' feather crap, not the classic episode, it is garbage</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="200">
    <text>Very good.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="201">
    <text>Where's my $0.99???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="202">
    <text>Really love this game. Play it every day.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="203">
    <text>Thanks Arniedillo fan.  I downloaded ArnieDillo app and it's really fun!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="204">
    <text>I got this app free thanks to FeaturePoints!
Sign up now, and you too could get all the top apps free now!
All you have to do is:
-Go to FeaturePoints(dot)com
-Enter FIY2UE into the Referral Box (You gain extra points)
-Download Free apps or refer friends
-Get Free Points
-Get your Free iTunes Card!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="205">
    <text>Love this game, totally worth $1
But I got it free! :D</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="206">
    <text>Awesome and very addictive</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="207">
    <text>I don't know about this update, but it might be good.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="208">
    <text>Best app game ever</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="209">
    <text>If this is the kind of garbage we have to look forward to then I am done with Angry Birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="210">
    <text>The new Angry Birds episode (Red's Mighty Feathers) is a piece of JUNK.  It is not worth an update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="29" term="Red's Mighty Feathers" to="54"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="211">
    <text>Could be the worst thing I have seen. Great stuff usually from Angry Birds. This however does not make any sense. Hell the screen does not even move on the 1st level. 

You have my money already but if other franchises come out, I will pass if this the direction you are going. Good work though if the purpose was to be completely different from other levels and giving the user no clue what the objective is.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="212">
    <text>I suggest that the next angry bird be angry birds &quot;lord of the rings.&quot;love this game,can't stop thinking about it!!!!!!!!!!!!?????????????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="213">
    <text>Even after buying the 'full' version you still get ads for other angry birds games.  And even after paying real life money to unlock the eagle, you can only use it every so often.  This is a wonderful example of what is wrong with apps for iPhone in general.  I got duped into giving them some money, hopefully someone in the future will be dissuaded by this.  Rovio is an awful money grabbing company and knowing what I know now I will never give them another cent.  I encourage all to follow suit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="214">
    <text>I thought I loved 'Angry Birds' before the update, but the mad scientist lab is incredible. Takes me back to playing the game for the first time and it was just plain ole' fun. You guys have totally outdone yourselves with the adorable scenery and characters. More please... (PS- no offense but I was getting bored with the SW series)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="215">
    <text>I'm always looking forward to Angry Birds updates but this last one is awful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="216">
    <text>Red feathers flying around telling you what to hit-it doesn't even feel like Angry Birds anymore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="217">
    <text>You are ruining this super fun game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="218">
    <text>Please go back to levels like in the beginning.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="219">
    <text>This is awsome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="220">
    <text>But now every time I go to this app it automatically goes home, so now I can't even play.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="88" term="play" to="92"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="221">
    <text>The games pretty good.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="222">
    <text>It was fun but now it's just taking up space.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="223">
    <text>Fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="224">
    <text>Absolutame divertido. 100%</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="225">
    <text>I like the new update rovio keep up the good work</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="new update" to="21"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="226">
    <text>If I had a duck I would name it Lewis ??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="227">
    <text>It's not that fun I mean its fun when you play it for a little while but then you get so bored of it and I payed 99cents for it and now it's free what I want my money back!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="228">
    <text>I've been waiting four years for it to be free and today is the day! Now I can know what all the fuss is about!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="229">
    <text>Had this years ago when I payed for it (shut up its only a dollar you payed for) I wanted to see what the hype was... It's appeal lasted for the first chapter then it became an mucus emcee</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="230">
    <text>But since I downloaded it I've been having sound issues with my phone</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="231">
    <text>Ok got to the bonus surf and truf, now what??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="232">
    <text>Very good game but old</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="233">
    <text>This is the #1 game of all time with hours and hours of bird slinging action, you would be wasting money on your iPhone if you didn't get it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="234">
    <text>Why!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="235">
    <text>This is one of the best games ever!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="236">
    <text>You seriously rating this game lower over the picture? Who cares, thanks for a great free game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="237">
    <text>Stringbeam1, it's the original one, so obviously it isn't themed -.-</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="238">
    <text>I pooped my pants</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="239">
    <text>Great game. I love that the update lets you have one more page of fun!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="240">
    <text>REALLY fun but some levels are near to impossible</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="241">
    <text>This app, angry birds rio, angry birds seasons, and angry birds space keep crashing. I'm expecting updates soon.  I love the games.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="242">
    <text>Bring it back---</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="243">
    <text>Here's my review for Red's Mighty (Crappy) Feathers: it's just not fun. I lost interest quickly. I hope Rovio sees all these 1 star reviews and takes them to heart. Rovio, please go back to what you're good at!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="244">
    <text>So addictive</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="245">
    <text>:) thts</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="246">
    <text>ok tho... I STILL LUVVVVV ITTTT!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="247">
    <text>Hey I think this game is cool but its kinda stupid cuz all you do in it is fling a bunch of little birds around.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="248">
    <text>It has been cutting out and restarting in the middle of my games, so that I am unable to beat high scores or get more stars. Not cool. And it restarts the game so when I try to get back to the game, it hasn't paused in the level and I have to go through the first screen again.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="249">
    <text>Fun when it first came out but it first came out</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="250">
    <text>Teaches while having fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="251">
    <text>Game crashes every time in the new update :/</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="252">
    <text>Awesome awesome awesome awesome!!!!!!!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="253">
    <text>Since I got the mighty eagle I am forced to sign in each time I play, truly annoying.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="254">
    <text>??????????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="255">
    <text>Fun really like the new levels</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="256">
    <text>People are complaining about the new update of Angry Birds. It's just an ADDITION of levels to the original game with a twist, and it's NOT that bad. Sure, it's different from the previous levels, but it's unique and could get a bit challenging if you play the whole thing instead of just playing two levels and saying it's horrible. I'm sure there will be more levels of the same classic Angry Birds coming soon, so all the complainers need to take a seat and be patient. Great job on the game, Rovio! And for all who don't have the game, don't let these reviews prevent you from getting it. You don't have an iPhone/iPad/iPod Touch unless Angry Birds is on it.

P.S. I don't work for Rovio or anything, F.Y.I.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="257">
    <text>Sorry but the game is just not fun anymore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="258">
    <text>And u pay for the toons by the way.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="259">
    <text>The game is fun and all but the the pop ups are awful and it notes me about cartoons!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="36" term="pop ups" to="43"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="260">
    <text>One of my favorites.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="261">
    <text>5 stars easy!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="262">
    <text>Angry Birds rock!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="263">
    <text>I love Red and Chuck.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="264">
    <text>I would honestly be willing to pay for an Angry Birds Toons app for one or two dollars set up exactly how it is set up on the Angry Birds app or a little different as long as it's not confusing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="265">
    <text>Mighty eagle rocks too.(:</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Mighty eagle" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="266">
    <text>More Angry Bird Toon videos with them please.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="16" term="Toon videos" to="27"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="267">
    <text>But the Toons are so great there should be a different app for it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="8" term="Toons" to="13"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="268">
    <text>GET THIS GAME!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="269">
    <text>the new song awful,terrible,horrible,etc.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new song" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="270">
    <text>3) at the beginning of level the extremely slow speed that I'm given control (I'm swiping to get to the bird, but no response).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="271">
    <text>1) bird doesn't seem to go where I click, but rather in the general direction of the pig...extremely annoying. 2) the extremely slow speed that the birds reload.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="152" term="birds reload" to="164"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="272">
    <text>Big complaints about it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="273">
    <text>If the first two are fixed, then I'd give it 4 stars.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="274">
    <text>I don't see what all the hype is about. Really kind of dumb. Throw birds at buildings to kill pigs.. Nintendo has better games for casual gamers. If you want a really great game on the App Store check out infinity blade, Tiny, Tower, Warzone: Anomaly, Eufloria, or anything by Telltale Games. Kairosoft makes pretty fun and cute games, too.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="275">
    <text>I used to love this app but when ever I try to do anything it crashes and won't let me open it again</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="276">
    <text>Really I don't know how this got millions of downloads I got it while it was free and I still feel ripped off.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="277">
    <text>Every time I try to play the new episode it always crashes but never the other episodes</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="29" term="new episode" to="40"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="278">
    <text>The constant interruptions and harassment's to buy something took the fun out of the game. Recently the game would auto send me to other websites. I paid for these games, this wasn't suppose to happen....Grrr</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="279">
    <text>Cool</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="280">
    <text>Once, I wrote a good review for this app. I am now realizing how dumb I was. This app is like giving a dead body plastic surgery before its burial, with the surgery prolonging the burial. I can not wait until the Angry Birds fad ends. It has been around for 3+ years and all they ever add is 15 levels every three months or so to milk the franchise. END IT PLEASE! To conclude... I wish to bash all of the five-star reviewers over their heads with various pottery.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="281">
    <text>Look in the settings for Magic Places. Can't believe I just noticed it. They will track you even if the app is closed.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="282">
    <text>But if it's gonna stay free I would like a refund pppppplllllllllllllllleeeeeeeeaaaaaaaassssssssssseeeeeeeeeee?!?!?!?!?!?!????????????????????$ back 
$ back $ back $ back $ back</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="283">
    <text>New levels are horrible...totally different game than angry birds in my opinion.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="New levels" to="10"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="284">
    <text>Developers dropped the ball on this update.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="285">
    <text>Awesome with moving targets</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="286">
    <text>Wish this and Seasons had the dotted lines like Space and Star Wars.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="287">
    <text>This is a game i will be playing when i'm old because it really is an all time classic! :) POWER TO THE BIRDS!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="288">
    <text>imagine a new game of angry birds when the pigs go zombies or in the after life heaven (angry birds) vs hell (pigs)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="289">
    <text>Whenever I click a level on my iPod touch, it crashes automatically. I don't see why it's doing it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="290">
    <text>Used to be cool but now if I try to three star a level those stupid &quot;buy me&quot; pop-up birds come up and it's annoying.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="291">
    <text>This is a must have game for your iPhone, iPod, or smartphone. ??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="292">
    <text>Good things come to people who wait, and the good thing is, THIS APP IS FINALLLY FREEEE!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="293">
    <text>You should get it. It's much better than the free version. It's easy and challenging at the same time. It's a game anyone can play.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="294">
    <text>I like it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="295">
    <text>The game is awesome and challenging...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="296">
    <text>It keeps on crashing on me I hate fix it now</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="297">
    <text>Well this annoying million dollar mobile game does not provide challenging mind games but people buy this game all the time sigh...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="298">
    <text>....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="299">
    <text>It's too hard and too repetitive.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="300">
    <text>The newest update is terrible.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="301">
    <text>Please do something to make it more interesting, or stop designing these ridiculous new levels.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="84" term="new levels" to="94"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="302">
    <text>Still a good game but old version was better</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="303">
    <text>I won't be upset with the look either.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="304">
    <text>I really want an indigo bird!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="305">
    <text>And please put an indigo bird!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="306">
    <text>Just please!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="307">
    <text>!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="308">
    <text>It will make the game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="309">
    <text>so so so so so so so sooooooooooooooooooooooooooo much better!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="310">
    <text>Thanks for reading!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="311">
    <text>Please!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="312">
    <text>It doesn't even matter what you name it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="313">
    <text>Just please - can you put an indigo bird?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="314">
    <text>{ :):):):):):):):):):</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="315">
    <text>Please put an indigo bird!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="316">
    <text>It doesn't matter what power you give it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="317">
    <text>):) if you put an indigo bird :(:(:(:(:(:(:(:(:( if you don't put an indigo bird. }</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="318">
    <text>It could be a magpie, you know.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="319">
    <text>Please!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="320">
    <text>so so</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="321">
    <text>Please put an indigo bird into the game.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="14" term="indigo bird" to="25"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="322">
    <text>It kills a lot of time and keeps you busy for hours!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="323">
    <text>But since this is only an opinion i would truly suggest with whatever you feel like since it is your $0.99</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="324">
    <text>Instead of wasting money on new levels just get a new game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="325">
    <text>I think angry birds is a waste of money and is getting old.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="326">
    <text>It just make angry bird more fun with the electric shock I can't wait for a new episode of the game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="327">
    <text>Its good</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="328">
    <text>Great game but, how many times do I have to purchase the ?mighty eagle?!? Every time there's a mega update, I have to purchase the eagle again! Rip offs.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="329">
    <text>I ?????????? this game I Whod have gave this game 100 stars</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="330">
    <text>Good &amp; nice</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="331">
    <text>Can't play the new updated version because it keeps crashing.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="19" term="new updated version" to="38"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="332">
    <text>Add new levels, not games within the game.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="4" term="new levels" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="333">
    <text>I love angry birds and still do but I give them a three star rating because of the    reds mighty feathers levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="334">
    <text>It's only one mess up.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="335">
    <text>It's still my favorite game and I will still keep playing the game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="336">
    <text>Best game I ever played!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="337">
    <text>#OCD</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="338">
    <text>I paid for the app, why are there ads ******</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="339">
    <text>Game was fun till the ads I was planning on buying their other games but not so sure now</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="340">
    <text>This makes the new levels mostly a frustration instead of fun.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="15" term="new levels" to="25"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="341">
    <text>The new levels introduce twitch play, where you have to do things quickly and just at just the right time/way to win.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="342">
    <text>I love angry birds,but im not happy with you.Why do you need Open GL 2.0? I can't get that because I have an Iphone3G,so now I'm going to miss out on new levels.Please fix that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="343">
    <text>Also the daily reward is gone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="344">
    <text>I agree w/ other negative reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="345">
    <text>Please undo last update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="12" term="last update" to="23"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="346">
    <text>The plus side: there are tons of levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="347">
    <text>This app is awesome up to a point. I wish this app was easy to win.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="348">
    <text>I think the new update is pretty fun o.o and I like it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="12" term="new update" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="349">
    <text>Can't stop playing!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="350">
    <text>Pop</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="351">
    <text>Awesome game I love it my dad loves it my sister loves it and mom loves it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="352">
    <text>Never have I met something that makes me so entertained and angry at the same time. Frustratingly addictive- in a good way.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="353">
    <text>Best game I ever played.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="354">
    <text>I enjoys it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="355">
    <text>The new levels are horrible.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="356">
    <text>The new levels are completely boring.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new levels" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="357">
    <text>I am a big fan of angry birds too.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="358">
    <text>Hard.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="359">
    <text>You pays sometimes then it turns out free.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="360">
    <text>There should be an option to turn off Game Center permanently.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="361">
    <text>What I DON'T like is that ridiculous Game Center garbage.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="362">
    <text>Absolutely ridiculous.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="363">
    <text>I don't need to see a leader board.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="364">
    <text>I don't compete with friends.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="365">
    <text>ONCE. 

Game is awesome, addicting and plays flawlessly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="366">
    <text>I'm fine with that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="367">
    <text>Really.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="368">
    <text>Just like everything else in life.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="369">
    <text>Worth 6 stars but only giving one until they stop that Game Center crap.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="370">
    <text>I don't mind turning it off.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="371">
    <text>Not everyone wants that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="372">
    <text>I can't STAND having to go through that stupid thing every couple days to disable it when I already did that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="373">
    <text>The update is otherwise good -- not great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="374">
    <text>I hate tower defense games.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="7" term="tower defense" to="20"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="375">
    <text>There are still tower defense levels on my phone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="376">
    <text>The game crashed and deleted all my progress.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="377">
    <text>And the new power of the red bird, directional targeting, kinda goes against the appeal of the original game -- you fire a bird and can't change it's direction.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="378">
    <text>More please.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="379">
    <text>Love this game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="380">
    <text>I love this game so much!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="381">
    <text>It's a nice game, I like it very much.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="382">
    <text>Two days after installing this, found that my phone was burning 2% battery per hour just sitting there, with all background apps shutdown. Restarted phone and still was happening.  As soon as I uninstalled Angry Birds, it started behaving normally again.  Too bad, was a fun game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="383">
    <text>why somebody didnt see this like a good game for relax? with me its real great</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="384">
    <text>Wop wop</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="385">
    <text>Love short fuse cool update</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="386">
    <text>Not bad</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="387">
    <text>I can't even play most of the levels/episodes! Whenever I try and start an episode like &quot;mine and dine&quot;, the app closes out</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="388">
    <text>I love angry birds, this update just needs bug fixes. It crashed when I tried playing a level.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="389">
    <text>I love the moving targets! And to all those people that plan to quit cuz they dont like these moving targets...just dont play those! Duh</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="390">
    <text>Boring... Dumb.... Not much else to say besides it will be the first level I don't even attempt to complete.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="391">
    <text>Awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="392">
    <text>This is a fun game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="393">
    <text>The app keeps crashing on my iPod 4th gen ever since the new update.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="394">
    <text>PLEASE fix this!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="395">
    <text>Its the best game in the world</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="396">
    <text>My game crashes at the logo screen. Used to play fine.  Help.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="397">
    <text>He has learning apps that need the network, which makes this app a pain for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="398">
    <text>Give us the ability to turn off cartoons some way other than putting the iPod into airplane mode!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="23" term="turn off cartoons" to="40"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="399">
    <text>I like the game and there always seem to be more levels than I have time to master.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="400">
    <text>This game is heavily marketed to kids - fine by me, my kid loves the blankets and bath towels and t-shirts - but they've added videos to the app you can't turn off anywhere in the settings.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="401">
    <text>I don't want my kid idly watching cartoons, I don't mind playing games.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="402">
    <text>Please help on the new update every time I try and go on birds of a feather it keeps taking me out. :(</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="403">
    <text>You should make it mighty feathers+traditional gameplay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="404">
    <text>I like it.the new levels are relly fun.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="14" term="new levels" to="24"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="405">
    <text>Still,I miss the old gameplay.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="M" from="17" term="old gameplay" to="29"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="406">
    <text>It was free for 1 day! So what if you paid for it. It's only a $0.99 app. I bought this a long time ago &amp; I'm not complaining. I think it's cool it was free for a little bit. It's a great game. It's not like they made Angry Birds Star Wars free. (If you like this game &amp; it's your first &amp; only angry birds. You should get Angry Birds Space.) It's almost better in my opinion. :)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="407">
    <text>Definitely a five-star addictive game, but the ads have become excessive.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="408">
    <text>You pay for the game, you don't deal with ads...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="409">
    <text>Just a thought</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="410">
    <text>This isn't a new level, it's a totally new game. The concept is completely different and takes any fun out of Angry Birds. Change it back to the way it's been, and if Rovio really wants to keep this &quot;level&quot; then make a new Angry Birds game and add it to the 10 other ones. But leave the original alone!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="411">
    <text>I can't play the new part since it keeps crashing on me, please fix it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="412">
    <text>Awesome adicting fun it is the Best awesomest game EVER!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="413">
    <text>Just jumped on the angry bird train. Love it!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="414">
    <text>When it shows the loading screen everything turns BLACK and RETURNS TO HOME fix it please</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="415">
    <text>?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="416">
    <text>Create something original.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="417">
    <text>And why do you want me to register????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="418">
    <text>Haven't you milked this enough considering it was ripped off from castle???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="419">
    <text>Wft??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="420">
    <text>Your other games haven't been such a hit have they?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="421">
    <text>so many commercials is making the  game slow to load and also makes it slow when playing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="422">
    <text>Awesome update thank you this is awesome I can't wait for the next levels!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="423">
    <text>I'm almost out of levels!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="424">
    <text>I've been a massive Angry Birds fan for years. After finding no enjoyment in Amazing Alex or Bad Piggies, Rovio decides to force these on me in Angry Birds?  For the first time since the first AB app I'm thoroughly let down. Lame move!  This isn't AB.  It's random garbage advertising a different game. No thank you.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="425">
    <text>Please go back to the old way, sorry but the new level are horrible!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="426">
    <text>This is a fun game and for 99 cents is very entertaining.  However, as you get further into the levels, it becomes pretty obvious that this game was written to keep you from progressing unless you spend hours doing the same pointless task until you succeed, or you pay more money to be allowed to progress with a reasonable effort.  Kind of takes the entertainment out of it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="427">
    <text>Its still loading and it has been fir five days. I want it to go away already. Please help. This is annoying even though that i like all the games but if it keeps telling me its installing and it is not thats unacceptable.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="428">
    <text>This is awesome!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="429">
    <text>I've always been a big fan of the entire Angry Birds series. However, with the most recent updates to this particular game, there is a hugely frustrating glitch. On levels with the egg dropping birds, more often than not whenever I attempt to drop an egg the icons atop the screen interfere and the result is them trying to sell me an eagle rather than dropping the egg. I've talked to others who have had the same issue. I really thought that Rovio would be above such plebeian glitches by now.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="430">
    <text>Really don't see what all the hype is about....my 6 yr old nephew thinks its pretty cool though, so I keep it on my phone ;)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="431">
    <text>angry birds was a great app until the update the new theme is stupid (who listens to polka!)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="49" term="new theme" to="58"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="432">
    <text>really rovio?!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="433">
    <text>and the &quot;reds mighty feathers&quot; whats up with that</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="434">
    <text>Addicted and loving it!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="435">
    <text>Love this game it's dope</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="436">
    <text>No new levels added for months now.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="437">
    <text>I used to like it but not now. After the update I do not like not interested in moving targets and mighty reds feathers.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="438">
    <text>Love the game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="439">
    <text>Awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="440">
    <text>They should make a minecraft angry birds</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="441">
    <text>It keeps going back to the home screen when it's on the loading screen :/</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="442">
    <text>When I go to play the game it just take me out please fix and when I went to see a video of the end of the world it just exit me out so fix it !</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="443">
    <text>When yu play angry birds you're like so123im so happy</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="444">
    <text>Just hard enough to be addictive but not impossible enough to make you quit forever. I love the original thought to the game and upgrades keep the game spicy. Best bang for you buck!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="445">
    <text>HEY what happen to the daily powerup. That's the last time I will update. If course I could buy power ups. Isn't that a bit of bait and switch.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="446">
    <text>A+ to kill some time if yeah don't have anything to do</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="447">
    <text>Well done</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="448">
    <text>Nuff said</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="449">
    <text>Running iOS 6.1.3 and keeps crashing. Fix it please.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="450">
    <text>This update stinks. Period</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="451">
    <text>My last review was on the Space Eagle a very bad copy of the Awesome Mighty Eagle which is my latest review and an unlimited supply of them can be bought for 99c so it gets 5 stars but the Space Eagle should be the same?Then I might actually like it. By the way if you are complaining because of the logo for Roviow on the Angry Birds App then stop its just saying who it's made by( just a picture! ) who cares about the little pic the game is what counts!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="452">
    <text>This is the worst. It wasn't broken til you tried to fix it. Stinky!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="453">
    <text>No more daily power-ups.  And you don't get any unless you pay more than what you paid for the game.  New level is not as fun.  I'm disappointed to say the least...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="454">
    <text>Got it FREE!(;</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="455">
    <text>It fine!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="456">
    <text>It's so fun that I can Play it all day :)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="457">
    <text>It crashes as soon as  i get to load the level</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="458">
    <text>Use to love angry birds  
Until new features were install/update 
After that remove off phone miss the begging version of when it came out.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="459">
    <text>read the required ios products.ipod gen 3-5 and iphones,aswell as ipads only.So shush,iloveoneepublic.-six comments down-</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="460">
    <text>Don't like new levels but still okay game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="461">
    <text>I cant play the new missions.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="16" term="new missions" to="28"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="462">
    <text>Whenever I try to play them the game quits me out an it's so annoying</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="463">
    <text>The new update is crap.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new update" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="464">
    <text>I LOVE THIS GAME,but needs more levels with pink bird,and a new world</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="27" term="more levels with pink bird" to="53"/>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="60" term="new world" to="69"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="465">
    <text>Just plain fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="466">
    <text>I love angry birds. I have them all. But this new level is along the lines of Bad Piggies. Not a fan. Very different game and it's both too hard and just not fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="467">
    <text>It'd be cool to be able to re-play an awesome shot so you can show others those amazing shots..</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="31" term="re-play an awesome shot" to="54"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="468">
    <text>angry birds has always been great and even though others tell about problems it's still awesome.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="469">
    <text>I have a suggestion.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="470">
    <text>Just a suggestion, thanks rovio!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="471">
    <text>Whoever decided to make the birds go poof needs to be hailed as a god. Love this game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="472">
    <text>Fun fun fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="473">
    <text>Why do you keep messing with a good thing? It's not even fun anymore!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="474">
    <text>I dont care if its adds for another angrybirds, i dont want to see them!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="475">
    <text>Can't stop!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="476">
    <text>It has just been sitting on my home screen with a blue bar for about 4 days (I don't remember when the update came out) and I can't do anything....?!?!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="477">
    <text>I just updated the app and the little blue loading bar thingy on the app itself is stuck on full.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="478">
    <text>I can't open the app, or delete it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="12" term="open" to="16"/>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="29" term="delete" to="35"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="479">
    <text>Angry birds is the best game of all time. Nothing can beat or ever will beat it. When it has those days when it's free DOWNLOAD IT. Still worth it for 99c though. When you download this game you will like it. Trust me. If you don't, that's fine you probably didn't play long enough. But, those who play longer are very lucky and will have a better time. Again I love love love love LOVE this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="480">
    <text>I give it a 5 rr eating! I do because you can just beat all the levels and then you get more and more. It is so addicting. You will love it if you get it. It is awesome! You all probably know how awesome it us. You will brcause almost everyone knows angry birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="481">
    <text>they keep on crashing on iPod touch 4th gen</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="482">
    <text>Is keel</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="483">
    <text>I just got a new iPod and when I tried to  download the mighty eagle it wouldn't let me.( I bought the mighty eagle on my previous iPod).
I'm still using the same account as my old iPod to.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="484">
    <text>Cool game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="485">
    <text>This app used to be the best app in the store, now look at it. Crashes too much, ads, etc. poor birds...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="486">
    <text>Every time I try to open the new levels, it doesn't work at all. It just kicks me out of the game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="487">
    <text>Level 22-2 - plan to get the best score possible on your first try. On subsequent and improved attempts the new score shows, the birds cheer and count 10k for those remaining then?

Nothing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="488">
    <text>And from the reviews, it sounds like it isn't worth tr aggravation.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="489">
    <text>PS - bad piggies sucked.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="490">
    <text>Game crashes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="491">
    <text>Since te update, can't even play the new level.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="41" term="new level" to="50"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="492">
    <text>Bring back the old icon. This one looks awkward with your logo sitting there randomly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="493">
    <text>I downloaded this and everytime i try to get on a new level the game takes me to my home page!!! Its so aggravatin!!! Ive even tried deleting it and downloadin again but but dont do no good! DO NOT GET THIS APP!!! ITS MESSED UP!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="494">
    <text>I have been playing Angry Birds for a while and love it. But the latest level just takes this game to a new level of low.

Honestly, was this designed for a group of semi-literate morons who need to be hand held through the game? 

Part of the fun is getting through a level only to find its good for one star and working to clear it to three. That's gone. There is no excitement here. 

Pass. The Angry Birds may have come home to roost.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="495">
    <text>Don't hate I like the app in all but it takes forever to update!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="496">
    <text>Every time I try to get on the new story, the screen goes black and the I'm back on my home screen! Fix it!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="497">
    <text>To many adds on a paid app?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="498">
    <text>Really fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="499">
    <text>the game is challenging... on purpose so they get u to buy the eagle?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="500">
    <text>i think its what its called which clears a hard lvl for u. so its a hard lvl after hard lvl until u break down and buy the stupid ?99 eagle attack.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="501">
    <text>well im disappointed i bought this game and the next day its app of the week.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="502">
    <text>its a fun game i guess but wayyyy over hyped!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="503">
    <text>plus they advertise their own games non stop while u play.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="504">
    <text>The most addictive game I've ever played. It's going to get me fired! But please STOP THE SHOCKWAVE NAG SCREEN!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="505">
    <text>Absolutely love angry birds Better than mario!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="506">
    <text>It crashes every time I go to play a level I love this game and want to freaken play it, it's by far one of the best games on the App Store now only if it would work -3- I'm using my iPod 4g iOS 6.1</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="507">
    <text>Awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="508">
    <text>Has some glitches and some levels seem impossible to win but it's a great fun ADDICTING game! WOOO</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="509">
    <text>Omg I'm like soooo glad I got this for free!!!!! I love angry birds!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="510">
    <text>I just put angry birds on my I phone, it played fine, I closed out of it, and when I went back into it the sound doesn't work!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="107" term="sound" to="112"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="511">
    <text>what happened, how can I fix it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="512">
    <text>Good news for who haven't buy it
Bad News for who have buy it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="513">
    <text>Angry Birds is a great game and if they made a jurassic park one I would buy it right away!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="514">
    <text>FREE FOR ALL</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="515">
    <text>This update is terrible, it's not the same game, it's reworked bad piggies.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="516">
    <text>I can't get enough of this game!!!  Love it!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="517">
    <text>Really do like it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="518">
    <text>Angry birds is a awesome app. Make some Batman levels</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="519">
    <text>Never mind the endlessly infuriating new levels or the cacophonous new intro music that sounds like it was composed by someone trying to mock carnivals...how can Rovio calls this an update at all?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="37" term="new levels" to="47"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="67" term="new intro music" to="82"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="520">
    <text>It's just a horrible overhaul...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="521">
    <text>I love Angry Birds and I always look forward to new updates. Unfortunately, Red's Mighty Feather is not fun at all. The gameplay is too linear and really lacks the destructive freedom that brought me to love Angry Birds in the first place. If it ain't broke, don't fix it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="522">
    <text>Amazing game.Youst change the logo :/</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="523">
    <text>Update, I just deleted because it always tries to log you into Game Center.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="524">
    <text>Not the fun, easy to waste time with game it used to be.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="525">
    <text>Goodbye, angry birds is really nothing but an irritation nowadays.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="526">
    <text>Used to be a fun game, but the latest updates are so difficult that you will either get three stars or nothing.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="31" term="latest updates" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="527">
    <text>Best game ever - angry birds are angry machines</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="528">
    <text>More like shoot randomly and hope you are just the right number of pixels to victory.

Still worth a play through but surprisingly overrated.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="529">
    <text>i have never seen a play button or black screen...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="530">
    <text>Those people are raging cuz they cant beat the levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="531">
    <text>And about all those 1 star reviews those people make no sense</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="532">
    <text>I love the challenging levels most apps are not like that!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="challenging levels" to="29"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="533">
    <text>Add the moving parts from reds might feathers into a new section in the bad piggies game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="534">
    <text>On my iPod Touch 4, the app crashes whenever I try to open the new level. Old levels still seem to work OK.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="535">
    <text>This level needs to be scratched.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="536">
    <text>This is not up to Rovio's normal par.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="537">
    <text>No playability whatsoever.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="538">
    <text>Was this even beta tested or presented to focus groups before global release?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="539">
    <text>Irritating and frustrating to play.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="30" term="play" to="34"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="540">
    <text>...Hate the new Red's Mighty Feathers level.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="16" term="Red's Mighty Feathers level" to="47"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="541">
    <text>C'mon Rovio! You're already a big company and have won over many fans of your games but really?! Including ads in a popular and paid app like this?!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="542">
    <text>I tried to like it doesn't work for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="543">
    <text>Adding the time component makes this no fun.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="time component" to="25"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="544">
    <text>This is not angry birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="545">
    <text>Congratulations! You have succeeded in ruining the Angry Birds game. If this continues through the entire series, the popularity well decrease very rapidly. I hope you learn from your mistakes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="546">
    <text>I'm happy that this app is free now, awesome!!!!!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="547">
    <text>You remind me of Microsoft and the Xbox One.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="548">
    <text>You were the top app for a long time, but then you change everything so that no one wants to buy it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="549">
    <text>Whoever is in charge of adding new levels should be fired.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="550">
    <text>Are you stupid or something?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="551">
    <text>Give us back the original angry birds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="552">
    <text>The new design is horrible.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new design" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="553">
    <text>So boring &amp; seriously flawed play; the timing and limited effectiveness of the red bird makes this game very boring.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="54" term="limited effectiveness" to="75"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="43" term="timing" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="554">
    <text>If I could I would not even give it one star.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="555">
    <text>Try bringing in different animals to shoot the pigs or something, stop brining in more power ups etc</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="16" term="different animals to shoot" to="42"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="556">
    <text>This morning I woke up and found the app on my home screen!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="557">
    <text>It also took the $.99.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="558">
    <text>Also, the new update is terrible, new levels are too easy.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="34" term="new levels" to="44"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="559">
    <text>I didn't even buy!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="560">
    <text>Rovio... REALLY!?!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="561">
    <text>This has to be one of the best games I've ever played on a mobile device</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="562">
    <text>Best app ever!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="563">
    <text>Angry Birds is getting boring about in-app purchase and It's very old</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="564">
    <text>This game is solid for 99 cents</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="565">
    <text>This game is really fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="566">
    <text>I don't think the &quot;brains&quot; behind the moving target segment really play angry birds. Execution is awful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="567">
    <text>lol lo encontre de casualidad y era free</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="568">
    <text>Awesome ;)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="569">
    <text>Game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="570">
    <text>I really want to play the new levels, but my app keeps crashing!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="571">
    <text>Very addicting</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="572">
    <text>One word:
iCloud</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="573">
    <text>Addicting but FUN!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="574">
    <text>It get more challenging each new level.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="575">
    <text>Lots of fun</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="576">
    <text>Love to play, challenge myself</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="577">
    <text>Heck yes</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="578">
    <text>A game I was waiting to get! Free? Niceeeee rovio! Keep up the great work!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="579">
    <text>It so much a junk kids should love to learn they shouldn't be on there iPod iPad or whatever all day they need to learn to get a life</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="580">
    <text>I don't get it. When did PIGS become bad??? The &quot;episodes&quot; are stupid and all you do is shoot things with birds. I don't understand why it's so popular. It gets boring after a while. Anyway, it's an okay app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="581">
    <text>Nearly impossible to get 3 stars and WAY TOO GIMMICKY. It's so difficult, cuts not even 1% fun!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="582">
    <text>I can't get all the levels the way I want but I still play it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="583">
    <text>This is the best game EVER!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="584">
    <text>I resisted playing this game for a long time but now cannot stop.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="585">
    <text>I like trains</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="586">
    <text>Hard to load sometimes glitches</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="587">
    <text>Enter Code:  0PWCKY</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="588">
    <text>Can't find the new levels!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="19" term="new levels" to="29"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="589">
    <text>Good game! And it is free now. Hope some day they will let minecraft be free.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="590">
    <text>The game is fun but some of the levels have some pretty poor design, forget trying to 3 star everything. The IAP pop-ups have really got to go as well. 

P.S. Fire whoever designed golden egg 5. That level is keeping me up at night.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="591">
    <text>Stupid little piggies! Love this game! Sometimes gets really hard though.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="592">
    <text>Great game love playing it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="593">
    <text>Angry birds is ok to pass time with, but most of the levels are if not impossible, very hard.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="41" term="most of the levels" to="59"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="594">
    <text>Don't buy it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="595">
    <text>The new update is poop.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new update" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="596">
    <text>I already think that this update is thumbs down.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="597">
    <text>You can get a ton of better stuff that's not a waste of money with 99 cents</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="598">
    <text>I'm on the 6th level of the new update, and</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="32" term="new update" to="42"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="599">
    <text>I absolutely love this game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="600">
    <text>This is well, ok:) it is fun but Manuel it could be a little bit more addictive but other than that its great:)!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="601">
    <text>I waited until I broke through #11 to rate this app. When I did succeed, I was nearly giddy with pride. After a few easy levels, I am again practicing my aim. The puzzles are fun and I am looking forward to another success
Yes, I am stuck again. It is way too much fun to quit, thus still a 5 rating!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="602">
    <text>My aim is improving with a better ratio of 3 star efforts.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="603">
    <text>Mary</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="604">
    <text>However I do not get help unless I
feel tapped out.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="605">
    <text>Thanks!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="606">
    <text>That's new for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="607">
    <text>The times I out do myself give me pleasure and am excited to see what is next.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="608">
    <text>again, yet - I find that an explosion on TV gets me a little excited.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="609">
    <text>It is fun to get help from the characters with special powers when I am really stuck.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="610">
    <text>Thanks for all the fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="611">
    <text>You still preoccupy me happily!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="612">
    <text>Now I am ready to go back and give it another try.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="613">
    <text>Hi, my aim has improved as has my ability to figure out how to get 3 stars on most all levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="614">
    <text>Thanks for the fun!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="615">
    <text>I enjoy your creativity to find ever more and different puzzles for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="616">
    <text>M
I had to give one level to the eagle and have been playing lots of solitaire to help recover.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="617">
    <text>Still enjoy the black exploding birds - the finality they offer.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="618">
    <text>The ability to pick up and retry gives the game yet another 5 stars.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="619">
    <text>I got mine for free and you had to pay $1 for yours! U mad?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="620">
    <text>I fear my birds are only mildly annoyed &amp; therefore can't really punish the pigs sufficiently. That &amp; it still randomly crashes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="621">
    <text>I love angry birds but the new update is awful!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="622">
    <text>Even my cat likes this game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="623">
    <text>SHUT UP ALL U PEOPLE WHO HATE THIS YOUR GROUNDED FOREVER!!!!!UNTIL YOUR DEAD??????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="624">
    <text>Owned this game for years and loved it.  This new update is so bad I had to check the current reviews since the horrible gameplay left me frustrated and speechless.  All the reviews below about the update are 100% accurate.  It's complete garage and should ne avoided!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="625">
    <text>I CAN'T FART ON MY IPOD
There MUST BE A WAY to fart
In the game without in-app purchases</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="626">
    <text>i love the new pink bird though</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="new pink bird" to="24"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="627">
    <text>This game is awesome!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="628">
    <text>im so addicted to it! but it!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="629">
    <text>U will always rock!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="630">
    <text>The new level, you have got to be kidding me. I would play electric guitar to show how extreme crap it is. Get bad piggies cuz it rules. Rovio, you just made a new level be crap. I am so top cool.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="631">
    <text>It is ridiculous that the paid version has ads</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="632">
    <text>Fun when it first came out.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="633">
    <text>YOU MADE MY FAVORITE APP CRASH SO I CANT USE IT!!!!!!! i hate you</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="634">
    <text>I can't remember...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="635">
    <text>The new update levels are garbage.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new update" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="636">
    <text>It's like a loss of identity, worse than Alzheimer's but better than Dementia or maybe it's the other way around...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="637">
    <text>The star rating thing today is plain boring I would like to see the star rating music again</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="638">
    <text>even two times.......:(</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="639">
    <text>X-D</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="640">
    <text>This game is awesome and easy and there are so many settings!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="641">
    <text>No challenge, a new game for little kids. Paid for game and now have to put up with Ads???!!!!! Very ignorant!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="642">
    <text>I personally know I'm not with most of the people who wrote the review, I actually like the new level set. It's more about timing this time than anything else. My initial thought was that I didn't like it, but after playing more of it and learning the strategy behind it I don't mind it as much</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="643">
    <text>This game was great before it started putting prompts for reviews at every other startup and irritating popups for micro-transactions in EVERY LEVEL.  Dear Rovio; If you absolutely must continue trying to squeeze dollars from your customers this way, at least have the decency to include an opt-out for those like myself who are absolutely NOT going to spend an amount equal to what I paid for the app in the first place just to have some gimmicky and expendable in-game item.  They are making me not want to play your game or anything else published by your studio.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="644">
    <text>I was so happy that it came free for the week ! But sadly , it won't download correctly ;( it keeps saying &quot; can not download &quot; this makes me sad !</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="645">
    <text>That new uptake is so cool, I mean, the bomb bird is my FAVORITE bird, now add electric and it makes it AWESOME!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="40" term="bomb bird" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="646">
    <text>This is a fun and challenging game I love it???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="647">
    <text>when I click on the first level it crashes everytime! fix it please!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="648">
    <text>Can't deny these birds. Nice update!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="649">
    <text>When it was just the Mighty Eagle for sale.  As I always say &quot;IAP's taste bitter,  like ashes&quot; bummer...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="650">
    <text>I've had the Angry Birds app for 2-3 years now, but this update is so bad, I got frustrated and just deleted the entire app. There's zero skill involved, it's frustrating and no fun. I honestly don't understand how someone could enjoy this. So long...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="651">
    <text>You bought so did I? This game is old and if you think it's unfair they made the game free for a little bit you have problems it was 99 cents</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="652">
    <text>It is awesome It all ways has new updates  like every month!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="653">
    <text>???????? ???????? ??????????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="654">
    <text>Boo</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="655">
    <text>It crashes</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="656">
    <text>The game is really really fun it's just that I wishes u guys wouldn't have made it so hard to get the golden eggs like getting 3 stars on two full pages now that's jut retarted so plz fix it or make it easier to get them but overrall a great game</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="657">
    <text>i like there shout ahhraketkkkaaa!!!!!! coool game! awesome as always</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="658">
    <text>Great game that keeps me entertained for hours!  I'm always trying to beat a level as quickly as I can in anticipation of seeing what the next level is like. Highly recommended to my friends.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="659">
    <text>Read tittle</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="660">
    <text>Angry Birds has always been one of my favorite games, up until recently. It has become very buggy and slow, completely unpredictable and unreliable. I still try but it usually doesn't work. (I use an iPod touch 4g)
If it still works good on the newer devices i recommend this game, and if you have an older-ish device i'd steer clear.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="661">
    <text>Always a classic.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="662">
    <text>You could do better  ??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="663">
    <text>It's a smart phone game that has much fame they call it angry birds</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="664">
    <text>After more than a week since I downloaded the app it still has not installed. What's up with that</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="665">
    <text>Angry Birds International, each episode is a different city like New York, LA, Hong gong, Paris, WHATEVER!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="666">
    <text>New game play is horrible and stripped of all the elements that made angry birds fun. A disaster.  Finally an update to get me to put away a beloved game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="667">
    <text>I really like all of the angry birds games, and I have a suggestion for the next game. ANGRY BIRDS HEROES!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="668">
    <text>Crashes</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="669">
    <text>The new format is tedious, slow to restart, and too difficult and frustrating.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new format" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="670">
    <text>Stop it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="671">
    <text>Love angry birds, but be update is no good.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="672">
    <text>The new version should be its own game, not an update to the original.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="673">
    <text>Fix crashing issues on iPod touch 4</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="674">
    <text>Angry Birds is a highly addictive physics puzzle with a ton of content for just 1$. It starts off slowly, as you just throw red birds, after they introduce more birds, (around level 15) the game becomes more strategic. Highly recommended.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="675">
    <text>So many different birds!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="676">
    <text>So many fun levels!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="12" term="levels" to="18"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="677">
    <text>cant play new levels when i open it crashes please fix</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="678">
    <text>LOL DON'T DOWNLOAD IT. IT HAS 69 TROJAN VIRUSES. I DID 420 VIRUS SCANS BUT THEY ARE UNDETECTABLE.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="679">
    <text>Enjoy!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="680">
    <text>It's a nice little &quot;finger flicker&quot; game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="681">
    <text>My favorite bird so far is the black bomb bird.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="682">
    <text>Earning achievements in the game is pretty fun as well.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Earning achievements" to="20"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="683">
    <text>I love it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="684">
    <text>Some levels get pretty hard, but that's the fun in it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="685">
    <text>I try to go for something and it always points me away from the target I want to hit terrible update</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="94" term="update" to="100"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="686">
    <text>I buy games for just that, GAMES! I'm tired of developers writing games that are sooo closely &quot;joined at the hip&quot; to Apple's GameCenter to where GameCenter is soo &quot;in your face&quot; to where the game is NOT enjoyable! I don't do GameCenter!!! Apple refuses to truly disable this thing, but the programmers of games have an option of not allowing there apps to use it! The only internet gaming that I do is &quot;downloading&quot; the games. I don't really care what &quot;JDoe123&quot; or &quot;ImGonnaWin98&quot; is doing, I just want to take a few mins &amp; unwind! Add an &quot;in-app&quot; option of linking to Apple's GC or not!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="687">
    <text>At all.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="688">
    <text>I do not like the latest level.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="18" term="latest level" to="30"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="689">
    <text>Holy freaking crap takes forever to download!!!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="690">
    <text>I have Angry Birds Rio Free,Angry Birds Space,Angry Birds Seasons,And now Angry Birds Original</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="691">
    <text>Awesom</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="692">
    <text>I paid $1.00 for this and and doesn't even work! Don't waste your time and money on this</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="693">
    <text>When you update this app, installing sequence is frozen.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="26" term="installing sequence" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="694">
    <text>I do not like this version, too much advertising after each round.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="14" term="this version" to="26"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="695">
    <text>Also, overhead ad banners prevent you for obtaining a maximum score.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="696">
    <text>If u hate it, then you are going to forget it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="697">
    <text>Golf game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="698">
    <text>Fun &amp; challenging</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="699">
    <text>I dont like angry birds much but it was FREE :P</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="700">
    <text>The game is real awesome with the iPod 5th generation</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="701">
    <text>Great little game, I enjoy it with my 4 year old grandson when in a restaurant.
Awesome little app, and cool game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="702">
    <text>Makes time fly by while waiting in lines. My kids love to challenge me for high score. Good game without the usual gun or blood violence.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="703">
    <text>At first it was fun, now you guys are just money hungry, I mean ads? For something I paid for? Get rid of it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="704">
    <text>I cannot stop playing this game. Awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="705">
    <text>Please fix!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="706">
    <text>This new update is always crashing...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="707">
    <text>This game is way better thank angry birds seasons I'm glad it's finally free this made my day</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="708">
    <text>This should have been introduced as an entirely new (but still crappy) game, rather than as a new &quot;level&quot; with no resemblance to the original formula.  Quit the love affair with the Bad Piggies machines and stick to the original concept.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="709">
    <text>Ohohoh shockwave blow my mind out!! Never knew that there will be a power like that ....... My sister use that a lot of times . It is much easier but some
Are hard ....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="710">
    <text>Love it! Buy it! Absolute fun!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="711">
    <text>App of the week I installed this on my iPod. A week later it kept shutting down the game after one play... And sometimes it doesn't let me play other worlds! I'd rather get something else with my money.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="712">
    <text>Angry Birds is an overall success but I found some things that were great and others that weren't. I didn't get this app to long ago but I had played it before on another electronic device. Here is a brief recap on what you can expect if your going from tablet to apple. 

The UPS

1. This version includes power ups that fire up your bird or rumble the pigs.
2. In this Angry Birds (AB) you have a new level inspired by &quot;Bad Piggies&quot;.
3. AB is the classic fun it has always been.

The DOWNS

1. On the tablet AB is free, but Apple charges $0.99 which is kind of unfair.
2. As well, on my tablet they would give you a free &quot;mighty eagle&quot; everyday but Apple didn't have that.
3. This had nothing to do with this AB, but on tablet HD cost $0.99 while Apple charges $2.00.

If this is your first ever view of Angry Birds I'd say this is worth it. 

Enjoy!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="713">
    <text>GREAT, on the go game to play. Any time, anywhere</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="714">
    <text>They figured, since the game bad piggies was such a hit, they would incorporate more piggie vehicles in a fun mini game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="715">
    <text>Ok, so maybe the new mini game isn't a very big success, but Rovio is doing this because they're trying to appeal to a wider audience.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="17" term="new mini game" to="30"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="716">
    <text>Yes, I know, the levels for it aren't the best, and its hard as a rock to beat the last level, but its just an attempt to try something new.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="717">
    <text>I'm still giving angry birds 3 stars, since my little brother loves this game so much, but please do better next time.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="718">
    <text>- Lawgamer411</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="719">
    <text>I loved AB. I play to improve my ranking even tho I know I'll never get to the highest score cuz of all the hacker/cheater scores. But this new version is just crap. I still play it, just not the latest v. 

ps: please don't ruin AB Seasons with a similar version.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="720">
    <text>Same shots often yield different results. There's no skill involved. I have the nagging suspicion that the game is programmed to make you lose a lot so that you feel like it's addictive and you are improving.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="721">
    <text>Amazing app half the reason I got a iPod</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="722">
    <text>Epic Fail</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="723">
    <text>This is a great way to spend five minutes or lose yourself for hours. Kudos.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="724">
    <text>Plz add a super hero angry birds and have batman superman and everyone plz mention me in the game if you make it and have green lantern flash all of the justice league and also please have a marvel one too PLZ and yea thx plz read this -Tarik</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="10" term="super hero angry birds" to="32"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="725">
    <text>I enjoy it a lot.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="726">
    <text>I &lt;3 Angry Birds!!! Don't stop making new versions!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="727">
    <text>I can't believe Rovio went to all this trouble to turn a perfectly fun and addicting game into a game that should just be thrown in the trash!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="728">
    <text>I'm officially not an angry bird fan anymore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="729">
    <text>The introduction of ads has been quite annoying and has caused me to not want to play this game anymore.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="20" term="ads" to="23"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="730">
    <text>I have enjoyed this game for a few years now up until now.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="731">
    <text>I paid for this game and I don't understand why I have to be subject to the interruptions of ads during my play.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="732">
    <text>Some complain about the difficulty of that perfect hit, but that little bit of challenge and finding it is rather rewarding. I wouldn't want to 3 star everything right off the bat. I've spent a good bit of time on this game, and it's great! Looking forward to more levels. Not a huge fan of the update before last with the different gameplay style.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="733">
    <text>Best mobile game ever!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="734">
    <text>They miss the mark, literally. It is super frustrating because the aim is off. The bird never seems to go exactly where I want. Maybe the arrow is forcing auto aim or something but if the pig is in the middle of a contraption but there's some other weak point, like TNT then I want to aim at that. 

Right now it's essentially &quot;button mashing&quot; throwing as many birds in as fast as possible and hoping a few hit close to the mark. Of course the delays at the start of each level aren't helping either. Let me start attacking right away, don't let the pigs have a 5 second jump on me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="735">
    <text>It's more strategic and a lot of fun.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="736">
    <text>I think the new idea for reds angry feather is great!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="25" term="reds angry feather" to="43"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="737">
    <text>Don't buy if you have 4th gen iPod</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="738">
    <text>I don't even know what this new update is like, worked fine in the past, now it won't load on my 4th gen iPod touch.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="32" term="new update" to="42"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="739">
    <text>0.99 cents for the eagle and it was supposed to be unlimited usage but since the update now I have to wait an hour between uses STUPID CHANGE IT BACK!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="740">
    <text>I love this game!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="741">
    <text>Really hard to tell where I sit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="742">
    <text>Wish it would still show in vertical mode.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="743">
    <text>Great that I can move between iPhone and iPad without losing all of my hard work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="744">
    <text>Wish I could do that in space and rio.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="745">
    <text>Really hate the new leaderboard.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="16" term="new leaderboard" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="746">
    <text>I love the game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="747">
    <text>I used to love angry birds but after the new update whenever I try to play the new level the app stops altogether but it works fine for the rest of the levels rovio better fix this soon</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="748">
    <text>I HATE Red's mighty feather's it's stupid and it's a whole different thing then the rest of the game ??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="749">
    <text>The update accidentally deleting my game would have been more enjoyable.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="750">
    <text>Worst update ever.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="update" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="751">
    <text>Yay</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="752">
    <text>Rovio should make a angry birds hobbit    :)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="753">
    <text>This game is awsome but the new levels are hard but still awsome!!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="28" term="new levels" to="38"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="754">
    <text>This new update should be a whole new game, not an update. It's completely different, and completely awful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="755">
    <text>Love me some Angry Birds!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="756">
    <text>The best app to have when you are mad just fling the black bird and blow up a pig or six I goten two free sofar this one and rio. Can you make space free too?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="757">
    <text>Then need to make another free app of the week. It's been over  a MONTH and still no free app. I hope they make another free app cause I really want angry birds star wars</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="758">
    <text>Terrible. Random responsiveness of the red bird.  No interest in completing the levels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="759">
    <text>It is amazing game :)) I never get tired of playing this! :))</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="760">
    <text>You took a great game that was challenging and ruined it with childish gimmicks.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="761">
    <text>Where is the fun in &quot;cheating&quot; 

I won't be playing anymore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="762">
    <text>The power-ups are ridiculous and boring.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="763">
    <text>The excitement of a new update quickly turned to disappointment. This is not the game we have come to love. It's just not fun to play.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="764">
    <text>Hope you come out with something new other than Star Wars SOON!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="765">
    <text>I was addicted to the originals but DONE with this ridiculous game.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="766">
    <text>I absolutely cannot stand this game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="767">
    <text>Disappointed ):</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="768">
    <text>Cool</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="769">
    <text>This is the best game I have ever played but I think you should make something where you can make your own levels.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="93" term="make your own levels" to="113"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="770">
    <text>That would make this game a lot more fun because once you complete the game there are more levels that you can play that aren't part of the campaign.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="771">
    <text>That would be cool!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="772">
    <text>Crashes all the time!  I can't load the first level; it just shuts down!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="773">
    <text>Works ok with iPhone 4 and IOS6, but now crashes EVERY TIME on 1st Gen iPad running IOS5.1, so, as I said . . .</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="774">
    <text>I hope Rovio adds more levels to this new update and maybe include another bird besides Red Bird.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="775">
    <text>It's a lot more challenging hitting a moving object rather then something stationary.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="776">
    <text>Gotta disagree with all the haters.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="777">
    <text>I love seeing all of the piggies contraptions.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="25" term="piggies contraptions" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="778">
    <text>I love the newest update.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="779">
    <text>Rovio took a risk by adding something fresh and different and it works great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="780">
    <text>Couldn't Rovio just update the levels?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="781">
    <text>Please bring back that look we had in version 1.5.2 in the next update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="38" term="version 1.5.2" to="51"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="782">
    <text>Why can't it look like it did when it first came out?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="783">
    <text>Or at least let us play on lower versions!!!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="27" term="lower versions" to="41"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="784">
    <text>And update it soon.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="785">
    <text>I don't really like what angry birds looks like these days.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="786">
    <text>????If you like this check out Chaos Drive!????

????My invite ID is 787854195????

You'll see many familiar faces from LOC and GS!  The UI takes a little getting used to if you're used to LOC and GS.  More active game play.  Use my invite ID 787854195 to receive a SR card.  See ya in the game!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="787">
    <text>Wouldn't sync on 4G (data worked perfectly when using other apps). All progress was gone until I came home and logged back in to my Rovio account using my wifi, which means all my progress will be gone when I'm offline (on an airplane etc). A sure downside to the cloud functionality. I've already had to start from scratch many times when I'm playing on a new device.

One more thing, the original Angry Birds theme song is so much better than the new version. Bring it back!

Update: Thank you for bringing back the original theme song! Love it! I'm upgrading you to 4 stars!</text>
  </sentence>
</sentences>
