<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<sentences>
  <sentence id="1">
    <text>It has great interface with Google maps, allowing you to find the restaurant/hotel after you've read the reviews.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="13" term="interface" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="2">
    <text>This app is just as wonderful as the full web version.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="3">
    <text>Very helpful and can get exactly what I want</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="4">
    <text>Recomendo.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="5">
    <text>not as easy to use as desktop but still good</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="6">
    <text>Incredibly good!!!
Exec Chef Randy...extraordinary culinary skills

We caught fish by day and THE chef prepared them 4 different ways...all exquisite!!

Asst manager Jerry made our experience super!!!

Our waiter Jacob was remarkable...service, humor and professionalism !!!

Thanks very much</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="7">
    <text>This is my go-to for tips and reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="8">
    <text>App keeps on improving, I use it all the time, helpfull!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="9">
    <text>...it's been very helpful with booking a room, dining, etc, the few times I've used it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="10">
    <text>Cannot flip through photos.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="11">
    <text>Cannot page forward in saves.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="12">
    <text>...tripper advice for food &amp; lodging, especially in smaller towns! use it/contribute all the time. we wanderers have to help each other out...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="13">
    <text>Love it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="14">
    <text>Hooked on Marahau neat little cafe on the beach. Casual seating. Wonderful food. Try Lamb shank. Desert special. Service with a smile.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="15">
    <text>Works great!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="16">
    <text>Why the f would I want to know about an attraction in Germany when I am looking for something on the other side of the planet near my current location?!  2)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="17">
    <text>Other than that, terrific.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="18">
    <text>after zooming in back to where I actually am and picking something out to see more information the &quot;back to map&quot; button goes back to a blank page.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="104" term="back to map&quot; button" to="127"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="19">
    <text>Two major annoyances 1) set the app to use my current location then enter a search term and it zooms out to the entire world!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="20">
    <text>The map refuses to re load forcing one to start completely over again.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="4" term="map" to="7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="21">
    <text>Glad I chose it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="22">
    <text>You have the options you need when choosing a place to stay and the ratings are pretty reliable.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="23">
    <text>Definitely the best app for travelers.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="24">
    <text>Great app; easy to search and</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="19" term="search" to="25"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="25">
    <text>I love the save option for things you like!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="save" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="26">
    <text>Like a pocket version of the website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="27">
    <text>Great for traveling on the go, but lacks features to access your own personal profile, reviews etc.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="28">
    <text>Use this whenever I'm traveling and find it essential for judging suitability of restaurants and hotels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="29">
    <text>Excellent coverage of Kyoto.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="30">
    <text>Love this APP. Good info.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="31">
    <text>Thanks</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="32">
    <text>Works wherever we go in the world.  Currently trying it out in Korea! Most entries for places are in English. Though as you would expect many are in the host countries language.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="33">
    <text>Very helpfull</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="34">
    <text>App final shows the cuisine which previous versions did not. Great improvement and gives one to select wisely their choices to eat</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="35">
    <text>I found so many great hotels restaurants and things to do on this app. I use it now as  well to share my experiences to fellow travelers</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="36">
    <text>Reviews always include some grumpy people and some extra happy people, but they do help a lot.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="37">
    <text>Excellent app for planning a quick getaway, and flexing along the way as plans change.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="38">
    <text>The place is a DIVE. Based on Trip Advisor reviews, we made a reservation. It was so bad we just walked on our money.
I will post pictures later. Horrid. I don't know who wrote those reviews. Scam.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="39">
    <text>Struggle with the iPod and iPad apps includes the flashing of the screen anytime I type or enter a command(iPad) and when trying to book a hotel it won't move beyond the check-in and check-out dates(iPhone). Perhaps bc they're booked solid. But I don't think so. Just some minor improvements needed.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="40">
    <text>For hard to find places it takes a little more effort, still  easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="41">
    <text>I have written a couple of reviews with it and it is easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="42">
    <text>So easy to use - has become a valuable travel tool - wouldn't leave home without it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="43">
    <text>I have just started using the app for the vacation we are on in South Africa.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="44">
    <text>The restaurant reviews are invaluable in navigating the options available in the area.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="restaurant reviews" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="45">
    <text>We arrived at dollar with a 2 pm reservation plus the rapid service I signed up for last week. It's now been over an hour in line. The placed is mobed with hundreds of customers in line yet very very few counters open. It's about 40% running. There is no where to sit and crying babies and disappointed families in every corner. Food is on the floor and the place is complete disarray. I will never rent of the dump again. I would rather walk. Actually if I had walked to Pasadena I would be almost there. Plus the staff are rude and ignorant. No compassion for the customers standing in this never ending line rather than be with their families for Xmas. My daughter and I flew in from New Jersey to visit my mom. She has a whole dinner planned tonight. Unfortunately we will be here at dollar waiting for our pre reserved rental car. Rush hour starts in 30 minutes, that will end any chance of seeing my family tonight. Shame on dollar for not properly staffing their rental car center during the important holiday season.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="46">
    <text>I love this App when looking for hotels in areas I'm not familiar with!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="47">
    <text>I'm a flight attendant and do quite a bit of traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="48">
    <text>Very useful for gathering information to assemble dates, celebrations, trips, you name it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="16" term="gathering information" to="37"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="49">
    <text>I like the app but it has some bugs that are annoying, when I do a search and then refine the search it limits the options of filtering for distance or rating and I have to then do a new search to get the other to work, also when I go into a specific restaurant then go back out to the search page it takes me back out to the wrong search,
Needs work to be as good as it could be.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="50">
    <text>This is a great way to find out for locations that we are trying to visit, you can save so many problems reading the  comments!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="51">
    <text>Great information for places worldwide.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="52">
    <text>One of the few accurate guides for lodging and dining in Mexico</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="53">
    <text>Some are good ( look for reviewers who have posted a lot in the forums and also those who give evidence that they actually travel).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="54">
    <text>TA is okay on hotels, not so great on restaurants.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="55">
    <text>well, if you are relying on TA reviews to plan trips, you might want to supplement with other sites).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="56">
    <text>Sort of like TA reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="57">
    <text>Yelp, chow hound, que are much better.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="18" term="que" to="21"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="chow hound" to="16"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Yelp" to="4"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="58">
    <text>Regular TA much more usable than app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="59">
    <text>Ignore attraction reviews, head for forums ( again, some are good, but....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="60">
    <text>I love this app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="61">
    <text>Aplicativo super ?til, com varias dicas importantes e a opini?o de cada consumidor. Recomendo</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="62">
    <text>Tips, reservations, directions... I've been using TripAdvisor in all my trips for a long time, specially when I visit new places and need updated and reliable info. I also enjoy contributing with reviews!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="63">
    <text>The redesign of the app is perfect!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="redesign" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="64">
    <text>Keep up the good work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="65">
    <text>The recent update/upgrade has resulted in an app that's very slow, often freezing up and generally a pain to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="66">
    <text>It's invaluable to have this wealth of data at my fingertips; making our travel experience all the better as we focus on hotels and restaurants that get great reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="67">
    <text>I also use this app to write reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="68">
    <text>I use this app to find accommodations and restaurants on all our travels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="69">
    <text>I love being able to quickly write a review with my real-time thoughts.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="29" term="write a review" to="43"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="70">
    <text>Easier to get reviews here than Google.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="71">
    <text>Google doesn't have much.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="72">
    <text>Need as many reviews as possible when choosing a hotel especially.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="73">
    <text>Some reviews are silly, like personal complaints or an impatient person...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="5" term="reviews" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="74">
    <text>Just use common sense when reading and judging</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="75">
    <text>Excellent app for travel</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="76">
    <text>And the huge selection of restaurants is amazing!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="77">
    <text>I love this app, works in all my favorite cities.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="78">
    <text>Trial and error in trying those places is fun!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="79">
    <text>This app is fantastic!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="80">
    <text>The reviews are very helpful and I can always find great food no matter where with this app!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="reviews" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="81">
    <text>Just by chance we happened by this darling little place, that had 3 empty tables, 2with reservations. The server was extremely busy with 30 people to serve and did a fabulous job. She recommended the 2specials plus their 2best sellers, we decided one one of the specials and one of the favorites. Again, fabulous ! Then came the dessert crepe, absolutely declious ! Thinking of going back for breakfast.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="82">
    <text>It's great I like writing reviews and reading we're am gonna go next</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="83">
    <text>This app is so helpful!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="84">
    <text>The reviews and descriptions have not steered us wrong!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="85">
    <text>Super !!! Very useful !!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="86">
    <text>Amazing!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="87">
    <text>This app is way better then others I've looked at, there could be improvements but nothing substantial, I love the things to do category!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="88">
    <text>Great resource for all sorts of travel information.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="89">
    <text>Everything I need for travel at my fingertips.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="90">
    <text>?!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="91">
    <text>This app is a 'must-have' for iPads!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="92">
    <text>Wish could find another app similar to this one with attractions</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="93">
    <text>So awesome! Very helpful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="94">
    <text>Great app for travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="95">
    <text>Obviously every place isn't going to appear, and you should know better THAN to expect everything to be included; moreover, don't expect all reviews to be completely accurate or grammatically correct...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="96">
    <text>Mto bom!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="97">
    <text>I use it to plan all my trips.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="98">
    <text>Such a great app and easy to use!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="99">
    <text>I was go to this app for reviews very helpful!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="100">
    <text>Bring it back!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="101">
    <text>I am VERY disappointed the menu feature is not on the new update!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="102">
    <text>I love my trip advisor app and use it daily!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="103">
    <text>I just downloaded this app. 
Logged in.
Can't find reviews that I know that I've written.
As a new owner of one of the establishments, it's important for me to see ALLLL of the reviews that effect my business!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="104">
    <text>Upgrade needed!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="105">
    <text>I like the website but this app needs help.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="106">
    <text>Saved locations seem to vanish, it doesn't say what you're logged in as, and now it seems to have forgotten our username.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="0" term="Saved locations" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="107">
    <text>Love to see that available instead of having to get on the Mac/PC ...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="108">
    <text>Then they tried to do an &quot;ios7 friendly change&quot; and honestly, it just blows.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="109">
    <text>Also, I can't access my personal info to see where I stand with contributions and whatnot.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="110">
    <text>Sorry, but there was absolutely nothing wrong with the old version.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="55" term="old version" to="66"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="111">
    <text>Great app, accurate and helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="112">
    <text>Easy to navigate</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="113">
    <text>So thank you for having this app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="114">
    <text>Trip advisor is an awesome tool to share with others experiences that you've had to allow others to see how a hotel, attraction, etc...is before they make their choice.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="115">
    <text>Particularly now that they're pushing their own tablet.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="116">
    <text>Also, when doing a hotel search, you get far fewer hotels than when using the web site!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="117">
    <text>Since TripAdvisor is owned by Microsoft, I'm not surprised that they don't want to make the iPad app better!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="118">
    <text>Message notification is almost non-existent and its impossible to access any &quot;saved trips&quot; or add anything to a saved using the app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Message notification" to="20"/>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="66" term="access any &quot;saved trips" to="93"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="119">
    <text>The iPad version of this app needs work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="120">
    <text>Also, there's no way to filter out hotels when interested in only B&amp;B's.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="121">
    <text>Great app for travelers!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="122">
    <text>Very convenient, useful info and easy to use.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="24" term="info" to="28"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="123">
    <text>Incredibly slow and sluggish app (iPhone 4/iOS 7.0.3).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="124">
    <text>No possibility to select New Zealand dollar as a currency.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="125">
    <text>No se equivoca, la mejor referencia antes de viajar!! S?per recomendado</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="126">
    <text>Enough said.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="127">
    <text>Genco is an old world Italian restaurant, the sandwiches are the best in town. When you walk in you feel like you are being greeted by family, and the soup tastes every bit as good as grandmas soup. That is because everything at GENCO'S is homemade with love! A Must have is the wedding soup. I went in and had a small bowl, I was so sorry I didn't get some to bring home. 
I live in Boca Raton, and I drive to Fort Lauderdale just for one of there great sandwiches. All are excellent, hard to recommend on over the other. So keep going in and decide for yourselves!!!

Address for Genco is
257-B Commercial Blvd, Lauderdale By the Sea.

Also in case you are wondering I am not related in any way!Just love this place :)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="128">
    <text>Could use a few more filter options (a la the yelp app) , but overall great app and great site with many more, and more discerning, users as far as I can tell.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="10" term="a few more filter options" to="35"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="129">
    <text>Trip adviser helps me find all my info when traveling. 99% of the time it's right on.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="130">
    <text>I love this app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="131">
    <text>It offers everything from the website all in the palm of my hand.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="132">
    <text>I love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="133">
    <text>Great!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="134">
    <text>Can't sort for anything - price, distance, rating - anything!! Defeats the whole point of the app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="135">
    <text>This was one of the two most used apps on my recent trip to Germany!  Keep up the great work.  Kudos to the dev team</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="136">
    <text>I find this App very helpful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="137">
    <text>It's so easy to find terrific restaurant!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="138">
    <text>I'm a big fan of TA. I also like to see pictures of places before going there in addition to reading reviews.

Seems like TA is not really making a lot of efforts to clean up pictures before they're posted. Many are upside down or sideways.

Not good!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="139">
    <text>Spend some time planning a trip with this app and you will know where you are and what to do when you get there.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="140">
    <text>Great way to find some things to do with good honest reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="141">
    <text>I downloaded the city app while I was travelling and was very happy to find that the maps worked even without using data.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="142">
    <text>Lets you write your review right away!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="143">
    <text>Love having the ability to rate places and have your opinion read by others.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="144">
    <text>Makes it easy to search places and see what others think before you go.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="145">
    <text>I am glad this app is available on iPhone and iPad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="146">
    <text>Don't have to wait until you get home.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="147">
    <text>I only used your app because, I thought it would show me excellent hotels that are smoker friendly! I found this is not the case &amp; feel your misrepresenting your app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="148">
    <text>The only setback is that not all proprieties are list in this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="149">
    <text>I use it every time I travel,,,</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="150">
    <text>Gran cantidad de informaci?n a un toque de pantalla!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="151">
    <text>I travel for a living and this is one of the apps I can't do without. Nice job all round!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="152">
    <text>I find tripadvisor very helpful when trying to find restaurants in particular.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="153">
    <text>Nice for travel!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="154">
    <text>App works fine, but I'd like to be able to fully view my account (contributions as an example) on the app. Also, the rating functionality is limited on the app versus the website - the app only allows you to give an overall rating and doesn't break it down further.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="155">
    <text>Have had for several months now. No crashes, no locking up. Shows me what I need to see.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="156">
    <text>Trip Advisor is a great service and they have produced a great iPad app to go with it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="157">
    <text>As a pro pilot, I use it all the time for hotel selection and things to do around the world.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="158">
    <text>The only way to search and research travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="159">
    <text>Easy to use app; very resourceful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="160">
    <text>Amazingly accept bad reviews of places which is especially helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="161">
    <text>My &quot;Go-To&quot; app for restaurant reviews. For a serious foodie this app will help you to avoid the dogs in town and discover the real gems. You can vote with your dollars and this app. Gotta love the power of social media to reward the best and ignore the rest.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="162">
    <text>The new version is much neater and easier to use.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="new version" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="163">
    <text>Our best friend abroad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="164">
    <text>I have tried its info a couple of times and it always turns out very reliable. Great service with this app. Just give it a try.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="165">
    <text>Great app for on the go!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="166">
    <text>I really love</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="167">
    <text>Thanks !</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="168">
    <text>Only recommendation: sites you get to through clicking on embedded links (restaurants or hotels) should be on Safari or another browser, not embedded.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="169">
    <text>Great app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="170">
    <text>TripAdvisor, what would we do without you ?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="171">
    <text>Easy to use updated info at hand</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="172">
    <text>This app is awesome!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="173">
    <text>Found some restaurants in my town that I didn't even know about and a couple that I thought had closed but just moved.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="174">
    <text>The Things To Do tab gives some really good ideas for a vacation and also just around where you live.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="175">
    <text>Love this App.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="176">
    <text>This is one of my go to Apps when planning anything from a trip to a date night to a day out with the family.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="177">
    <text>Restaurants, hotels, attractions, more. Favorites or &quot;must do's&quot; can be added to &quot;Save&quot; list. Have a question?  Ask it in &quot;Forums&quot;.  Get it. Use it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="178">
    <text>The app works very well at home or on the road, anywhere with an Internet connection.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="179">
    <text>IPad is my travel medium and this may be my most used app and easiest to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="180">
    <text>Great useful information !!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="181">
    <text>Recommend it to everyone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="182">
    <text>Awesome App!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="183">
    <text>It has helped me find so many restaurants in my area that I never even new were there!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="184">
    <text>Never make a reservation without checking TA. Always check reviews on restaurants, hotels, resorts, or attractions. Never worry about the results as the members tell the truth. There are differences of taste and level of service expected but you can read a few reviews and get a feel for what to expect.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="185">
    <text>Made planning my vacation very simple. Great information</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="186">
    <text>I've discovered that a lot of phone apps don't compare to the full website in terms of functionality. That is not the case with Trip Advisor- it works just like the website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="187">
    <text>The best and the best of these programs I've seen far too diverse. ????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="188">
    <text>TripAdvisor is the place I start my travel planning long before I make a booking. I can get great ideas from others experiences and the hotel reviews by others give a variety of perspectives which I find helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="189">
    <text>App works great!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="190">
    <text>We use to book our vacations and reviews from travelers are very helpful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="33" term="reviews" to="40"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="191">
    <text>Review your faves or use as a discovery or decision too or tie breaker!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="192">
    <text>Wonderfully handy app while traveling!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="193">
    <text>This was a great way for us to plan a trip to Martha's Vineyard.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="194">
    <text>Very useful app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="195">
    <text>We found out all we needed to know before we went.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="196">
    <text>Just got back from a trip in Spain and had numerous problems with this app.  It worked differently on the iPhone versus the iPad.  It kept locking up, which meZn I had to constantly &quot;hard restart&quot; my iPhone 5.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="197">
    <text>This app, will be useful on my motorcycle trips.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="198">
    <text>Consistently use trip advisor for all of my trips everywhere I go.  Wouldn't go without the app or the city guides.  Taking a star away because it keeps asking me to rate the app!   Annoying!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="199">
    <text>It has the option to save things which I like about. Places to see, forums, places to eat.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="200">
    <text>I use this site every time I travel and to learn about new places nearby. I consider it my most useful travel/dining app by far.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="201">
    <text>The map does not display all my saved locations. In the past version it worked fine.
How can I get my saves to show on the map?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="202">
    <text>Use Trip Advisor the time, very helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="203">
    <text>I can't figure out how to use it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="204">
    <text>It's too bad, cause I love Trip Advisor (website).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="205">
    <text>?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="206">
    <text>May delete it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="207">
    <text>?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="208">
    <text>Unable to access reviews, change information (user name, photo, etc).</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="10" term="access reviews" to="24"/>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="26" term="change information" to="44"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="209">
    <text>I use the attractions part to see best things in the area. Works EVERYTIME.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="210">
    <text>You can find different venues in almost any city.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="211">
    <text>This is a great app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="212">
    <text>Love the reviews other travelers give.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="9" term="reviews" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="213">
    <text>It is very helpful if you 're in an unfamiliar place.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="214">
    <text>Would be nice to see locations on a map and view restaurant menus.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="17" term="see locations on a map" to="39"/>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="44" term="view restaurant menus" to="65"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="215">
    <text>We don't book anything without checking Trip Advisor.  And, it provides a great opportunity to give feedback on our experiences.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="216">
    <text>I have used trip advisor on several trips- its reviews and recommendations have been an excellent compass to more enjoyable experiences.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="217">
    <text>I've utilized trip advisor as my new &quot;go to&quot; place for honest, impartial reviews. They haven't let me down :-)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="218">
    <text>Nice guide</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="219">
    <text>Amazingly easy to use and has a great user community</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="220">
    <text>Helped me plan my trip to Germany with ease.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="221">
    <text>If nothing else, this gives me a good place to start my searches. The reviews are usually up to date so I can trust the opinions to be accurate of the information i need now.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="222">
    <text>Better than any tour guide...for all pockets</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="223">
    <text>To whom ever needs a concise informative and a very interactive tool to help make that crucial decision of where and how then the Trip Advisor App is the one.......and i hate apps...so try it...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="224">
    <text>Candid comments are the most helpful when planning a travel and this app/site is the only place I look to, use, and trust!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="225">
    <text>This app and website are my best friend.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="226">
    <text>This should be the most trusted site ever!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="227">
    <text>Love trip advisor</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="228">
    <text>Very helpful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="229">
    <text>La mejor aplicaci?n para buscar bonitos lugares</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="230">
    <text>This is the only must have app if your an adventurous spirit! Love to travel and this app makes it even better!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="231">
    <text>Just what I was looking for!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="232">
    <text>Es una web muy completa que yo utilizo siempre para encontrar hoteles,tiene la ventaja que tiene fotos y comentarios de personas normales muy validos.
Para monumentos y cosas que ver es muy ?til tambi?n.En los restaurantes no me vale mucho, hay muchas opiniones de anglo hablantes y de low cost travellers y su gusto es muy diferente del m?o.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="233">
    <text>Change it back!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="234">
    <text>I love trip advisor &amp; until today I absolutely loved the app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="235">
    <text>They have made recent changes to the app which make it impossible to read a category of reviews.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="69" term="read a category of reviews" to="95"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="236">
    <text>I used to be able to click on any category of reviews for a hotel without having to read all 300 of them.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="237">
    <text>If you are going to make changes, make the app more efficient, not less so.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="238">
    <text>No longer quick &amp; easy to access in a snapshot when booking a hotel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="239">
    <text>It is an app - Good, bad &amp; ugly should be easily accessible independently for a snapshot of pros &amp; cons.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="240">
    <text>This new Trip advisor is great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="241">
    <text>I don't let one bad report influence me as they are very subjective.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="242">
    <text>I use this all the time when we are traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="243">
    <text>The information on dining and lodging us a great help and the unbiased reviews are welcomed.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="244">
    <text>The info provided is usually right on.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="245">
    <text>I find that I rely on TA quite often.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="246">
    <text>I love using the TA App whenever we travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="247">
    <text>Love being able to pull up the restaurants near me when on a trip. My husband and I always try to hit restaurants in the top 5 wherever we go, and they almost never disappoint!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="248">
    <text>Os coment?rios s?o muitos pr?ximos da realidade . Tenho conseguido muito boas dicas</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="249">
    <text>I wouldn't even CONSIDER booking a hotel room without consulting this amazing app.  No where is there so much info. And photos of where you are considering to stay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="250">
    <text>Place I go to get the scoop no matter where I am</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="251">
    <text>Awesome when traveling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="252">
    <text>Great app to have!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="253">
    <text>I wish Trip Advisor would improve their app. It's frustrating to use - can't filter easily.  Basically, the app is not intuitive.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="254">
    <text>Consensus averages gives good sense of what to expect. Reviewers are generally truthful and steer you straight.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="255">
    <text>It really does exactly what you need it to...advise you on any trip to anywhere !!! I love it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="256">
    <text>I downloaded an update and now the flight search doesn't work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="257">
    <text>I appreciate the easy access to reviews of restaurants and other places.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="17" term="easy access to reviews of restaurants and other places" to="71"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="258">
    <text>I've compared Trip Advisor to other flight search engines and it always found the best deal for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="259">
    <text>Please fix!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="260">
    <text>Really what I liked about the app is how accurate the flight search has been.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="54" term="flight search" to="67"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="261">
    <text>It looks good and it runs smooth</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="262">
    <text>Nice app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="263">
    <text>Please hasn't changed since 1975. Only two restaurants and the food was horrible. If you budget is low and your expectations are lower it's the perfect place. You get what you pay for.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="264">
    <text>What happened to the menu feature? And used to have a link to restaurant website.  Miss those features!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="265">
    <text>Spot on, Tripadvisor!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="266">
    <text>love this app and it's so helpful when I travel!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="267">
    <text>Este sitio es fabuloso, siempre ha sido ?til.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="268">
    <text>Can't sore reviews by star rating, lame.

Keeps demanding to post thugs on my behalf and won't let me sign in via Facebook when I click no, lame.

I'll still use it, but under protest.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="269">
    <text>Nice!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="270">
    <text>UI is terrible and now we have a continuous never-ending looping login everytime I try and write reviews</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="271">
    <text>Every update is worse than the last with this company.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="272">
    <text>The best resource for finding a decent place to stay. I have never been sorry for having read the reviews here. You have to be logical when deciding who to believe, so here is my formula:

What is the over-all rating?
What is the opinion of those people who stayed there recently?
What are the complaints?
What do you want from your stay?
How much do you want to spend? 
Is it worth it?

That formula has always worked for me,  and I depend on Trip Advisor anytime I am unfamiliar with a destination and need a place to stay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="273">
    <text>???????????? ??????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="274">
    <text>Would be a complete embarrassment even for a high school project. Barely ready for alpha.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="275">
    <text>i am a senior contributor and i love reading the reviews of others also.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="276">
    <text>its not as obvious as on the website.  a little user point of view engineering</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="277">
    <text>this really is a very good app for the ipad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="278">
    <text>trip advisor has proved to be a reliable source of information for me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="279">
    <text>would be great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="280">
    <text>one thing that annoys me is that the website is so well laid out and easy to navigate but the app takes a little learning to try and figure out where things are.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="281">
    <text>it really is a useful and well functioning app though.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="282">
    <text>I am a big trip advisor user, and am happy they have an app, but it is *useless* if you are in a place where you don't have data!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="283">
    <text>If you are going to go through the trouble of making an app, take advantage of what a native app allows you to do, like keep state and store data!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="284">
    <text>For example, I'm in Thailand.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="285">
    <text>I look forward to seeing the improvements.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="286">
    <text>Walk out of the hotel and it is all gone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="287">
    <text>I have wifi at my hotel, make some plans using TA and save some places.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="288">
    <text>!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="289">
    <text>Not only are the saves not available offline, even the restaurant that was on my screen gets wiped out and I'm back to the home screen when I go back to the app a few minutes later.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="290">
    <text>I should also be able to:
- write reviews for uploading later
- add new places that are not in the TA database (this part is super frustrating when you are off the beaten path).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="291">
    <text>Love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="292">
    <text>It rarely crashes and is loaded with lots of great info for trip planning.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="293">
    <text>Information is current to what's online and easy to navigate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Information" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="294">
    <text>We have used trip adviser on the web for many years. I'm so very glad this mobile app works just as well.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="295">
    <text>Will be back. Good service and food!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="296">
    <text>Very easy to locate places to eat, play, and stay</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="13" term="locate places to eat, play, and stay" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="297">
    <text>Update 11/05/13:
Now a bloated piece of junk. &quot;Advisor&quot; does not mean book hotels, see menus, or any of the other crapola that has been added to this app. Time to locate a better app than this one. 

----------
Previously: 
Cannot add a business
Cannot report a name change for a business

Does not understand that a &quot;nearby&quot; business that is 25 miles away is not nearby, especially in a city like Chicago

Biased toward certain businesses, skipping past local businesses for &quot;trendy&quot;, or &quot;favored&quot; businesses. Advertisers perhaps?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="298">
    <text>Needs work</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="299">
    <text>Great idea</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="300">
    <text>We've used this app successfully in the U.S., Barbados &amp; Costa Rica and it's been ultra helpful. When visiting foreign countries, Be sure to see how many reviews are posted for a place &amp; the overall rating before you &quot;pull the trigger&quot; &amp; give them your hard earned money.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="301">
    <text>I love using trip advisor and the app works great!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="302">
    <text>This app is very convenient not just when traveling but also finding out cool stuff in your home town.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="303">
    <text>You won't be disappointed</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="304">
    <text>A must have for any one who loves planning trips.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="305">
    <text>Great ap!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="306">
    <text>Trip Advisor was very helpful on our trip to OH.  I wouldn't want to be without it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="307">
    <text>Easy to use on the iPad or iPhone for traveling and quick searches for restaurants.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="308">
    <text>For trip planning its better to log in on a computer to see the full application.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="309">
    <text>Ideal para viajar en todos los sentidos...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="310">
    <text>I use TripAdvisor to checkout restaurant  and hotels. I regularly write reviews. Great aide to proving leisure time activities.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="311">
    <text>Excellent. A must have.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="312">
    <text>Love the regular website and the app makes it twice as easy to find all your travel info!
It's a great reference  for trip planning, day tripping or local exploring!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="313">
    <text>Great app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="314">
    <text>I'm surprised at all the very positive reviews of this app. It seemed to me that this app is not at all designed well for tourists. Here's why:

1. There is no way to save location for viewing offline. Your favorites are saved, but accessible only when you have access to the Internet, so if you've looked up a restaurant, but don't remember exactly where it is, you'll have to use international roaming just to check the map and see how close you are.

2. The search function does not allow you to apply new filters while keeping your previous ones. If I searched for $ and $$ restaurants in Prague, and then wanted to narrow the search to exclusively Czech food, for instance, it would erase the price limitations and show me $$$ and $$$$ Czech restaurants.

I ended up relying much more on recommendations from friends and blogs, which I then loaded onto Apple maps, which I could access offline. If only Yelp would go international!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="315">
    <text>This Is a must app if you do a lot of traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="316">
    <text>It is also easy to use and has a lot of really useful functionalities.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="317">
    <text>It has a lot of information.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="318">
    <text>Just remember that the reviews come from users so you should read a few before making a decision - and even potential check another source just for reference.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="319">
    <text>Also love to travel on my own time off and Trip Advisor is great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="320">
    <text>And remember that it doesn't work if you are off line!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="321">
    <text>It is very helpful - from St. Louis to San Isidro.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="322">
    <text>Travel a lot for work in the US and now globally.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="323">
    <text>But then again - when are we ever not connected any more!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="324">
    <text>I highly recommend it to novice and seasoned travelers alike!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="325">
    <text>So make sure - especially if you are traveling somewhere where you may not have data service to have a source handy that isn't dependent on being 'connected.'</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="326">
    <text>At least old app version had a distance filter, even if it was not user friendly/intuitive. Hopefully you have a quick upgrade in the works... And make sure you have actual users test it for intuitiveness. Not just your own people who already know the software and won't be able to spot problems as easily.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="327">
    <text>I was surprised how many timely and accurate reviews were here for Europe and Mexico.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="328">
    <text>Its not like any good native app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="329">
    <text>there is no proper navigation animation and flow.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="330">
    <text>zero smoothness, slow, worst design.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="29" term="design" to="35"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="331">
    <text>I really like this app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="332">
    <text>Very accurate when it comes to prices.. Booked my first flight through Trip Advisor yesterday!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="31" term="prices" to="37"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="333">
    <text>Thanks!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="334">
    <text>Badly done. Example: no coffee category. Cafe doesn't find coffee shops. One coffee house is listed as fast food. There isn't any fast food category in the app with which to find it again! Totally incompetent, these are extremely obvious and basic failings. And stop asking for location turned on!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="335">
    <text>I use this app all.the.time. Very handy and accurate</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="336">
    <text>Except for the pesky &quot;review reminder&quot; that kept popping up.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="26" term="review reminder" to="41"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="337">
    <text>Decent app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="338">
    <text>simple and to the point directly, love the pointing to my destination feature</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="339">
    <text>Now that I have the ability to review places right on my iPhone, I use my tripadvisor much more. And I'm very satisfied.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="340">
    <text>So handy, so insightful, so on target!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="341">
    <text>I like that you can post photos.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="342">
    <text>It's a great way to find a new food place even if you have lived there forever, I guarantee this app will find something new for you to try or see.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="343">
    <text>The ratings from users are so helpful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="ratings from users" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="344">
    <text>Love the mapping part too.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="9" term="mapping" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="345">
    <text>Just needs to work with iMacs or another map program to get from point to point</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="346">
    <text>Good app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="347">
    <text>Everything you need to know is all right here in one app - from reviews to prices and comparisons - you can plan your entire getaway without getting a headache.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="348">
    <text>Overall, a wonderful app that can't be beat!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="349">
    <text>What's not to like?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="350">
    <text>The only reason for not giving five stars is sometimes the app crashes without warning - not a huge deal, but definitely annoying.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="351">
    <text>Great app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="352">
    <text>Just like American Express, don't plan a trip without consulting this app. Invaluable information.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="353">
    <text>Love the ease of use of the app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="9" term="ease of use" to="20"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="354">
    <text>1.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="355">
    <text>However two features I use often are broken in this version:</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="356">
    <text>Filter by distance and sort by rating.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="357">
    <text>This was my favorite app and I use it a lot.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="358">
    <text>Used to be easy, but can't figure out how to it anymore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="359">
    <text>Near me feature: after selecting a restaurant and returning to list it loses the sorting by distance an it reverts to sorting by rating.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="360">
    <text>Only fix I found is to go back to home screen.
2.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="361">
    <text>Great design and functionality</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="design" to="12"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="17" term="functionality" to="30"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="362">
    <text>Good reviews</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="363">
    <text>Using it to read up on the places we will be going both before we booked for the reviews, and after booking for tips and tricks.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="364">
    <text>Mobile access to the forums is also great.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Mobile access to the forums" to="27"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="365">
    <text>Uploaded the app no problem, from there out - all problems. The only review I've been able to write so far has been this one boo!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="366">
    <text>Recently injured in a car accident, I can't sit at the computer for hours researching information for my up coming trip and was worried I wouldn't be able to gather enough to do the kind of thoroughness I like. This app makes it possible for me to do so on the bus, or lying comfortably in bed. Thanks!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="367">
    <text>However, in the first 10 minutes of using the app I found two major glitches - 1) when hitting the back button from a hotel page, it doesn't respond for upwards of 10 seconds, and if you hit it more than once before it loads, the app goes back to the home page and you lose your search preferences; 2) when changing check in/out dates, you can't go to another month; when you hit the &quot;next&quot; arrow, it flashes and then goes back to the current month - so don't plan on checking rates or availability unless you're traveling in the next few days.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="368">
    <text>Very poor design and easily preventable.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="10" term="design" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="369">
    <text>I love Trip Advisor and I love being able to use many of the web tools on mobile.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="370">
    <text>It's new and improved and so smooth to use, highly recommend If you like traveling! 5 stars!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="371">
    <text>Why can't I filter restaurants by cuisine anymore?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="16" term="filter restaurants by cuisine" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="372">
    <text>Switching to another app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="373">
    <text>I hate it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="374">
    <text>I always use this to find restaurants near me when I am traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="375">
    <text>Works great and reviews are usually on the mark.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="376">
    <text>Quem ja conhece o trip advisor agora pode usar ele direto no iPhone com as mesmas funcionalidades, muito pr?tico e eficiente!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="377">
    <text>Searched one city and now it is stuck there, i.e., can't change cities.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="61" term="change cities" to="74"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="378">
    <text>Worthless!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="379">
    <text>This app contains so much useful information it is truly addictive!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="380">
    <text>Such a handy app no matter where you are traveling!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="381">
    <text>I trust it more than almost every other ap on my phone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="382">
    <text>I get great ideas and reliable reviews from Trip Advisor.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="31" term="reviews" to="38"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="383">
    <text>Use it for every trip! Couldn't live without tripadvisor!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="384">
    <text>I absolutely love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="385">
    <text>It is so helpful when traveling, and also helpful at home to see what other people are saying about my favorite restaurants.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="386">
    <text>Otherwise, good for the basics!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="387">
    <text>Can't read your own contributions or see badges.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="388">
    <text>Have to scroll thru all the pictures to get to the end.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="389">
    <text>Can't vote reviews helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="390">
    <text>Back button needs work as well.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="391">
    <text>Need to improve functionality on this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="392">
    <text>Would be nice if you could skip to the oldest/ newest Pics without scrolling thru each one.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="393">
    <text>Very helpful for honest information</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="394">
    <text>Overpriced. Portions were a joke. Much better restaurants to choose from</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="395">
    <text>It helps us narrow down where we should eat, stay and play,
as sometimes we can't seem to make up our minds.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="396">
    <text>Updated version is terrible, let me have the old one back please

We love this app and take it everywhere we travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="397">
    <text>Still love this app, used it 4 times just today!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="398">
    <text>Everywhere we have chosen off of Trip Advisor has been spot on, and when we travel we want to have great experience and Trip Advisor and fellow travelers make that happen!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="399">
    <text>So I'll bump up to three stars
old review below...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="400">
    <text>Getting use to newer version still like the web site better.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="401">
    <text>Thanks and fellow travelers keep up the great writing and sharing!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="402">
    <text>Easy to use and very accurate.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="403">
    <text>I always go to trip advisor to see opinions whether the are good reviews or not.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="404">
    <text>Thanks for the great app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="405">
    <text>I was hoping to replace Yelp and Foursquare with Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="406">
    <text>Disappointed I won't be able to.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="407">
    <text>The deal breaker is you can't check in on a location.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="34" term="check in on a location" to="56"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="408">
    <text>I love this app and it is has a lot of helpful information on it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="409">
    <text>Since I did update unable to even open app!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="34" term="open app" to="42"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="410">
    <text>What is going on??</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="411">
    <text>This is a rare misstep for them.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="412">
    <text>There is no more sorting by price so I will stop using this app and slow down on my reviews for TripAdvisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="413">
    <text>This app was almost perfect.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="414">
    <text>The mapping was a little klunky so when it said the update made that better I upgraded.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="mapping" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="415">
    <text>I love this app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="416">
    <text>Very helpful!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="417">
    <text>I really like it....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="418">
    <text>Beautiful app , that help you to choose based in your preference ...a lot of details...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="419">
    <text>Excellent app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="420">
    <text>I like this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="421">
    <text>Very helpful in finding out things to do!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="422">
    <text>I use TripAdvisor on my phone, iPad, and computer whenever I'm looking for a new restaurant or hotel. I trust the ratings from other reviewers, and I write many reviews myself...this app makes it easy to keep connected to this community.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="423">
    <text>We didn't have a single bad meal!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="424">
    <text>It made my vacation a wonderful experience.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="425">
    <text>We tried several restaurants based on the user reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="426">
    <text>I used trip advisor on a recent vacation.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="427">
    <text>I will use it on every future trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="428">
    <text>This app is easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="429">
    <text>I love this app for planning trips and finding things to do in places I visit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="430">
    <text>Easy to navigate and lots of information and pictures provided!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="8" term="navigate" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="431">
    <text>I have been using Trip Advisor for a while and really appreciate the feedback from other travelers.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="432">
    <text>This is a great program.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="433">
    <text>I'm looking in a few upcoming vacation spots and this app helped a lot with my itinerary!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="434">
    <text>Great</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="435">
    <text>app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="436">
    <text>I don't leave home without consulting this site.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="437">
    <text>Great app that is very user friendly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="438">
    <text>I use it very often.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="439">
    <text>Great app! Helps you plan a vacation or a simple weekend with honest reviews about companies.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="440">
    <text>Keeps crashing</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="441">
    <text>I like Google + Local saves option much better.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="442">
    <text>This app even if you select view all saves still forces you to only see saves for one location at a time.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="443">
    <text>Outside of the saves and lack of professional reviews (I hate relying on user reviews) this is the most useful travel review app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="111" term="travel review app" to="128"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="444">
    <text>Love everything about this app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="445">
    <text>Love this app!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="446">
    <text>Perhaps over simplified but more impressive is the GPS element, a nicer attribute that the website lacks.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="447">
    <text>Easy to navigate and responds well to actions indicated by users.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="448">
    <text>We used recently for a very impromptu trip to Florida and was extremely pleased with the ease of use and the quality of reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="449">
    <text>App is easy to use both for writing reviews and reading them.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="450">
    <text>However, the traveler submitted photos are slow to load and sometimes the app seems to lag.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="451">
    <text>I like the app UI and ease of use.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="app UI" to="17"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="452">
    <text>The app has a few features I didn't even see on the website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="453">
    <text>Used it to research hotels for an upcoming trip to Singapore.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="454">
    <text>tripadvisor is very good app i recommended that any one need any thing from shop to activities downloaded and enjoy it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="455">
    <text>Solid app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="app" to="9"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="456">
    <text>finding that I depend on TA more and more whenever I'm on the road.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="457">
    <text>Restaurant ratings are spot-on, hotel ratings very accurate....</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Restaurant ratings" to="18"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="32" term="hotel ratings" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="458">
    <text>I never travel anywhere without first checking out trip advisor</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="459">
    <text>Nice to have on your phone when traveling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="460">
    <text>It's great to get other users perceptions, even better when they leave insider tips</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="461">
    <text>The app never accepted the review.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="14" term="accepted the review" to="33"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="462">
    <text>I typed a complete review and then clicked the submit button.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="463">
    <text>The latest version has an intermittent bug.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="464">
    <text>The button flashed and that was it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="465">
    <text>I guess I'll reboot the app and try again.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="466">
    <text>I clicked Add Photo and added one to the review that was never accepted, and it appears to have accepted the photo without the review, which is still visible.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="467">
    <text>There is no error message, and everything else seems to work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="468">
    <text>I even received an email thanking me for the photo but did not receive one for the review.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="469">
    <text>Running my own business this app is ideal for keeping me connected with customers to see what we can do better or just keep doing!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="470">
    <text>You can only have horizontal use, which I never like to use. It doesn't have all of the features of the website: for instance, on the app I can't look back at what I previously reviewed. It's just not as good as the website; no reason to download.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="471">
    <text>Always happy with TripAdvisor recommendations</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="18" term="TripAdvisor recommendations" to="45"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="472">
    <text>I'm a traveler from way back, whether on business or pleasure, I may not have time to squander. This app helps me select the best places to see and things to do when I'm out and about.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="473">
    <text>!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="474">
    <text>It's great!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="475">
    <text>I always consult Trip Advisor whenever we are planning a trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="476">
    <text>I love Trip Advisor.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="7" term="Trip Advisor" to="19"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="477">
    <text>The wealth of info alone would make it wonderful - but what a bonus to be able to review places you have been.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="478">
    <text>Shame.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="479">
    <text>Unfortunately I delete it within 10 minutes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="480">
    <text>It froze a lot and I kept getting stuck only in certain cities while searching for hotels within a small country with no option to go back.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="481">
    <text>I love trip advisor and I was glad to see an app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="482">
    <text>Excellent application for search in the area of Tourism (hotels, restaurants, attractions, etc.)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="483">
    <text>This app helped me a lot and I really like it. I really and truly recommend that people should buy this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="484">
    <text>Baj? la aplicaci?n para revisar en mayor detalle lugares y tipos de hoteles que estaba viendo en la versi?n web, sin embargo no encontr? ni siquiera la Villa que hab?a encontrado en el web. Por otro lado, no encontr? donde cambiar la moneda y me aparece todo en euro. 
En definitiva, pareciera servir cuando uno tiene elegido el hotel para s?lo revisar como les pareci? a quienes antes estuvieron en ?l....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="485">
    <text>If I don't take a look at this App I think about the place twice.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="486">
    <text>Two thumbs up!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="487">
    <text>Great App and features.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="488">
    <text>Much better after latest update, had trouble saving reviews until updated!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="18" term="latest update" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="489">
    <text>Map isn't even as easy to see and read.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="490">
    <text>The former app was so user friendly and laid out well for navigation.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="491">
    <text>The update, October 3, is more cumbersome, harder to get back to home screen, has no &quot;back screen&quot; button that I've found.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="update" to="10"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="492">
    <text>Am so tired of companies &quot;updating&quot; their apps just for the sake of updates!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="493">
    <text>We use Trip Advisor all the before and during our travels. Most of the commentaries are very helpful in making our trips successful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="494">
    <text>Great!!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="495">
    <text>Simple as that. There's not much to say because that's all I need in a travel app like this. Very transparent as well!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="496">
    <text>It is such a great app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="497">
    <text>I really have no words!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="498">
    <text>Speechless.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="499">
    <text>And thank you!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="500">
    <text>I love traveling and I just can't stop using this to do a the research! Congrats!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="501">
    <text>So helpful!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="502">
    <text>That would make this app absolutely amazing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="503">
    <text>Love the option to &quot;save&quot; places to go to.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="24" term="save&quot; places to go to" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="504">
    <text>Only thing I wish is that I could &quot;favorite&quot; form threads.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="39" term="favorite&quot; form threads" to="65"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="505">
    <text>Overall - terrific!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="506">
    <text>Great app so far.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="app" to="9"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="507">
    <text>Very user-friendly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="508">
    <text>But why not add a feature that allows users to share newly discovered thingstodo.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="47" term="share newly discovered thingstodo" to="80"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="509">
    <text>This app is amazing!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="510">
    <text>I would recommend it to everyone!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="511">
    <text>It has Ben great so far withstand couple of minor issues.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="512">
    <text>It'd be great if there was a way to see my &quot;saves&quot; sorted by distance as well as a way to mark them as seen.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="40" term="see my &quot;saves&quot; sorted by distance" to="81"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="513">
    <text>When left running in the background on some modes, I think it keeps location services on which seems to be draining my battery faster than usual.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="514">
    <text>Finally, when I'm using this while traveling, I really don't want to use international roaming to upload a review, but remind me later waits about 5 minutes and them pesters me again, so a star off for that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="515">
    <text>I've been using this app to plan and manage an overseas trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="516">
    <text>I'm not sure if it is that, or in just using it more than normal.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="517">
    <text>Pls add portrait view for iPad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="8" term="portrait view for iPad" to="30"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="518">
    <text>Pretty easy to use and navigate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="23" term="navigate" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="519">
    <text>Good reviews by serious travelers.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="5" term="reviews" to="12"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="520">
    <text>The best travel site for planning your stay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="521">
    <text>For sure can't beat the price ...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="522">
    <text>Easy to use gives good info on things to do, food, and lodging.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="523">
    <text>I am sure even Aliens would use this app when traveling on earth. If you wan to enjoy your trip, use this App, Period.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="524">
    <text>I like the reviews and I find them very helpful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="11" term="reviews" to="18"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="525">
    <text>I find that powerful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="526">
    <text>I find a lot of hotels and restaurants read their reviews and respond.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="527">
    <text>They come from real people and I often submit my own review.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="528">
    <text>I find its a good way to let hotels and Resturant know how they are doing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="529">
    <text>Different views show different information which often requires digging in different places to put together a complete picture of ratings, price, menu, etc.  Tripadvisor is great but the app has a ways to go to catch up with the website.  It feels like sections of the app were written by different people and then kludged together.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="530">
    <text>Has a terrible HTML look to it, super slow, and not as detailed as the website. Maybe it's because I usually travel in Asia, but it would be much easier - and faster - to just use the website instead of the app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="531">
    <text>Excelente para buscar hoteles y turismo</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="532">
    <text>The TripAdvisor App is a shorter and better way to look up something instead of going onto their website and wasting more time! Sometimes, you can't always find what you are looking for so you have to go on the website but, it's the majority. I do all of my bookings with TripAdvisor through the app or through the Internet and it still works very well! Great job!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="533">
    <text>We have used this app to plan for special occasions and fun outings! Has been a great resource!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="534">
    <text>Must have for traveling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="535">
    <text>Great app, no problems</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="536">
    <text>the app does not allow guests to 'like' or find helpful the reviews they are reading.  As a reviewer,  that is my reward.  It allows me the opportunity to see what readers like or find helpful. Please find a way to bring this mainstay of your website to the app/mobile version.  Your reviewers need it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="537">
    <text>Tons of info on the smallest towns in France. Great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="538">
    <text>Tripadvisor is like having a local guide with you</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="539">
    <text>Very helpful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="540">
    <text>Great app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="541">
    <text>This app will save you time and trouble to avoid the troublesome places.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="542">
    <text>clear. organized. rich.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="543">
    <text>With many people on it, it's great to find local places to eat &amp; visit while you are away.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="544">
    <text>Always find where to go when you travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="545">
    <text>Love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="546">
    <text>Planning a trip somewhere I've never been and enjoying to helpful info and the many comments from people who have made the same trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="547">
    <text>The communities / forums really make this an all around excellent travel app and website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="548">
    <text>Love it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="549">
    <text>I love this app!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="12" term="app" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="550">
    <text>Search function not working properly. Shows only a few, apparently random restaurants in area (Rome) no matter what I try. Frustrating. Have gone back to TA using Safari.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="551">
    <text>The app should be tweaked as it has some flaws.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="552">
    <text>I like trip advisor, one of the better reviews around.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="553">
    <text>Love being able to look up the specific areas I'm visiting and have LOCALS chiming in too!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="554">
    <text>Picture it this way, my unstimulating review of the tripadvisor app is pretty much what the tripadvisor app is, unstimulating.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="555">
    <text>For the most part it does what I want tripadvisor to do, help me choose what I want to do, where I want to go, where I should stay when I get there and what I should put in my belly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="556">
    <text>What I don't like is that it makes me re-log into tripadvisor from my iPad each and every time I use the app even with remember me on.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="557">
    <text>It will also freeze or crash semi-frequently.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="558">
    <text>Other than that it is pretty ok.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="559">
    <text>The app, itself gives you access to virtually everything you need to know to plan your trip.  For a particular site, hotel, etc. for which you need to know more, the app has a built-in web browser which takes you to iPad-friendly web sites.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="560">
    <text>Good app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="561">
    <text>Love it. Very useful and informative. Highly recommended download.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="562">
    <text>Many functionalities (e.g. Ratings) are not working properly on iPad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="563">
    <text>I really think you should improve the app , because when I searched for Qatar only 4 hotels &amp; 4 things to go to appeared whereas there is alot of places to go to in Qatar and obviously there are more hotels then 4 .</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="564">
    <text>Easy way to write reviews and find great places to go and the best places to eat.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="12" term="write reviews" to="25"/>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="30" term="find great places to go" to="53"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="565">
    <text>The &quot;month visited&quot; feature doesn't work.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="566">
    <text>I can't leave a review on my iphone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="567">
    <text>Otherwise it's great when traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="568">
    <text>Excellent for finding places of interest at your destination, love the map with the attractions and the routing via google maps</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="71" term="map with the attractions" to="95"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="569">
    <text>Very helpful when traveling. Love it :-)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="570">
    <text>Makes things so easy.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="571">
    <text>I love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="572">
    <text>We took a trip and used trip advisor to find the hotel and places to go. We had a great time. Took me a little time to realize I could not book hotels, but otherwise was invaluable for our trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="573">
    <text>Love the app but got noting on Ireland pleas help me</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="574">
    <text>Great to look for places And interesting things to do whileb ravelling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="575">
    <text>I click on it and the hotels I've saved are gone!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="576">
    <text>one so all my saves are gone!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="577">
    <text>The MySaves feature isn't working properly.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="4" term="MySaves" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="578">
    <text>I never made</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="579">
    <text>It says I have to sync my trip advisor account.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="580">
    <text>Again a crappy update thanks again trip advisor.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="15" term="update" to="21"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="581">
    <text>It's really helpful. Don't miss this app if you're on a long trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="582">
    <text>Muy ?til aplicacion, con bastantes datos. Recomendable</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="583">
    <text>Hemos disfrutado de una estancia excelente. 
Tuvimos la gran oportunidad de  compartir un excelente servicio en el Club Premium. Muy de especial Sandra Sanchez. 
Gracias por su excelente servicio. 
Ovidio y Maggie  Vichot 
Habitation # 3203</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="584">
    <text>282- 0426</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="585">
    <text>It does exactly as advertised. I'm a pilot for large U.S. airline and I use this app all the time. It just works!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="586">
    <text>True you can ask to see your saved hotels in say only Chicago,</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="587">
    <text>This is a pain especially when you are in a location with a poor signal.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="588">
    <text>If you don't have this app, it's certainly worthwhile, but if you do take a careful look at the latest version before you upgrade.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="589">
    <text>There was nothing wrong with the old version, and this new one eliminates one of the apps most useful features: previously your saved restaurants, hotels, etc, were automatically sorted by location, now all of them are shown at once which is really confusing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="590">
    <text>but if you then want to look for your saved restaurants in Chicago, you have to do a second sort.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="591">
    <text>Great app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="592">
    <text>It is a very goop application for tourisim</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="593">
    <text>Reviews and recommendations have never steered us wrong on this site!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="594">
    <text>Great app, just love it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="595">
    <text>I haven't had a problem using this app. My only issue is that I can't figure out how to look at my own reviews after i've posted them.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="596">
    <text>I use this app almost daily. I trust the reviews because unlike yelp or some of the other review forums there is this spam like quality where people are just shooting off at the mouth not so on trip advisor. Plus the coolest new feature is adding your Amex card for special benefits and offers</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="597">
    <text>I use this app all the time to get fast opinion so as not waste time or money in a tried and tested restaurant or hotel. It is easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="598">
    <text>I just plainly love this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="599">
    <text>Reviews are useful and the app is user-friendly.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Reviews" to="7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="600">
    <text>It helps me in selecting the places to travel, eat, stay.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="601">
    <text>I would recommend this app to everyone.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="602">
    <text>The reviews have always been accurate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="reviews" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="603">
    <text>I use the app all the time to find anything I need about traveling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="604">
    <text>Used it everyday on my travels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="605">
    <text>i love reading everone elses reviews and then checking it for myself most of the time they are on point others not so much but its good to get pointers so we dont get blindsided.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="7" term="reading everone elses reviews" to="36"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="606">
    <text>It never steers me wrong and it is so helpful to have.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="607">
    <text>On every trip we take I dont go anywhere until I check Trip Advisor!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="608">
    <text>I love this App</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="609">
    <text>Before I make up my own.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="610">
    <text>Great app anywhere, I go I can read other options.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="611">
    <text>Something must have changed with this app? I like it, and never did before. It's very user friendly, easy to say if a review was helpful and to write a review. Is that is what is new? The ability to write reviews on the app?? It's great, whenever on my iPad will use the app over the website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="612">
    <text>Nice app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="613">
    <text>Can't figure how to sort by price. I will use another app to search for Hotels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="614">
    <text>Example: went to Seoul, told a friend (native of Seoul) that I planned to dine at the #1 ranked restaurant...he had not heard of it and was very skeptical.  Later, we stopped by the restaurant to find the longest line to get in restaurant we had ever seen.  The line went down the street and around the block....amazing! I have the video on my phone to show people who are just learning about Trip Advisor.  I appreciate the reviews from people and try to contribute whenever I can.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="615">
    <text>Latest version crashes on launch on my iPhone 4, iOS 5.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="0" term="Latest version" to="14"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="616">
    <text>Please fix.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="617">
    <text>So convenient and easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="618">
    <text>I use this app from beginning to end when planning a trip or going out of town for business.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="619">
    <text>Love the rating system!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="9" term="rating system" to="22"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="620">
    <text>Love this app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="621">
    <text>I'm enjoying it so far hopefully when it's time for me to go out and do stuff ifs worth using!! :)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="622">
    <text>Excelente App para b?squeda tur?stica. Great app for travelers</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="623">
    <text>Com certeza um dos melhores aplicativos/sites de dicas de viagens!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="624">
    <text>Forums are very helpful, too.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Forums" to="6"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="625">
    <text>Every trip starts at tripadvisor :-)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="626">
    <text>Great reviews from the US to wherever!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="627">
    <text>What a great app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="628">
    <text>Easy to use, info is accurate and everything you need to know as a traveler or tourist!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="629">
    <text>Solid reviews.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="reviews" to="13"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="630">
    <text>Works well when you're looking up places on the go.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="631">
    <text>And, more importantly, directions!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="632">
    <text>This is wonderful app to take with you for travel ...</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="633">
    <text>And, to use at home.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="634">
    <text>Just got back from Chicago where we used this to find attractions, restaurants ....</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="635">
    <text>Don't  leave home without it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="636">
    <text>Great!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="637">
    <text>Now that I have found Trip Advisor, I do not do anything travel related without consulting it first.  If you do any traveling, for business or for fun, you must check out Trip Advisor!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="638">
    <text>I like how the map figure integrates with the locations being reviewed to give you an idea of where they are located. Also like how you can zoom in and out on the map to modify options. Having noted these positives it would be nice if the app allowed one to vote for helpful posts. Overall this will be great for use while on the road to complement the full web version.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="639">
    <text>Good app that works well except I have found multiple wrong addresses on it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="640">
    <text>All the email links included in Trip Advisor forum posts are not linkable

Bottom line - I love TripAdvisor on the WWW but only tolerate it on the iPad for the convenience of accessing a quick list of restaurants in areas where Yelp doesn't have a strong presence.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="641">
    <text>1. ALWAYS have to login again even when checking &quot;remember me&quot; (so I never login)
2.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="642">
    <text>Type too small to read in reviews so must use iPad's accessibility feature - why can't TripAdvisor allow stretching and zooming in?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="643">
    <text>3.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="644">
    <text>I don't have a personal assistant but  my work requires a fair amount of travel.  This app makes me feel like I have an assistant taking care of my travel plans!  Love it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="645">
    <text>Esta bueno</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="646">
    <text>There does not seem to be any way to search or view Bed &amp; Breakfast lodging options from the iPad app. 
Is Trip Advisor going hotels only?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="647">
    <text>Maybe I'm more critical.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="648">
    <text>I find that reviewers are generally too generous with their ratings and comments.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="649">
    <text>I'd like to be able to sort by rating, in most cases.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="650">
    <text>It's difficult to figure out the order in which places are listed:  is it by distance?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="651">
    <text>, rating?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="652">
    <text>, price?</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="653">
    <text>All that being said, I've been using it constantly on our recent trip.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="654">
    <text>It's easy to pull up nearby restaurants and hotels, or by city, and easy to write reviews.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="655">
    <text>Exc</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="656">
    <text>Great app to go to a place you never been, gives you an idea from other people experiences</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="657">
    <text>I never realized that so many people do a lot of research of Hotels prior to booking. Hope all my reviews will help everyone out!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="658">
    <text>Great app, works great for all my travels for both business and personal.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="659">
    <text>If I want to take a customer out for lunch or dinner I know exactly where to go, and know that it will be great.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="660">
    <text>My nay complaint is the maps, they're sometimes hard to use (if you move it a bit ti see whats around, it will automatically change the results to new search results in that area...).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="661">
    <text>Excellent tool for planning a trip, the reviews people post are always very high quality and helpful.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="662">
    <text>But nonetheless very good and useful, thanks for the great, free app TipAdviser!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="663">
    <text>They're also not very detailed, street names etc.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="664">
    <text>Easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="665">
    <text>Nice app</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="666">
    <text>I love the fact that it lets you upload pictures of places.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="33" term="upload pictures of places" to="58"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="667">
    <text>Trip advisor is a very helpful tool for those who like to travel, yet do not know the areas they are about to visit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="668">
    <text>????? ???? ??? ????? ????? ???</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="669">
    <text>Very good for the iPhone</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="670">
    <text>Is quick, easy, but above all is the cheapest way to fly</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="671">
    <text>In a trip to Florida, I relied on this app for all my adventures, and I was not disappointed. It has stuff on the big touristy cities and on the small local stuff too. Love it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="672">
    <text>The app takes me to Manzanillo Mexico.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="673">
    <text>For example, I am vacationing in Ixtapa/Zihuatanejo  Mexico.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="674">
    <text>I want to search for a restaurant in Zihuatanejo by name.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="675">
    <text>I set the filter to Zihuatanejo and I want to find information on Manzanillo bay in Zihuatanejo.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="676">
    <text>It needs a great deal of work to improve its functionality.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="677">
    <text>It shows me every restaurant with that name in their system around the world and then I have to search thru the list to find the restaurant I want.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="678">
    <text>Trip Advisor provides very useful information but extremely difficult to search.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="73" term="search" to="79"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="679">
    <text>Very awkward to say the least.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="680">
    <text>Even though I set the filter to Zihuatanejo it combines the Ixtapa restaurants in the list.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="681">
    <text>The app is limited on functionality</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="682">
    <text>It goes to a black screen and just stays at that black screen until I turn my phone off and on.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="683">
    <text>Let me start by saying that I am a huge fan of Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="684">
    <text>It's very laggy, and crashes every single time I try to scroll through any pictures.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="685">
    <text>I use the app to read the reviews and scroll through a few photos, so it is very aggravating.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="686">
    <text>I am however very disappointed in the app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="687">
    <text>Overall the app lags constantly, and crashes often.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="688">
    <text>I am holding out on deleting the app in hopes of an update that fixes all the problems, but until then I'll be sticking to the website version of Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="689">
    <text>The app really helped us navigate where to go - and what to avoid.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="690">
    <text>As a frequent business traveler, I always check tripadvisor before heading into a non none restaurant and find it to be spot on most of the time.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="691">
    <text>Have used it many times for domestic and international traveling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="692">
    <text>Whenever we take a trip anywhere Trip Advisor is the first app or website I visit. We have found many different and interesting places we wouldn't have found otherwise. Thank you Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="693">
    <text>I almost always look at reviews before I travel for work or pleasure to get a sense of how the properties are performing. Doesn't take long to sort out which places are doing a good job. One bad review does not a bad experience make but if you see several it might be time to re-think your plans.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="694">
    <text>Good app but I wish it had all the details when adding a review like it does on the website.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="695">
    <text>I would like it if there were more subcategories in the things to do such as museums, zoo, sports arena, etc.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="696">
    <text>An option to change each list hierarchy for distance, price, rating also would help.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="697">
    <text>I have used on several trips now to evaluate lodging, dining and things to do.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="698">
    <text>I've found the reviews as a whole very helpful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="19" term="reviews" to="26"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="699">
    <text>Thanks to the staff and management for making my 1st trip to London so fabulous! From uniforms (doorman especially) to spotless rooms and common spaces it was unexpected quality and service.   Dinning is A+ but being from the US I didn't get the pork and beans on the breakfast buffet. Try a steak sandwich in the tea area it's wonderful along with the cute and  delicious little bites they serve with tea. Too posh. No need to prebook tours in US the Concierge staff can do it and know more about the sites.
Basically, I loved this place, so I'm planing a trip to London by myself and feel totally secure,safe, and familiar with the area and hotel! Cee ya soon.
Byudeva</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="700">
    <text>Love taking trips with the family and this app helps full those &quot;what are we doing today?&quot; questions.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="701">
    <text>Love it. It's been a very convenient addition for me in my arsenal.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="702">
    <text>This app has been very helpful whether going on vacation or just trying a different restaurant around town.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="703">
    <text>Definitely has made vacations more enjoyable!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="704">
    <text>I really enjoy trip advisor and being able to have a good app on my iPad is wonderful. The app has all the functionality of the website and as long as u create an account (you can link one to Facebook), u can access ur saves anywhere. Definitely a must have if u travel a lot.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="705">
    <text>Now the links are gone and there is much less versatility present</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="706">
    <text>Prior version was better.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Prior version" to="13"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="707">
    <text>The newest update seems to only want to link you to book a hotel room. You can't click on the ratings review to skip to just the good-bad-terrible reviews. At one point trip advisor was the only site I trusted to give real reviews. I don't feel the same anymore. It really is sad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="708">
    <text>Love it!  Makes finding things to do and places to stay and eat easy!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="709">
    <text>I like it before the OS7 changes.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="710">
    <text>I love the actual tripadvisor website and never choose a hotel without checking TA first.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="711">
    <text>That said, I hate the app now.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="712">
    <text>Wish I could undo the so called upgrade.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="713">
    <text>Now I hate it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="714">
    <text>Very nice app for check restaurant hotel and more, very attentive !!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="715">
    <text>Very easy to use!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="716">
    <text>Great app very helpful!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="717">
    <text>Finally a tool that helps you find places to visit.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="718">
    <text>I definitely appreciate all of the reviews posted, both positive and negative, to get a sense of the restaurant &amp;/or hotel I am considering, so I can make an informed decision. I also enjoy being able to share about those places I really enjoy...and those I don't!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="719">
    <text>Love it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="720">
    <text>Very user friendly and easy to navigate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="31" term="navigate" to="39"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="721">
    <text>Great app to write my reviews on!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="722">
    <text>Crashes, and returns inaccurate results.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="723">
    <text>Totally useless when yo are traveling</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="724">
    <text>This version no longer does that.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="725">
    <text>In the previous version you could scroll the map and see your desired categories update on screen.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="726">
    <text>You have to type in a cityor location.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="727">
    <text>This update negates the usefulness of the previous app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="728">
    <text>It does not know where yo are at any more and does not provide location service.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="729">
    <text>We love to travel both locally and internationally. Use this app every time.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="730">
    <text>Finds nice restaurants:)</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="731">
    <text>Their data base of hotels and things to do are growing every day, lots of great information and tips for planning a vacation.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="732">
    <text>I have been using this app for more than a year , and definitely is the best travel app in the market , is the only way to know by fellow travelers what's happening in the city your are visiting related to hotels, restaurants , tours etc.

Keep improving !!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="733">
    <text>We don't use any other review site.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="734">
    <text>Great app to have when planning or on a vacation
It has great options on family fun stuff to do</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="735">
    <text>Great app to get info on any place you want to travel!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="736">
    <text>Accurate reviews from other travelers..and great recommendations for thing to do.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="737">
    <text>I use this EVERY time I travel.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="738">
    <text>That's what I say</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="739">
    <text>Love this app it's been so helpful on my last 3 vacations</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="740">
    <text>We use this app in planning our trips and while on our trips for restaurants, clubs and sightseeing! Great help!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="741">
    <text>We see and visit so many places we would have missed if not for Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="742">
    <text>Love Trip Advisor.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="743">
    <text>Good so far</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="744">
    <text>Works fine, no complaints here</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="745">
    <text>Facebook login required to save or sign in. That takes an above average app to below average.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="746">
    <text>I just started using this App and the 1st thing I noticed is that under restaurants' filters, there is a large selection, but Kosher isn't one of them. Since it's the one that matters the most to me, I am rather disappointed.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="747">
    <text>Add features available in the full web version such as adding the 'like' button for reviews and adding details on the reviewers.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="748">
    <text>Needs a portrait view.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="749">
    <text>It helps when your on vacation looking for a place to eat.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="750">
    <text>I like this app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="751">
    <text>Not as good as the website!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="752">
    <text>Hope to add more filters (such as dining options), also clicking &quot;back&quot; after choosing a restaurant clears the previous filter and I get the main list!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="12" term="more filters (such as dining options)" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="753">
    <text>I would strongly recommend it</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="754">
    <text>We travel the world a lot and this is the perfect app to help us identify restaurants and hotels.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="755">
    <text>We find it far more useful and up to date than the guide Michelin.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="756">
    <text>We have found the reviews all very useful and accurate.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="757">
    <text>Love using it to read reviews if unknown restaurants before we go.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="758">
    <text>Sometimes difficult to navigate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="23" term="navigate" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="759">
    <text>The app and mobile presence both need help, fast. The inability to do much of anything other than browse is tough. For people searching its great but the reviewers matter too. At this point mobile needs to be just as capable as desktop. &quot;View Full Site&quot; means not enough focus on mobile. Please increase features!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="760">
    <text>Great app, but viewing photos are a pain to get out of.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="761">
    <text>iPhone 4S.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="762">
    <text>It seems to stick after  touching the &quot;Done&quot; button.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="763">
    <text>The handiest app alive</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="764">
    <text>A functional and stylish update to one of the best travel tools around.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="25" term="update" to="31"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="765">
    <text>We like to see what people say before trying a new place and this helps greatly. You can sort from the good and bad reviews and then decide.  The app gives a blank green screen sometimes when posting a review and some other glitches but don't let that stop you.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="766">
    <text>I tried to write a review on a restaurant, and the app kept asking me to sign in with Facebook, which I did several times. It never would let me submit the review.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="767">
    <text>Fast and accurate.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="768">
    <text>Real nice app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="769">
    <text>Don't waste your time with this app!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="770">
    <text>Prices listed never match the actual hotel prices.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="Prices listed" to="13"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="771">
    <text>Easy way to rate and write reviews</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="12" term="rate and write reviews" to="34"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="772">
    <text>The new app seems to be based on html5.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="773">
    <text>While it's functional but it loads very slow and looks ugly.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="33" term="loads" to="38"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="774">
    <text>Useful and speedy. But must have Internet.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="775">
    <text>I use the site extensively for planning trips like the one we took to Hawaii. It helped us pick our hotel and the restaurants we ate at and the excursion we did.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="776">
    <text>Works well, wish it was more integrated with google maps</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="777">
    <text>Presently on vacation and TripAdvisor has been exceptionally useful in identifying good places to eat. Starting to rely on it more &amp; more.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="778">
    <text>Can't even write a good review cause I have not been able to use the app w/o it asking me every two seconds to rate it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="B" from="15" term="write a good review" to="34"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="779">
    <text>Classified Chinese restaurants as French.  Ridiculous.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="780">
    <text>Any time we try someplace new, whether it be a hotel, restaurant or other large attraction, checking Trip Advisor is a must!  I appreciate the honesty of others and the ease of navigating through the site.  Thank you!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="781">
    <text>Nothing else needs to be said!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="782">
    <text>As an RV'er, this app is of great useage.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="783">
    <text>From finding businesses to grabbing a meal on the run, this is a fantastic tool.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="784">
    <text>Great trip tool.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="6" term="trip tool" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="785">
    <text>Thank you for the initiative.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="786">
    <text>Can visit the great places no matter where i go wz real reviews from ppl like me</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="787">
    <text>Love this app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="788">
    <text>Just started using Trip Advisor &amp; love it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="789">
    <text>Trip advisor has been easy to use   Making it an invaluable tool</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="790">
    <text>Great application when travelling.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="791">
    <text>The interface is easy to understand.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="4" term="interface" to="13"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="792">
    <text>Other than that, it's perfect.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="793">
    <text>This app has been very helpful on my honeymoon search.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="794">
    <text>It would be nice to be able to enlarge the photos though.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="31" term="enlarge the photos" to="49"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="795">
    <text>Excellent!!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="796">
    <text>I use this frequently especially when traveling to find reliable food and fun options.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="797">
    <text>???????????????????</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="798">
    <text>Other than that it's very reliable!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="799">
    <text>I use this app a lot to write reviews, they need to have the option to add pictures from your mobile device.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="71" term="add pictures from your mobile device" to="107"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="800">
    <text>I hadn't.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="801">
    <text>Just beginning to travel and visit various restaurants and Trip Advisor has been extremely helpful in our selections.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="802">
    <text>Thanks to all who take the time to input positive and negative comments.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="803">
    <text>Sometimes I have gone against the comments and wish</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="804">
    <text>Majority of the comments critique level of service, cleanliness, price, kid friendly.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="805">
    <text>I travel throughout the Americas, Europe and Asia on the regular monthly basis . I have tried many of the travel guides written up by many notable magazines and were given high recommendations but none tach the usefulness of the tool . 

Some aides focus only in certain regions but even then I have found this tool to provide better advice not only in the same region but worldwide . 

I am a believer and a constant user now and would not leave home without . 

I would most certainly recommend this to anyone .</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="806">
    <text>Wish maps (locations of newer hotels were updated more).</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="807">
    <text>Would be great if age of property and renovation dates were included for hotels, too.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="808">
    <text>Also would love to have an individual resort map of all the resorts available to view.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="27" term="individual resort map of all the resorts available to view" to="85"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="809">
    <text>Great information is available.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="810">
    <text>Just started using the forum and I'm finding it very helpful. Forum members seem to really want to help,</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="811">
    <text>Not having a lot of time to plan vacations I rely on this app for all my planning and have found it to be really reliable.Time saved good choices and enjoyable times have resulted.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="812">
    <text>I always check Trip Advisor before I consider hotels, attractions, restaurants. It's invaluable and a great resource. Can't go wrong with it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="813">
    <text>The Trip Advisor iPad app lacks a lot to be desired for me. It's a better experience on your web browser. On the iPad app you can't hide the left side bar which takes up too much room after you find what you are looking for and you can't enlarge the font or stretch the screen on the app either. The browser experience has way too many pop out windows on Trip Advisor web site. 
Other than the listed items we love Trip Advisor, all the customer reviews are great when visiting a place you haven't been before.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="814">
    <text>stars if you make changes to the above listed items.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="815">
    <text>They are trying to push vacation listings, but you can't drill down to a neighborhood . Orlando is a big area and you get a zillion listings that come up. I need one near a particular neighborhood. You can't search for that and going through all their postings for Orlando isn't feasible. Use airbnb instead. They know what they are doing. You can put in any address where you need to be and listings pop up all around it. How can you miss something as simple as this? Those that have a listing on trip advisor must be losing out. I think they are now too big to care.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="816">
    <text>Una excelente app para los viajes</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="817">
    <text>Fantastic app!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="818">
    <text>Always useful and accurate</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="819">
    <text>I  downloaded trip advisor App for my iPhone. It shows information about large cities, places, destinations however, Information about hotels, restaurants and newer places are not in the data. It really did not help me much.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="820">
    <text>What a great aop</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="821">
    <text>Works well and helpful</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="822">
    <text>Help! Been re-installing/deleting it.. Still wont let me open the app! Please let us (old iphone users and old iOS users) use this app! Fix it for us!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="823">
    <text>If you have the patience to navigate through its, um, &quot;quirks,&quot; then you can get to their good info.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="824">
    <text>I like Trip Advisor, but their app is slow and feels buggy.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="825">
    <text>I'm in charlotte, nc.  I selected current location from the opening screen then selected restaurants.  The app pulled up the &quot;Current&quot; restaurant in Washington DC.  I then tried to sign in and the app ignored my constant clicks on the sign in button.  I then exited out of frustration.  I've used the app several time since it was updated and have been frustrated with the navigation every time.  Please fix this thing.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="826">
    <text>Everything you want from TripAdvisor</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="827">
    <text>I check Trip Advisor before booking any hotel or trip or for advice on where to eat while we're away, and what to expect.
I've had many successful, adventerous trips thanks to Trip Advisor!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="828">
    <text>I love having this both on my iPhone and iPad to reference when I'm on the road.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="829">
    <text>Soy fan?tico de esta app cada vez que viajo, el ranking de restaurantes es magn?fico.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="830">
    <text>I respect the opinions of others and this is the place to go for opinions</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="831">
    <text>I hate the new changes since the iOS7- it's not user friendly, keeps freezing and won't let you see pics.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="832">
    <text>Please bring back the old version, or fix this one!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="R" from="22" term="old version" to="33"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="833">
    <text>I am a senior contributor but lately when I try to open TripAdvisor on my IPhone 4; it starts to open for two seconds then I am back to my icons screen.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="834">
    <text>It is interesting but I don't know why it's seems to be extremely slow and apparently you cannot upload images with iPhone devices.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="835">
    <text>Your best trip companion !!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="10" term="trip companion" to="24"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="836">
    <text>Very handy app especially when I haven't exactly planned what I want to do in range area that I am visiting</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="837">
    <text>So easy to use.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="838">
    <text>And mostly the reviews turn out to be extremely
Credible.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="839">
    <text>I love it.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="840">
    <text>Great app for Europe, not as useful in the USA</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="841">
    <text>Works like it should.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="842">
    <text>Handy app to have your fingertips.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="843">
    <text>New version is terrible.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="0" term="New version" to="11"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="844">
    <text>Hate the design.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="9" term="design" to="15"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="845">
    <text>Very user friendly app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="846">
    <text>Simple interface encourages me to write more reviews!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="7" term="interface" to="16"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="847">
    <text>Any thing that can help me find a bar is awesome!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="848">
    <text>I found amazing on my india trup</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="849">
    <text>Probably my favorite feature of Tripadvisor is how current (fresh) the information is.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="850">
    <text>This is THE main source of travel info I use when planning a trip, whether looking for lodging, restaurants, things to do, nightlife or just tips about a destination I'm not familiar with.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="851">
    <text>this app and I never leave home without it!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="852">
    <text>Love</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="853">
    <text>Makes a huge difference.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="854">
    <text>You choose, a travel guide that was published several years ago or Tripadvisor with reviews posted this vet week!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="855">
    <text>I love traveling its helps me a lot and I help people too!!!</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="856">
    <text>No matter how many times I restart the app and apply so it sorts the results by rating, the app continues to sort the results by distance. Absolutely worthless to me when there are 700 results within 10 miles and I'm looking for the top 10 results.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="857">
    <text>If you want the best traveling guide app then look nowhere else. This will really make your travel in any country in the world the best travel experience. I ALWAYS depend on this app it become like a part of me.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="858">
    <text>Awesome</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="859">
    <text>Wont recommend</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="860">
    <text>Not a native iOS app.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="861">
    <text>Takes long to load and isnt responsive.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm class="E" from="14" term="load" to="18"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="862">
    <text>Very bad.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="863">
    <text>I've been using this app for some time now. I love it when it works and I love doing reviews but tonight I'm in Billings,  MT at the Spring Hill Suites. I'm using near me and it don't show at all.   I've stayed in Billings many times and this is one of the better hotels - it shouldn't be this hard to rate something.  Guys I know you can do better than this</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="864">
    <text>Trip Advisor is great for traveling and even better with the app on the go.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="865">
    <text>Highly recommend.</text>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="866">
    <text>I have used this for vacations to Paris, Miami, and Cape Cod.  Always find fun things to do and good food.</text>
  </sentence>
</sentences>
