<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<sentences>
  <sentence id="1">
    <text>Definitely liking this app. Use it all the time. It would be really nice if it gives us 10gb free space. ^^</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="free space"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="2">
    <text>I have a factory refurbished older iPad and it cannot run IOS 7.  Can't you make a &quot;legacy&quot; Dropbox app available for those of us that don't have brand new equipment?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="support older IOS"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="3">
    <text>Did not work on my new iPhone 5s. Only showed sliding logo's</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sliding logo"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="4">
    <text>Very convenient for moving files without connecting to a computer!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="moving files without connecting to a computer"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="5">
    <text>Downloaded the latest update and now my app has disappeared, and the App Store won't let me download it again.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Downloaded update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="6">
    <text>I love having all my photos backed up automatically and not having to keep them on my phone.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos backed up automatically"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos backed up not having to keep them on my pho"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="7">
    <text>Dropbox app is bug ridden and they have no desire to fix basic things. It may work for a while, but eventually it will break and there will be no recourse from Dropbox to fix it. Support will ignore you. Dropbox is extremely arrogant about. Competition is now catching up. Finally and thankfully.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Support"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="8">
    <text>Works well, especially for saving files for offline use.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving files for offline use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="9">
    <text>Have been using Google Drive for a few months, paid account - the desktop app was totally unreliable and failed to sync just too often. So came back to Dropbox, always syncing smartly and reliably.

A bit pricey though - almost twice as expensive as competitions if you want the extra space.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="extra space"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="10">
    <text>Wish I could rename files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="rename files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="11">
    <text>I have been an avid Dropbox user and supporter for a few years now. But with this new upgrade requiring iOS 7 (which I don't have), and many apps supporting other cloud storage providers, I find I may have to switch to Box, SugarSync, Mega, Mozy, or any of the other cloud storage sites who aren't forcing me to upgrade to iOS 7.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cloud storage "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade to iOS 7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="12">
    <text>Ever since iOS 7 update, Dropbox has not worked; constantly crashes, when it does run it is EXTREMELY slow, and there are problems with camera uploading. PLEASE FIX ASAP.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera uploading"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="EXTREMELY slow"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="13">
    <text>I install Dropbox yesterday. When I start the App the  dialog box ' app wants your location' appears in an endless loop</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="location"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="14">
    <text>UPDATE 2/21/13 New Update:
Same problem

Installed update and froze up. I can access through the &quot;open&quot; option on dropbox App Store page but not through dropbox icon on phone page. I deleted and reinstalled - same thing. I'm operating on the latest IOS for iPhone 4. Please fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="dropbox icon"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Installed update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="15">
    <text>You guys have already put MOVE SHARE DEL, why you guys do not allow us to COPY RENAME????????????????</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="COPY RENAME to folders and files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="MOVE SHARE DEL"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="16">
    <text>Simple to use. And the voice recognition is great!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Simple to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="voice recognition"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="17">
    <text>Works in conjunction wirh Google Drive, File Manager, Documents....</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="document organization on iphone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Works in conjunction wirh Google Drive, File Manag"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="18">
    <text>Flat out will not open on a new iPad Air</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="19">
    <text>rocking. sleek simple design.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="simple design"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="20">
    <text>I can't open the goddamn app</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="updating"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="21">
    <text>Only one issue, I cannot access my mp3, aiff, and WAV files. The issue started today, but I hope goes away. I use this for work and having access to my files is extremely important.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access my mp3, aiff, and WAV files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="22">
    <text>This is a fantastic desktop &amp; laptop tool but with no search or text file editing/creation on the iPhone, it is almost useless on that platform.

I've between 500-1000 simple text files in Dropbox. When will we be able to:
1. Mark favorites at the folder, 
2. Search file contents, 
3. Edit simple text files including adding new files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="adding new files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Edit simple text files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Mark favorites at the folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Search file contents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search on iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text file editing/creation on iPhone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="23">
    <text>All these updates, and I still can't rename things? That's really important...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="rename things"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="24">
    <text>Like the drop box service, but upgrading is too expensive.  Suggest graded levels of subscription</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Suggest graded levels of subscription"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrading"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="25">
    <text>Why did you drop support for earlier IOSs? Does Apple make you?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="support for earlier IOS"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Use on old iPads"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="26">
    <text>I don't really know how to created the file like a word document or something.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="created the file like a document "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="27">
    <text>Those would be useful!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 6 share sheets"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="28">
    <text>I think this app is awesome and this whole program altogether! But I mostly use Dropbox for music and it gets kind of annoying that the music doesn't go in a playlist like in the music app. Can you change that?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="music go in a playlist"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="29">
    <text>Thanks for nothing dropbox</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download ipod"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="30">
    <text>Finally we can share links to folders!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share links to folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="31">
    <text>I can't open since the last 2 updates. Pop-ups go crazy on the iPhone 5! I'm uninstalling</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pop-ups"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="32">
    <text>When I open it crashes my iPad</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="work on iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="33">
    <text>I liked the old color scheme. The new, all white hurts my eyes. Please revert back to original.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="old color scheme"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="34">
    <text>I just wish you could edit your word documents other than that it's great!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="edit your word documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="35">
    <text>Until the last update. Please fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reliable"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="36">
    <text>You should put the folders first... And then the files!
I would put a folder as favorite, thus putting all the files inside this as favorite too.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="put a folder as favorite"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="putting all the files inside this as favorite too."/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="37">
    <text>This use to be a great app on iOS 5. Having iOS 7 and the latest version of 

Dropbox and it's really bad. The new UI for viewing photos and video needs improvement to return to the way it was.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="UI"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view video"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="viewing photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="38">
    <text>My wife and I share a 100GB account, and it's amazing! So many things:

Automatic photo/video upload, iPhoto import, works with the Mailbox app, shared folders, photo aggregation on the website and mobile, the ability to store files only on the cloud (saves space on my Mac from old files)...

...and the obvious things like having everything backed up in real-time, and accessibility of my files from anywhere.

I could do without it anymore! Remember when we just had computers and hoped they didn't break and lose all our files?

One suggestion: if I have automatic photo upload on and download a photo to my phone's camera roll (say, for #TBT), don't automatically re-upload it to Camera Imports! It's already in Dropbox, silly. And yes, obviously if I use Instagram or some other photo sharing software to doctor it, I know it's a different photo and will therefore upload.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" shared folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability to store files only on the cloud"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="accessibility of files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="automatic download a photo to my phone's camera ro"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="automatic photo upload "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Automatic photo/video upload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="automatically re-upload it to Camera Imports"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="backed up in real-time"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhoto import"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photo aggregation on the website and mobile"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="39">
    <text>Since the update, it won't backup to Dropbox.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="backup to Dropbox"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="40">
    <text>Very slow uploading, and poor background uploading :( does it really need 3h to upload several megabyte video over 10 Mbit internet ?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="background uploading"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pload several megabyte video"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="slow uploading"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="41">
    <text>Im on a crappy hotel wifi that goes in and out. Been trying to download a 1gb file for over 2 days now. But for some reason dropbox has not allowed favorited downloads the ability to resume  and instead restarts the download from the beginning every time it fails. It's almost 2014. We have the technology to RESUME A DOWNLOAD what's the problem here?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download file"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Downloads of favorites"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="RESUME A DOWNLOAD"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="42">
    <text>It does a poor job at retaining the starred items in memory. So I wait a long time for an MP3 to buffer, I &quot;star&quot; it so I won't have to wait next time. But then next time it often has to buffer all over again!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="star"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="starred items feature"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="starred items in memory"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="43">
    <text>What happened?  I used  to rely on Dropbox to transfer files from my iPad to my computer. The camera upload still works but that's about it. They need to fix this App!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Send to Dropbox option"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="transfer files "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="44">
    <text>Dropbox is extremely  useful. Easy to access on any device or on their website. I've never had any issues with it and have been a user for years.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access on any device or website"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="45">
    <text>Great companion to the desktop version. Nice for viewing, but not so great for making updates.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="making updates"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="viewing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="46">
    <text>Thank's for app,but can you add offline mod?for exmple i want save one video in my iphone,and after that play it with VLC</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="add offline mod"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save one video in my iphone,and after that play it"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="47">
    <text>As soon as i updated to version 2.1. I can't open Dropbox. I can't delete it--but it is not on my phone. And I can't redownload it....help!

Updated: I see the suggestion is to delete and reinstall--HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO DELETE WHAT ISN'T ON THE PHONE, despite the fact that the App Store says to open the app, but will NOT open when you press the button?

FURTHER UPDATE--version 2.1.1 brought back dropbox to my phone. Upgraded to 3 stars. Once I play with it, I will assess whether it deserves more stars...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="delete and reinstall"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="dropbox to my phone."/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open Dropbox"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="updated to version 2.1."/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="48">
    <text>I now see that you must have IO7 or better for the app.
I didn't wish to upgrade to IO7 on my ipad2 and can't on my orginal ipad.
I feel you guys tossed us out in the cold.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade to IO7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="49">
    <text>Since new update 2.1 on Feb 15th, I get a splash screen followed by a crash.
Otherwise, 5*</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="splash screen"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="50">
    <text>An excellent App.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Ease of Use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="51">
    <text>I never know when it's gonna even work. I click on the icon, my enter password shows up and either it's stuck on that and I can't even enter a password, or I enter it and nothing happens. This was a great app. Now it stinks! Big time!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="enter a password"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="icon"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="52">
    <text>keeps crashing every time I try to make an account</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="make an account"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="53">
    <text>Seriously...why did select all functionality no longer available on everything?! (For most apple app) If i need to upload 500 images...i have to check those 500 images one-by-one!?!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Select all"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload images"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="54">
    <text>When I launch the app, all I have is a black screen with a gray bar underneath. This update rendered the app useless. I am using an iPhone 5 with iOS 6.1.4.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="black screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="gray bar"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="55">
    <text>I rely on Dropbox for syncing daily annotated PDFs from my iPad to my home computer.
After today's update sync stopped working.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing PDF"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="56">
    <text>Not working with iOS7.0.3</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="working with iOS7.0.3"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="57">
    <text>This app used to work flawlessly. After the most r event update however I can't even open it. I get the logo screen and then the app crashes completely. The update has rendered it useless!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="logo screen"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="58">
    <text>I can't open it on my ipad 3. Help! Crash! Crash! Crash!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="59">
    <text>Dropbox, you messed up my presentation this weekend when you wouldn't open when I needed you the most.  But I forgive you, because 1.You are Free. 2.You are so convenient. 3.You've changed the way I work. 4.My pictures just come to you like magic. 5.You open my PDFs, Docs etc. with ease.  

Baby, you're not perfect, but you get better and better as time goes on.  

Love, XOXOXO</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open my PDFs, Docs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pictures just come to you "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="60">
    <text>&quot;Awesome&quot; update with new can't-view-PDFs feature!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="view PDFs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="61">
    <text>I updated the dropbox app on my iPad and can't view any of my PDF files. Viewing wasn't a problem before the update. Help?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Viewing PDF on iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="62">
    <text>Can't open files, files won't update.  They show they haven't been modified in months when I modified it five minutes ago and all my other devices and computers not on iOS7 show the update.  If these problems get fixed I'll change my rating until then it will remain a 1 star.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="files update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="modify file"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="63">
    <text>Cant think of any specific complaints, but there is always room for a more robust interface</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="a more robust interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="64">
    <text>Dropbox could be better with faster uploading and downloading speeds also you should add the options to sync multiple photos from your phone to your camera roll instead of just one at a time!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="downloading speeds"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync multiple photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="65">
    <text>This app has been go so far for me. On my iPod touch 4 generation I has done so much in so little of time. Little than 30 seconds it had my account created and pictures uploading on there! Although I am looking in to this, I trust this will keep mine and your apple devices' apps, music, photos/ videos and so on safe with all your personal files. :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="account created"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pictures uploadin"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="66">
    <text>Please fix the syncing issues with the iPad app. Currently have to re-login to get files to update. Allow users to force a sync! Trying to automate it would be good if it worked, but it doesn't.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="automate"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="files to update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="force a sync"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="re-login"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="67">
    <text>No crashes so far, not affecting my phone or ipad functionality. But I have noticed that you can't share folders, only a single file, which is pretty ridiculous because then I could just email that single file to someone, but when you have a whole bunch of pictures that you want to send, you can't send the whole folder of pictures.  I had to upload all the pictures to a named folder, then I had to use the Internet browser to login to Dropbox and then send the link to the folder from there.

That so far is my only complaint, but its a big issue for me.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" upload all the pictures to a named folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="my phone or ipad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share single file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="68">
    <text>Dropbox is a great service. However, when I use the camera upload option in iOS 7, it only uploads the original photo and not the edited one. Otherwise, I'd rate dropbox as 5 stars.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload option"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="edited photos upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="69">
    <text>Sometime in the last month Dropbox stopped syncing. The most recent files on my phone are all 1 month old yet there are many more current files that I have loaded in Dropbox desktop folder for syncing. Help!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="loaded files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="70">
    <text>I didn't have to uninstall just shut down app and reload and connect to wifi</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Upload videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="71">
    <text>Needs a cloud sync feature. And subcategories.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cloud sync feature"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="subcategories"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="72">
    <text>app used to work wonderful except recent update.. unable to open most of our PDF files .. DROPBOX help!!! need fix ASAP!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open pdf files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="73">
    <text>When you have them upload they save as a photo not a gif so they don't work would like this fixed</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="save as a photo"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload gif"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="work with gifs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="74">
    <text>Normally 5-star app but now it will not open</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="75">
    <text>This latest update did nothing to stop crashes. Completely unusable.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="unusable"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="76">
    <text>It's super easy to copy pictures to clipboard or even save them to your phone, but why can't I download my videos?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="copy pictures to clipboard"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="download my videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="77">
    <text>Only downfall of this app</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="move to folder"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="78">
    <text>We should be able to do text documents! :(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="text documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="79">
    <text>Please bring back the old viewer, it was phenomenal. I like the page preview feature of the new version, but the general PDF viewing experience is worse. Specifically, it is very disorienting how the viewer returns to the topic of the page if you tap out of full screen view. I also miss the 'page xx of xx' feature when scrolling.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="old viewer"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="page preview feature"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="page xx of xx"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="80">
    <text>I have used the Dropbox app for a long time with no serious issues. Sure there are glitches once in awhile, but usually runs very smoothly. I have it uploading my photos, which it does consistently well and syncing docs I need. No problems here, not sure what the bad reviews are about.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing docs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading my photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="81">
    <text>New update doesn't detail what's changed. Now the app doesn't work. Just a black screen with a gray bar at the bottom. Please fix soon.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" gray bar"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="black screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="82">
    <text>That moment I figured out I could transfer photos from my iPhone to laptop faster via dropbox than plugging my phone into the USB port.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="File sharing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="transfer photos from my iPhone to laptop"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="83">
    <text>If we could create docs inside the app that would be great</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="create docs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="84">
    <text>Beautiful app, but NEEDS the ability share folders. For people on the go, we need to be able to email links out to people, sending tons of individual links to people is not feasible.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="able to email links out to people"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sending individual links to people"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="85">
    <text>Downloaded it to find that it doesn't even open. The AppStore says it's downloaded but nothing shows up in my app selection screen.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="86">
    <text>What is up with updates?  Multiple attempts with no progress,  just same slow nothing.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="slow"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="87">
    <text>You can't share folders? How many engineers have you hired? Ugh.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="88">
    <text>It's a really good cloud app, but what makes it stand out is the new .pdf viewer! Now I can read huge files on the iPad. You can't do that on Google Drive's app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new .pdf viewer!"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="read huge files on the iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="89">
    <text>My iPad works fine when I open Dropbox... But every time I open it on my iPhone 4 is either crashes or it continuously pulls up a messiah making it hard to close. It needs to fixed... Fast. Even after the current update just a day ago it is still crashing on IPhone!! This needs to be fixed.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="90">
    <text>I cannot open this app anymore. It crashes immediately! I loved it until the last update and used it a lot. I even purchased the Pro version. Now my work abilities are severely compromised!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Pro version"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="91">
    <text>The new design fits in well with iOS7, but it would be better if there was an option to rename files and folders. It's also impossible to send files as email attachments instead of sharing their links through the default Mail app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="rename files and folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="send files as email attachments"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="92">
    <text>The app greatly enhances the capability of the iPad by making it truly portable.  You are able to access your materials on all of your devices &amp; share with others either for the purpose of collaboration or simply dispersing information.  Both are very useful in the world of education!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" share with others either for the purpose of colla"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access your materials on all of your devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="93">
    <text>Flawless operation - ZERO problems. Easy to use - almost effortless. New auto-upload of photos and videos is a great &amp; useful addition. Customer support is second to none (when I did have a question, support answered it before two hours had passed).</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Easy to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload of photos and videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="94">
    <text>Older versions of this app used to allow me to preview word, excel and pdf documents. While the preview pane is still there the app just tells me the file name and size and does NOT display the content... Completely useless.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="display file content"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="file name"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="file size"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="preview pane"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="preview word, excel and pdf documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="95">
    <text>Please include the option to view thumbnail larger while viewing in the photo folder.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="view thumbnail larger"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="viewing in the photo folder"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="96">
    <text>Will not open since update. Some people use your free 2 GB plan, others pay for a lot of storage. Please help all of us out.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="storage"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="97">
    <text>Cannot download latest update, it was working fine for a year and then the updates started. I felt I needed to give this two stars because its been four days and they haven't fixed it yet. I use this app for work and now I can't.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download latest update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="98">
    <text>This update keeps shutting my entire phone down. Have taken drop box off my apps just so that it won't freeze up my os.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="99">
    <text>On the newest version I can find no way to see th entire file name. It shortens it with ... On the old version I could click the file and then minimize the left bar and see the file name, but on this version I don't see any way to do that. The point of this is files right? Seeing the full names of those files is sort of important.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="left bar"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="see th entire file name"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Seeing the full names"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="100">
    <text>COME ON DROPBOX!!!! This is getting ridiculous! I've uninstalled and reinstalled and it's still stuck!
Your customer service said this update would fix it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="customer service"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="UPLOAD VIDEOS"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="101">
    <text>This is a must have App as you can set it to sync all your pictures and once you take one they are saved in the cloud and also accessible by any other device you have Dropbox installed on and are signed into! One amazing MUST HAVE product and App xx</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="accessible by any other device you have Dropbox "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saved in the cloud "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync all your pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="102">
    <text>I get a pop up about push notifications and if I push ok it pops back up again making it completely inoperable. I tried changing all the push notification options and it doesn't fix it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pop up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="push notification"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="103">
    <text>I have been using Dropbox for years now and I have never been more happy when it comes to sharing files with myself (between all my devices) and with friends. Out of all the things I have tried, Dropbox has been the fastest program to upload any file and can be accessed immediately anywhere even through their website.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file can be accessed"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload any file "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="104">
    <text>I can't share folders!  That was the only reason I made a Dropbox in the first place.  Ugh.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="105">
    <text>Useless. Don't waste your time</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="106">
    <text>I love the idea of Dropbox but my cloud does the same thing... My videos take a really long time to upload I think it froze :( If the app didn't take up space on my iPad then I would be impressed ;)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="videos upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="107">
    <text>In a previous version, if the user was looking at pictures and suspended the app it would leave it right where they were upon restarting the app. Now the app completely refreshes at start up, which gets annoying sometimes. Also its more cumbersome to swipe through images since it's only responsive on the top half of the screen instead of the whole screen.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="looking at pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="refreshes at start up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="responsive on top half of the screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="swipe through images"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="108">
    <text>best cloud service ever.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cloud service"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="109">
    <text>Use to be good until I cannot open any office documents.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open any office documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="110">
    <text>This is crashing every time I attempt to open something saved.  Please help!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open something saved"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="111">
    <text>It's very convenient to use, however not being able to switch between accounts without un-linking the phone would be great. Also an improvement in the media player would also help.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="able to switch between accounts "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="convenient to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="media player"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="112">
    <text>I did not give permission to upload pics. The settings say its off yet it continues to upload. STOP!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="loading pics"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload pics"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="113">
    <text>I liked very much the upgrade to pdfs (divisions and search). However, they aren't displaying anymore. Fix it and it will be perfect.
Best wishes</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="displaying (divisions and search)"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade to pdfs (divisions and search)"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="114">
    <text>comic book reader would be nice... is store all of my cbr and cbz files on dropbox so i can read them anywhere</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="store all of my cbr and cbz files on dropbox"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="115">
    <text>Since the iOS 7 update the app is useless.  I have been using the app for sharing files while I travel but it know longer works. 
Is there going to be a fix or do I just start deleting it off all my devices?  On the iPad it just crashes.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="116">
    <text>Since the new update Dropbox freezes and blanks when viewing files, never did it before with the old os.
Really annoying to what was a good product.
Hope the powers that are responsible read this and provide a much needed fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="viewing files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="117">
    <text>Love this app.

Can you please integrate a spam filter feature so I can select and identify senders from which I no longer wish to receive emails.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="select and identify senders to receive emails"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="spam filter feature"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="118">
    <text>fix it -_- wont let meh open it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open current version "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="119">
    <text>While Word doc files open fine in Dropbox on my PC and on my iPad (I haven't upgraded my iPad Dropbox app in a while and haven't upgraded my iPad to iOS 7), these files no longer open on my iPhone after upgrading to iOS 7 and updating my iPhone dropbox app. Since the files I most often open on my phone app are doc files, this greatly handicaps the usefulness of Dropbox. Very sad!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Word doc files won't open iphone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="120">
    <text>Why is Dropbox using my location, even after I have just turned the phone on and haven't even opened the app?? 

Had to disable this is privacy settings to just to resolve the battery drain. 

Seriously, the developers have gotten some weird bugs going on with this latest update and need to resolve them pronto. 

Very disappointing. :(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="battery drain"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Location services"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="privacy settings"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="121">
    <text>My videos aren't loading into my Dropbox. Once the load all the way up, and should go in and move on to the the next instead it jus starts over. Can you please help? Otherwise it's great. Thanks for fixing the uploading vids bak into phone problem.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Videos loading"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="122">
    <text>Love the service but annotations on PDFs have disappeared from Dropbox since iOS 7 update. Need these back please.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" iOS 7 update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="annotations on PDFs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="123">
    <text>I have no idea how to get drop box files to sync with the iPhone or iPad</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="drop box files to sync iphone ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="124">
    <text>I just love using Dropbox. But iOS 5 is required to use it. How can I use it in iOS 4.1?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 5 is required to use it."/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="125">
    <text>Great app I love the new design but with the new update when you try to share a link to a specific file that has a space in the file name I have to manually replace the spaces with %20 so it will hyperlink correctly. This used to not be a problem. Please fix this ??. Other than that one problem this is a great app also I like the fact that if you download a picture from the app onto the iPhone it doesn't auto upload the picture so you have 2 copies of the same photo in the auto upload folder. Thank you for that fix. Keep up the great work.??</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="auto upload folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share a link to a specific file that has a space i"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="126">
    <text>I love Dropbox on my Mac and I use it all the time to share files with my photography clients. However I find it very annoying I cannot email the link to my clients in the iPhone app! Makes it hard for on-the-go sharing! What's the point of the app if I cannot share my folders?!
Please change!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="127">
    <text>Why did you remove open in option for music files?
I used to be able to do this with my sound files Why??</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open in option for music files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="128">
    <text>I use several apps for PDF viewing and one feature that keeps me on the prowl for the holy grail of PDF viewers, is an app that supports PDF markup. Being a musician and heavy e-reader, I rely heavily on PDF markup. 

Dropbox, give us some simple PDF markup abilities, e.g., highlight, pen, erase, opacity, and you will put several PDF viewer apps to bed. Couple these features with the ability to share a folder of PDFs with other Dropbox users and you've converted me, and countless others, to PDF viewing through Dropbox.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability to share a folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF viewing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="supports PDF markup"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="129">
    <text>I love our Dropbox functionality and speed. BUT the iPad app is broken. I am not finding a way to read the longer, truncated file names in the left column. I can only hide it, not adjust it.  This is no biggie for people with short names but our company has some longer descriptives in the names. Please fix so we can resize the column boundaries, as with many other apps.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="adjust names"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="hide names"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Read File Names"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="read the longer, truncated file names"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="resize the column boundaries"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="speed"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="130">
    <text>Ever since the update to the new PDF viewer (March 2013?) the Dropbox app shows me out-of-date copies of PDFs in my Dropbox that have been updated.  The modification times shown in the app reflect the existence of the new versions, but only the old version is displayed.  This ruins the app as a substitute for printing hard copies of drafts for editing and proof reading, which I had gotten to really like.  Dropbox support has been unhelpful.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="copies of PDF files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF viewer"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="support"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="131">
    <text>please fix it. it's the most often used function for me</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="read cached PDF"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="132">
    <text>The video I'm trying to upload is taking very long</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="133">
    <text>I can no longer link my account to my atomic web browser, don't know if it's cause of the iOS 7 update, if so then please update the app to work with it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="link my account to my atomic web browser"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="134">
    <text>Does everything you would hope it would do well. 

I wish I could email documents from Dropbox as attachments not as links.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="email documents from Dropbox as attachments"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="135">
    <text>Music player no longer works. Just about the only worthwhile feature for a mobile Dropbox.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Music player"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="play music"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="136">
    <text>Can't install on IOS 6 devices.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="install on IOS 6 devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="137">
    <text>Very useful. I don't have iOS 7 so I don't really have any compatibility issues. Shame I can't view animated gif files though.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="view animated gif files "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="138">
    <text>This used to be my favorite app, but now that I can no longer open Excel files it's useless to me.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open Excel files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="139">
    <text>I used to be able to view .xls files on my iPad AND iPhone.  I can still view them on my iPhone but they no longer open on the iPad. 

Sometimes the files will open for a few seconds and then a gray screen comes up. Most of the time I just get the gray screen.  The gray screen has the file name, &quot;Office Open XML Spreadsheet&quot;' and the file size.

My spreadsheets are simple (no macros) and small in size.  I've tried creating new spreadsheets and have the same issue.  Web research shows others have same issue but no fixes have worked for me. 

I'm on the latest IOS 7.0.4 and the most recent version of Dropbox 3.0.1.

Chat with Apple Support says it is a DropBox issue.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="gray screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view .xls files ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="140">
    <text>How to add voice memo from the iPhone?!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="voice memo"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="141">
    <text>Dropbox is a great program and tool, but with the last update which included a new PDF reader, I cannot open a PDF in full screen view, only thumbnail.  Please update, or if this is user problem, please inform.  I now have to use another program to vie my PDF files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF in full screen view"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF in only thumbnail view"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF reader"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="142">
    <text>Seriously needs a way to sort so folders are on top like normal.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sort folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="143">
    <text>One feature they should add is being able to import multiple photos to camera roll, then it be better.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="import multiple photos to camera roll"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="import photos to camera roll"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="144">
    <text>I love Dropbox and this app don't get me wrong but I have one thing in particular that will help make this app much more easier and nicer to use. For those who have a lot of photos (let's say *cough: 8,000). Have it so instead of uploading all photos, have it so you can choose which ones to upload as a option in settings. If you do so I'll give the app the 5 stars it deserves :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload as a option"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading all photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="145">
    <text>My favorite old feature was uploading a bunch of photos and videos from the day overnight or while using another app. That feature is gone now, I don't know if an update thing or new iOS thing. It's very inconvenient to constantly have to make sure the app stays open to upload.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload in background"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading a bunch of photos and videos from the da"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="146">
    <text>This update would be a step up if you could actually see PDF's with it....</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDF viewer"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="see PDF"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="147">
    <text>The main issue I have with this app is that there isn't a &quot;keep me logged in&quot; feature. Please add and I will reward you greatly (with 5 stars) ; )</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="keep me logged in"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="148">
    <text>Awsome but cant do the powerpoint stuff i want to, not the apps fault though</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="do the powerpoint stuff "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="149">
    <text>Yay!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sorting by date"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="150">
    <text>It would be nice to change the name of the files. When importing things and putting it inside a folder the order is not how I want it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="change the name of the files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="importing things and putting it inside a folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="order things inside a folder"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="151">
    <text>Can we get push notifications for other things being shared, besides just folders. My bf is a photographer, he often sticks photos in our shared folder - would like a notification when things arrive. (I do have them turned on but never get them)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="get push notifications for other shared things"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="152">
    <text>Convenient! No more lugging the laptop or losing a thumb drive. My files are accessible anytime, anyone, from any of my devices or another's. With three full time students in the house the affordable upgrade holds docs, data, music and more! Lots of room available. More convenient and more affordable than an external drive.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="affordable upgrade"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="files are accessible"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="153">
    <text>Seriously? I keep trying to get to one of my files, but the app keeps crashing for some reason. Please fix this.

Other than that, you're doing an average job!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="trying to get to one of my file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="154">
    <text>The new PDF reader is AWESOME!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new PDF reader"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="155">
    <text>The app would be great with two &quot;features&quot;.  One the ability to read long filenames.  The app truncated all my files so I can't tell which is which in our companies file naming procedures.  Really is a complete PITA.  Next there needs to be a clear cache option.  I download a 700 mb file and open it in a app I really don't need to have it in two places on my iPad.  Add these missing features for more stars.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="clear cache option"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="download a file and open it "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="read long filenames"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="156">
    <text>This app is great but the only thing I don't like is that that it freezes a lot and doesn't load all of my pictures</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="load all of my pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="157">
    <text>Need to be able to set limited as to how  much space it uses on my phone. It's using over 500MB. My phone is out of space.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="set limited to how  much space it uses on my phone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="158">
    <text>I have used Dropbox for a while but the 2 features which I live the most are Open in Dropbox and save on your mobile device. Great vision and work.

The only piece missing in this is, when we go to the folder where we want to save the file it does not show a preview of the content if the folder. This will be a good to have.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" show a preview of the content if the folder."/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Open in Dropbox"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save on your mobile"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="159">
    <text>I generally love Dropbox, but since I upgraded to iOS 7 I can no longer view html files properly (I am referring to files saved on my Dropbox as .html). I used to view them displayed nicely as web pages, but now I just see the source code instead! Can you please fix that??

Also, can you please add the option to copy and move files? It would be a very useful feature!! Thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="copy and move files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgraded to iOS 7 "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view html files as web pages"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="160">
    <text>This is not a review of the Dropbox service (which is great) but of this app, which can use a lot of improvements. The single most frustrating thing about it is that it displays only a dozen or so characters in a file name. Since I have thousands of files, some with long and descriptive names, it is impossible to find what I'm looking for unless I download the files to the iPad one by one. There is no way to resize the file list to make more of the files visible. Why not?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="File names illegible"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="resize the file list"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="161">
    <text>Every time I upload pictures it starts to say &quot; conntect to iTunes &quot; and it keeps poppin up after I click ok .. Fix this ??</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="conntect to iTunes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="162">
    <text>I really love how Dropbox update design.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Dropbox update design"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="163">
    <text>It allows me to share individual photos but not entire folders!  What good is that?? I can easily text someone a single photo ... WTH ?  I want to be able to send a link to people of an entire folder with many pics in it from my mobile.  Seems useless now. 

On the other hand I do like that I can view and share excel documents. That's pretty cool. Although it does take quite a while to load it seems.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="load"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="send a link to people of an entire folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share excel documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share individual photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view excel documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="164">
    <text>I tried to launch it and it always crashes and exits. Even restarting the iPad could not address the issue. iOS is 5.1.1. Hope Dropbox team improves the QA process and perform more exhaustive testing before releasing a new version.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="launch"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="QA process"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="165">
    <text>This app not only looks great, but also provides excellent functionality.  Flash Drives are a thing of the past!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="looks great"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="166">
    <text>The new update released last week is terrible. I can not open many of my files on my Ipad. I have to open the files in other programs. Drop Box needs to fix this issue.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open many of my files on my Ipad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open the files in other programs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="167">
    <text>Does anyone else have their Dropbox app, not the site, increasing in memory even without any favorite files???. Have to erase app once every 2 weeks!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="memory"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="168">
    <text>Cannot open any saved files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open any saved files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="169">
    <text>I love this app, BUT it is not working with iOS7!!!!!

Please help Dropbox.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" iOS7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="170">
    <text>While there are many ways to remotely store files, Dropbox is the best one due to it's vast number of ways to access your files. I have it on my iPhone and laptop and use three shared folders with classmates and family. Finally, if you have a large file to send someone, you can just put it into your Dropbox and easily send that person a link to view and download your file! Even if they don't have an account! Incredible!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access your files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="remotely store files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share large files with someone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="171">
    <text>Music takes 15 seconds to load after you have selected a song ( doesn't matter if I'm on Verizon LTE or Wifi) also, it doesn't play the next song automatically instead you have to open the app, go back and pick the next song in the folder. You can't even hit the &quot;next&quot; button to skip tracks.  Please fix these in the next update!

Running iOS7. Same issues on iOS 6</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Music load"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="next button "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="play song automatically"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="172">
    <text>It won't close, and there is nothing to get me back to a home page. Too bad it is supposed to be used along with some apps I would like to use but since it doesn't work I can't use the others either.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="back to a home page"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="close"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="173">
    <text>I like the fact that I can download drop box on any device and share pics. What I don't like is the time it takes to download pics and that in order to download I have to always be connected to the Internet, this keeps the pics from downloading some times when I am away from wifi. 2.6.13 i'm still trying to figure out app support. pictures are not downloading and i am going to remove this app from my IPAD its worthless</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download drop box"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pic download"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="picture download"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share pics"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="time it takes to download pics"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="174">
    <text>This app never installed correctly, I don't see the icon.
Nevertheless, it always show up in the App Store under Updates.
It always says Installing...
I can't update it, can't delete it, can't use it.
Only App I've ever seen that does that.

ZERO stars!

What a Joke!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="delete"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="icon"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="install"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="175">
    <text>When I put things into my dropbox folder on my desktop, I can find files by date modified, by name, etc.  The app has an incomprehensible and un-modifyable sorting function.  It's almost impossible to find files within the app.  Once you find them on your phone, I believe you can &quot;favorite&quot; them.  But the challenge is to find them.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="dropbox folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="favorite"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="find files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sorting function"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="176">
    <text>Argh. Crashes all the time. This service, and this app, would be great if the app didn't crash when reading PDFs.

Great when it works.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reading PDF"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="service"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="177">
    <text>Some things I'd really like to see are the albums I created on Dropbox.com. I have recently decided to move my pics to DropBox and would like to have them available at all times on my phone, in my albums.

Also, an ability to highlight/edit PDF's would be rad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability to highlight/edit PDF's"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="see are the albums I created on Dropbox.com on my "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="178">
    <text>I use Dropbox for everything. Having this available easily on my phone made checking updates on projects from work to sharing items much easier when I'm not at a computer. Also makes it easy to get photos from phone to computer since I never seem to move them. 

Shameless plus here - works great combined with Ifttt to move post record things on calendar emails contacts via spreadsheet or special folders.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="checking updates on projects"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="combined with Ifttt to move post record things on "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="get photos from phone to computer"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing items"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="179">
    <text>Why is it that the navigation bar is suddenly two different colors now that I've downloaded iOS 7? Looks almost like some sort of glitch.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Navigation bar"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="180">
    <text>Dropbox, we're supposed to upload our photos and video, but where will it all go? With the amount of photos and video we take, 100 or 200GB won't last more than a few years, let alone be a permanent solution. Please offer a different storage system for photos and video for power users. 

And please, add the ability to tag photos and video. There is no way to navigate Camera Uploads with any amount of speed and efficiency. We need a way to display our photos once we have stored them; right now it is a giant useless folder. An Evernote system of tags and saved searches would enable us to keep all photos/video in one place and still sort them when needed. 

Great service overall, but you come up short in photo/video storage. Take a cue from Flickr: charge a fee for unlimited media storage. I'd still pay for a separate 100GB document storage, which is what I have now.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" tag photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="display our photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="navigate Camera Uploads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saved searches"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sort pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sort video"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="storage system for photos and video"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tag video"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload our photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload video"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="181">
    <text>awful app...I uploaded HUNDREDS of photos but app could not upload them all..lost hundreds of precious memories of concerts, times with friends, etc. I was SOLELY relying on this app; I had NO back up for these photos and deleted them when it said they were done. now they are gone. I can NOT access them.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploaded HUNDREDS of photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="182">
    <text>Can no longer add files directly from phone. Completely loses point for me now. Won't use it until I see an update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="add files directly from phone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="183">
    <text>I'm using this to exchange tracks for my bands new EP, so I can review what we have down so far. I like the app, and the program a whole lot, but my WAV files only load and play when I have a wifi connection. I personally don't have wifi and the house I live in chooses to keep it that way. Hopefully this is just a bug that they can fix up because if it wasn't for the files crashing, I'd give it a full 5 stars. Hopefully this review will make that difference. ;p</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="WAV files only load and play "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="wifi connection"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="184">
    <text>Not sure how I lived without it. Best way I know to keep all my important files in one place so I can access them from anywhere on any device!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="can access files from anywhere on any device"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="keep all my important files in one place"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="185">
    <text>One flaw is the fact that its almost impossible to load mp3s or WAV files over data. It will play for a second or two then say its unable to load this file. Fix please!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="load mp3s or WAV files over data"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="186">
    <text>Dropbox no longer accepts files from my iPad since latest IOS update. Before this issue the app actually worked and was an easy five star.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="accepts files ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="187">
    <text>I love dropbox, but lately I have had trouble with the app. 
I can log in through safari fine, but when I use the app I keep getting a pop up which won't go away that says &quot;connect to itunes to use push notifications&quot; the weird thing is, I have all notifications for Dropbox turned off!
I can reinstall the app and then it works for a while, until I switch to a different app or go to the home screen, then I have the same problem. 
Hopefully there will be an update soon to fix this. :(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="getting a pop up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="go to the home screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notifications for Dropbox"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="188">
    <text>All it needs is multiple accounts!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="multiple accounts"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="189">
    <text>At around 5pm every day all of my latest (today's) files just disappear. They are still there though. I can search for them and find them. Then tomorrow, they are magically back!

On my desktop there is no issue. Just on iOS. 

Is this a known bug?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="find file "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="IOS"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search for file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="190">
    <text>You can't download any videos into your phone. Like come on I don't know why yahoo would do this to me making a deal with Dropbox.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download any videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="191">
    <text>Best cloud sharing service, but app for iPhone stop working as it will not open on iPhone 5, keep asking to connect iTune for alert &amp; notification... I have to use Dropbox service through 3rd Party Software like iExplorer to use it.  Will give 5 stars if this fix. By the way, my iOs version is 6.1.3</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cloud sharing service"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="connect iTune for alert &amp; notification"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="192">
    <text>People seem to only right reviews when made so I'm sure there are more people then this that love drop box. It's better then any other cloud option. Beats skydive, google docs and the expensive i cloud stuff. I love it and highly recommend for all devises and all file types. Back up data to another hard drive just to be 100% safe  but it works across all my devises.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cloud option for all devises and all file types"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="193">
    <text>I keep getting the message &quot;connect to ITunes to get push notifications.&quot; i cannot get rid of this message. Can't connect to iTunes or use Dropbox. Even have trouble getting out of Dropbox. Please fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Push notifications"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="194">
    <text>Still no gallery in Camera Upload mode !</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Camera Upload mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Gallery"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="195">
    <text>It was cool, until the last update where now I can't upload from my iPhone.. It starts uploading , the progress bar shows it going, then when radionics he'd, the progress bar just starts again and again going over and over</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="progress bar"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload from my iPhone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="196">
    <text>At first when I got this it was cool, but then when I changed my mined about having my camera uploads in my Dropbox it says that I don't have any photos in my library when I clearly have photos in my library....please fix!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="having my camera uploads in my Dropbox"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos in my library"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="197">
    <text>Hate the new iOS 7 look. Ugly, not user friendly, takes more effort to navigate.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="navigate"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="redesign"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="user friendly"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="UX"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="198">
    <text>I'm very disappointed that I can't open most excel files anymore! Repeated tries works occasionally but it should work every time!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open most excel files "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="199">
    <text>Every time I try to open one of my audio files the app just shuts down. I have upgraded to the new version. This app needs some fixes. I love using it otherwise, and love that ican access any file in dropbox on all my computers and easily share with others</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access any file"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open audio file"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="200">
    <text>Very useful app.  Thank you! If only I could see my filled in fields of the Word forms on it it would be awesome. It is a pain and a hustle not to be able to.  
Also I miss the old app logo, new one is  just so-so.
Otherwise it is great.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="see my filled in fields of the Word forms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="201">
    <text>Dropbox is amazing and perfect for storage and safety I love it! I just wish there was an option to change the name of pictures and documents through your phone.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" change the name of pictures and documents through"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="storage and safety"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="202">
    <text>It's great but should put Apple TV support to view photos better in the Apple TV.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="view photos "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="203">
    <text>No longer able to hide the file list, so you don't have full screen displayed like previous version. Please bring back.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file list"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="full screen"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="204">
    <text>I typically don't leave support as my feedback, but I can't seem to get a response. This app crashes each and every time I try to open it on my iPad 3rd gen. I use it often on my Iph5 but for some reason here it doesn't work. Please update ASAP so it works again.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="205">
    <text>I love it. So easy even a cave man can  use it. I loaded 314 documents in about five seconds. Now I can read and work on documents no matter where I am. The cloud's got nothing on this. Dropbox rocks.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" loaded documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="read and work on documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="206">
    <text>I care more about the functionality than the looks, so this review will say nothing about the updated look.  There are some major bugs/problems with the update!!!!  I am no longer given the option to &quot;open in&quot;.  This means, I can look at my Numbers spreadsheets, but I can't &quot;open in&quot; Numbers, so I can't work with those spreadsheets or enter any info on them.  Major issue!!!  It makes dropbox completely useless for me.     Please fix this !!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="functionality"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="looks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open in"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="207">
    <text>The new interface is a very big disappointment. Is there any way to get Version 2.3.2 back?
Way too much white space which is hard on the eyes. Also, still not able to rename files -- unbelievable!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="rename files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="white space"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="208">
    <text>The camera upload on this app is really glitchy and it's not letting me put any of my pictures on it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Camera upload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="put pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="209">
    <text>I use it to sync files between a desktop, laptop, iPad, iPod and iPhone. 

And for collaborating with others by using shared files and folders. 

I once had a problem on my iPad with an endless loop asking me to connect to iTunes. But that turned out to be an Apple problem which for me could only be solved by a complete erase and restore. 

Since the problem only occurred in DropBox, I initially assumed it was their problem. It was not.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="asking me to connect to iTunes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="210">
    <text>Still no ability to change file names - a very basic function. Hard to believe after this amount of time. Error messages when simply trying to move files. No response from dropbox</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="change file names"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="move files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="211">
    <text>It works on a few platforms but I love to keep changing my phones every couple of weeks and this app is not universal on all platforms. They need to release this app on more platforms like newer Windows Phone 8 like Lumia 1020 and then it will be true 5 stars. Till then, sky drive wins.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="more platforms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="212">
    <text>I use ipad mini. But I cant even access to my account because the app crashes in iphone size every time i open it. Need a hotfix, URGENT</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access to the account"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="213">
    <text>This would easily be a 5 star app. Best idea ever.  But it loses 2 stars just because I have to download one photo at a time. This is a huge inconvenience.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download one photo at a time"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="214">
    <text>It was working fine with no problems and now I can't even get the app to open!! Not happy about this at all!! Please fix!!! I even deleted the app and re downloaded n it still doesn't open this is very frustrating because this a great app when it actually works!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="215">
    <text>Its good. Turn off camera upload in settings or click cancel instead of enable during initial setup. Great app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload enable during initial setup"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="216">
    <text>Easily the most important app on all my devices is Dropbox. If you are a multi-platform user this is a must have. I only wish there was streaming support for media files (btw @dropbox - I'd pay extra for that). I am a Pro subscriber and can say its worth every penny for any executive on the go. I also love the dead simple camera upload for my iPad &amp; iPhones but would like to see that integrated outside of a sync.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload integrated outside of a sync."/>
      <aspectTerm label1="simple camera upload for my iPad &amp; iPhones"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="streaming support for media files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="support multi-platform user"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="217">
    <text>But why does location need to be enabled?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="location"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="218">
    <text>Should be able to mark entire folders as favorites so they will save to mobile device, not just each file individually.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="able to mark entire folders as favorites"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save to mobile device"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="219">
    <text>The automatic upload feature is ridiculous as there is no intuitive or easy way to stop it.  Also, the delete function is confusing and should have some sort of dialog box informing you that you are about to delete a photo on your ipad, not just in dropbox interface, and ask you to confirm that you want to do this.  My wife tried to stop the automatic upload and hit the delete prompt thinking that may stop it.  We now lost photos of our newborn which we cannot recover.  Thank you Dropbox - you just lost us photos we will never get back!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="automatic upload feature"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="delete function"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="dropbox interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="220">
    <text>Need to have an option to select multiple documents (and/or folders) and forward them at the same time instead of opening each one individually!!!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="forward multiple documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="opening documents individually"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="opening folders individually"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="select multiple documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="select multiple folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="221">
    <text>It's way too slow!! Loved this app.. Then I updated and its like a flipping sloth. Ugh!! FIX PLEASE!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="too slow"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="222">
    <text>The inverted colors of the icon induce retinal after images, and in-app, the whiteout is hard on the eyes. The experience on an iPad Air is one of huge expanses of white or badly contrasting off-white/light blue and stencil-thin pale icons battling the brightness of it all. The spartan look works fine on an iPhone, where there is proportionately less white assaulting the eye; with the iPad, however, I keep trying to reduce the brightness of the display, but that only further impacts contrast and legibility. 
Also why is it not possible to change names of files or folders??</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="change names folder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="change names of files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="inverted colors icon"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="whiteout"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="223">
    <text>The app in iPhone needs important issue &quot;share via email&quot;</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share via email"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="224">
    <text>It takes forever to upload photos, 2-3 weeks after I started the photos finally became viewable. I had no problems installing the last update. I love the recent upgrades. Syncs perfectly. Sharing is easy. Overall, a great app but needs a few tweaks.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sharing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Syncs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="225">
    <text>Since they did a new update almost all my JPEG take too much time to open or even don't open. I need to save the file to see the photo on my iPhone. 

How can I have the old version?????</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open JPEG"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save the file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="226">
    <text>Keep up the good work but camera upload has stopped working for me. No matter what I change no photos or videos will load.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos or videos will load"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="227">
    <text>Always loved Dropbox. Reliable and handy. Newest version has menu problems. Can't upload. Please fix! Thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Newest version menu"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="228">
    <text>Can't use due to pop-up about push notifications. Open iTunes and connect for notifications. HATE IT!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pop-up about push notifications"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="229">
    <text>This app used to be flawless! But after recent updates I have issues uploading things. I'll select a bunch of my photos to back up and the app will crash out and only upload a few and not all. Major bummer!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos to back up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading things"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="230">
    <text>I want the old version , this don't have the option to share my files via Facebook message ,please bring back the previous version or fix that !!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="old version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share my files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="231">
    <text>I love the fact that its so easy to use and now my cel is working better than ever! If you're still thinking to get this app don't think anymore download it now, Thanks Dropbox!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy to use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="232">
    <text>With the latest update I can't open word documents. Yes they are saved in the right format. Its just not working please fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="documents saved"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open word documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="233">
    <text>I am having problems uploading stuff to survival craft a game. To upload it says i need to put it in dropbox but it wont let me share it with survival craft again what do i do</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share it with survival craft"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading to survival craft a game"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="234">
    <text>The app drains your battery cause it uses your gps all the time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="drains your battery"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="gps"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="235">
    <text>This is a great app, however, to move apps into a folder I have to go online. I have to overwrite in the app to update a file and then I have to use the web version to move updates files into a folder.
I may be doing something wrong so I'm giving 4 stars for now. If you or anyone can explain that would be great. I've looked over the directions and can't find how to do it all within the app. I want to use the app for its full purpose.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="to move updates files into a folder."/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="236">
    <text>Aside from the &quot;glowing&quot; feedback and all the media hoopla, this app really blows.  
Since the new upgrade, copying or especially MOVING files inside the app is impossible.  It times-out the app and crashes constantly.  
For me, it way more easier to store files in the storage area of my online email provider - GMX.  GMAIL has online file storage and a service very similar.  GO WITH THESE and KEEP YOUR HAIR.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="copying files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="MOVING files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="store files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="237">
    <text>With the latest update you can no longer download ePub files to iBooks. The option to download is grayed out. Looks like I will be moving over to google docs or something else.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download ePub files to iBooks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="option to download is grayed out"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="238">
    <text>How do you move files within existing folders? The world may never know. Great, fast app... But moving files is a necessity.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="move files within existing folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="239">
    <text>The latest revision (as of 10 January 2013) loops endlessly when trying to upload a 411KB file.  Had to email it to move to another device.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="240">
    <text>O sugest an puch notification in iphone  whem a file is added.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file is added"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="puch notification in iphone "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="241">
    <text>Well, it opened when I first installed it. Now it won't open at all. Fix it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="242">
    <text>Its amazing. The only thing to make it better is to have the ability or export videos to your camara roll</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="have the ability or export videos to your camara r"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="243">
    <text>I love it, making a password lock before accessing the actual app would be perfect, for the fact that most of the files are very important, but still an amazing app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" password lock before accessing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="244">
    <text>This works wonderful on my iPhone 4S. I have many things on my PC and it automatically syncs to my iPhone. I am never without important documents that I need to review or look up that are password encoded. Super easy and a huge time saver. Love it!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="documents password encoded"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="review or look up documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="245">
    <text>The fact that you can search within folders is extremely useful, and makes accessing files on the go far more convenient. I also think the latest style refresh is a big positive in the right direction. I use dropbox on all of my devices. I would like to see sorting within the app improved (e.g. by date), but it's good otherwise.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" accessing files on the go"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest style refresh"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search within folders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="246">
    <text>The service is great, but the app fails. Pressing &quot;Upload Here&quot; freezes the app and crashes it on the next open.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="service"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Upload Here"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="247">
    <text>Since the new update, I cannot now view my XLS files on iPad.  Please fix this ASAP. Thanks.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view my XLS files on iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="248">
    <text>Even Google Drive can refresh folders. 

Some simple suggestions to increase usability:

1. Currently, you have to leave the folder and come back in if you wish to refresh that folder. Let me refresh my folder with a refresh button so that I can view changes to files in a more streamlined manner. If I am constantly compiling a document on my computer and using my iPad to check that it looks okay or if I am constantly editing a photo and want a high quality, true color representation, then...#REFRESH!
2. Refresh Button
3. Button that Refreshes the Current Folder's contents.
4. The air smells a bit. Why don't we REFRESH it?
5. It is stupidly simple to add a refresh button
6. Mentos: The Refresh Button Maker
7. There's space on the top left of the app header to add a refresh button.  Nothing is there at the moment. It's lonely...
8. Give me an R, Give me an E, Give me an F, Give me an R, Give me an E, Give me an S, Give me an H! What does that spell? Easily implementable refresh button with high utility even to people who don't know they need it yet! Yaaay!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="folder refresh"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view changes to files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="249">
    <text>Hey Dropbox team! Please add the ability to rename files, as well as the ability for gifs to play. I know you can do it!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability for gifs to play"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability to rename files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="250">
    <text>Dropbox does not install on the iPhone. It has not since it first came out. Each update leaves me with the hope that it will now start working, but no joy. 

It seems like a nice app. Wish I could use it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="install"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="251">
    <text>I gotta say, overall I like this app, although the logic behind the 15 min cap on streaming alludes me. I thought they may have imposed it to reduce bandwidth, but with the limit it actually increases bandwidth. The reason is because I start downloading the whole file, then start streaming it. Once the 15 min is up, I then switch to the downloaded file. To me, this uses more data. Why can't I just stream the whole thing? Overall, though, I like everything else about this app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="15 min cap on streaming"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="downloading file"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="file streaming"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="252">
    <text>Very annoying to not be able to see an entire file name.  Put some flexibility in the width of the display for those of us who use files with longer names.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file name display"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="flexibility in the width of the display "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="253">
    <text>I'm having issues with moving my files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="moving my files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="254">
    <text>Do not update! Icon is ugly</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Icon"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="255">
    <text>Spent many hours successfully transporting pictures. Site then froze when I needed to export. All pictures are locked and frozen. I keep trying to re- access the app site with no success</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="export picture"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Frozen Screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="transporting pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="256">
    <text>Why is this for iOS 7 only now? Not very fair for people wanting to run this on older devices or don't wish to downgrade to cruddy iOS 7.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Compatibility"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Design"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="257">
    <text>I should know better than to update to newer versions. Unusable.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="New iOS7 style"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="258">
    <text>The current version doesn't show all files in dropbox. Please fix!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="show all files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="259">
    <text>In theory it's great but once a PDF is selected it can be impossible to close it.  I have resorted to tapping relentlessly on my screen so some magic will show the tools.  The PDF just sits there.  Way more effective to go through a browser.  Really?  Irritating!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="close pdf"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="260">
    <text>Having problem getting to update upgrade!?  It is stuck and I don't know what to do now???  Need response ASAP!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update upgrade"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="261">
    <text>Disappointed to see there's still no text editor after all this time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="text editor"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="262">
    <text>Latest version seems to have stopped playing my videos.  Sad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Videos stopped playing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="263">
    <text>Add features to let me edit office files, share folders instead of just files, and view more types of files (catch up to g drive) and you'll get five stars, and I can stop using google drive.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="edit office files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="264">
    <text>I'm trying to download minecraft pe maps but all it's says is cant view file</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="download"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="265">
    <text>I love the new design for iOS 7</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new design for iOS 7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="266">
    <text>You can't play wave files at ease ..... What about cluster play.... 1 star till updated...

Why not have an export feature... Export to phone

You can upload but cant download files to your phone

Update from today

........................

THE EXPORT FEATURE IS GREAT...
All I have to do is put a video from my computer on the Dropbox then download it to my phone ..... Perfect five stars from me....... Thank you very much people of dropbox

.........................

The export feature only works on certain videos.... There's a video I want to download like all the ones I successfully exported.... But it says for these bigger files...&quot; No app to use this video&quot; something close to that... Fix this by upgrading the size someone can download.... 3 stars until upgrade</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cluster play"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="download files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="EXPORT FEATURE"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="export feature  videos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="export feature phone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="play wave files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="267">
    <text>Would be nice to have a grid view of photos other than just the auto upload of camera roll. Also would be nice to rename files.

My last review still not fixed: This app doesn't support mobi file uploads. Would be nice to save my mobi files.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" grid view of photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1=" rename files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="auto upload of camera rol"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save my mobi files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="268">
    <text>It's useful and helpful. All my files and especially my photos are being synced FAST to my laptop. This is the app that I've been looking for. It's very convenient also to use.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="convenient to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos and files synced "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="269">
    <text>White white white!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="White"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="270">
    <text>How do I get MCPE maps and mods? Without iexplorer or any other fake website to get your money</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="MCPE maps and mods"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="271">
    <text>This app is perfect, next to ibook it is the most used app on my iPad(s).  The only thing I can think of to make it better would be the ability to display long file names, I use it as a repository for ebooks any many times have to download 3 or 4 books to find the correct one in a series.  Thanks for this great app!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ability to display long file names"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="272">
    <text>I've been using Dropbox for quite sometime now, I have earned a fair amount of space, and I love being able to access all my files from my iPhone, iPad, MacBook, and the Internet via anyone else's computer.

But these last 2 updates have disabled the save to camera roll feature, which I use all the time and have come across several times since the new update. Please please please add this feature back! I know I can just do a screen shot but i prefer the clean cut copy you receive, without boarders from saving images to the camera roll!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access all my files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save to camera roll"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="space"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="273">
    <text>The update is fantastic! Everything is easier to find, looks prettier, and is easy to access. Great job guys!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="find"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="looks prettier"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="274">
    <text>I love this app but I do wish I could highlight words in PDFs and create bookmarks. Would this be possible at some piont?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="create bookmarks in PDFs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="highlight words in PDFs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="275">
    <text>This app is the best utility ! Very needed ! I would suggest you to have at least 5 GB of space .</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="have at least 5 GB of space"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="276">
    <text>I would've lost hundreds of photos if it wasn't for this app! Thank you!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Saved photos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="277">
    <text>I wish you could save Notes from the home page to Dropbox, that would make organizing my devotionals and other thoughts easier, as well as increase the camera upload speed instead of just one at a time. Thank you</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" increase camera upload speed"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save Notes from the home page to Dropbox"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="278">
    <text>This is the single most useful app I have ever used. Bar none. 

Dear designers: Would love to see the functionality of the media player upgraded to allow play of songs one after another (without individually selecting them). Our band shares a folder and we put our songs in there, but you can't listen to them consecutively. They have to be selected one at a time. 

Thanks for listening.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="media player "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="play of songs one after another"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="279">
    <text>Love the support for password protected MS Office docs, thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="support for password protected MS Office docs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="280">
    <text>Sometimes I listened to mp3 files I have on Dropbox. Lately the sound stops after the screen locks. This didn't use to happen. Also the play, re, fw controls you get after double clicking the home button no longer work with this app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="listened to mp3 files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sound stops after the screen locks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="the play, re, fw controls"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="281">
    <text>I love the new clean UI. Very unintrusive and elegant</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="282">
    <text>Was nice , won't open since update</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="open"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="283">
    <text>Been using dropbox on the desktop for the past 3 years. Loved the service there. Got an iPhone 4s recently and installed the Dropbox app on it. Now I have all of Dropbox's great features on the go! It's great to be able to search for a resume or an crucial school document saved on my laptop from my phone. Dropbox saved me a countless amount of times!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="able to search for a document saved on my laptop f"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="284">
    <text>This app keeps crashing as its loading my document. Im a student in college using my iPad and this is not very good considering this is my book file.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="loading my document"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="285">
    <text>HOW CAN I CAN MAXIMIZE THE SLIDE SHOW ?! IT DISAPPEARED .. BAD UPDATE</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="MAXIMIZE THE SLIDE SHOW"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="286">
    <text>Take pointers from Yahoo on how to make iOS 7 Style apps that stand out from the 90% that are beautifully designed in blinding white. Ugly app and icon.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="icon"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="287">
    <text>So helpful</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Access to my files "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="288">
    <text>After the last update, it crashes every time I open the manual upload. Pls fix it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="manual upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="289">
    <text>The new UI is awesome</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="290">
    <text>Please add support for animated GIFs!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="animated GIF"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="GIF support"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="291">
    <text>Can't install the update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="install the update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="292">
    <text>I hoped the update would bring back the &quot;open in&quot; option but it didn't. Importing files into other apps is a major pain now. Why was this option removed? Please bring it back.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Importing files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Open In"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="293">
    <text>? Why can't I sign into separate Drop Box accounts?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sign into separate Drop Box accounts"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="294">
    <text>I tried reloading but it still asks to connect to iTunes and will not work on my Ipad</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="asking to connect to iTunes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="work on my Ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="295">
    <text>ALL 1,300 photos were deleted. I trusted Dropbox as a back up for my photos. I have no way of ever getting those photos back. The only kind of response I've gotten from them is a generic response saying they can't get back to me because there are so many inquires. Never will I ever use them again. DO NOT TRUST THIS APP!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="back up for my photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="photos were deleted"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="296">
    <text>Was I the only one to ever report this problem??

Ever since I downloaded the latest update the app on my iPad continues to show a pop up alert message. I click ok and it pops right back up!  I've turned off all alerts for the app and I have been in contact with Apple Support. We reset to complete default mode, reloaded the app and still the issue. It is so annoying. Is any else experiencing this?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pop up alert message"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="the latest update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="297">
    <text>I would like the ability to share a complete folder not just one file at a time. I'm not sure if I'm just not seeing this feature? It seems like a basic function at this point, since you can do basically everything else within the app platform. Other than that, I am very happy with the experience.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file at a time"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share a complete folder"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="298">
    <text>Version 3.0 auto updated today and now my photos won't upload. Luckily my SkyDrive added an upload feature.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Photos upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="299">
    <text>This app is really useful for having access to documents while I'm out.  The one big thing I think it lacks is a way to share folders while you're using the app.  I'd love to be able to share a folder via the app and I've needed to so this before while I was out, but unfortunately, this app as of 3/1/13 doesn't have that feature.  It would be really useful to have!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access to documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="300">
    <text>I've tried Google Drive, Box, Skydrive, but none of them could upload a 20 minute video I took. Dropbox was the only one that accepted my file.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upload"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="301">
    <text>I have camera upload on and when I opened it, it started reuploading over 200 photos even though they were already there. Not good.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera upload"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Reuploads"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="302">
    <text>Major sync failure! You put documents at work and go home and sync again only to find none of them are there. Other times when they are actually synced you can't open them! I'm deleting it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="303">
    <text>New interface is great</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="New interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="304">
    <text>Love the new UI. It looks awesome !</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="305">
    <text>I can pretty much have access to all my photos and videos on the go without it taking space on my phone. Love ittt &lt;3</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access to all my photos and videos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="taking space on my phone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="306">
    <text>Nice major update, overall the app works great. But, one thing that's still missing is bulk downloads. You can a) select multiple files and b) download files from Dropbox to your phone, but you cannot do both at once. Seems pretty basic a feature to overlook.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="bulk downloads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="download files from Dropbox to your phone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="select and download files at once"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="select multiple files "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="307">
    <text>It's annoying as all get-out.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="logo's colors"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="308">
    <text>Still no long file name support on iPad, why?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="long file name support on iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="309">
    <text>The layout is very clean but it fails to load editing settings or feedback components. It has potential, but is still buggy.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="layout"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="load editing settings"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="load feedback components"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="310">
    <text>I just got the app. I tried to log in on my iPad but it would not let me. I tried my email and my username. I tried different variations of my password. Nothing worked. So I reset my password, being careful to check spelling, etc. then I logged onto the desktop site (still on iPad) and it worked. I went back to the app but it would not work. I've used this app multiple times in the past, so I'm frustrated that it's just now not working.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="log in ipad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="311">
    <text>somethings wrong with the last update.
i only can view pdfs once. 
after opening for the first time, cannot view them anymore!

the latest update fixed the issue of crashes and also can view the pdfs without problem. thanks a lot for your work!  however there is still a problem which is that when you try using the &quot;open in&quot; option in other iPad applications, and ask to open in Dropbox, the filed just opened shows up in the iPad Dropbox application, but the Dropbox server is not updated... meaning that file is not found in the Dropbox folders if you access the folders in a different device/computer, etc...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access the folders in a different device/computer,"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Dropbox server updated"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view pdfs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="312">
    <text>Non-starred files occupied more than 600 MB and I have no way to reduce it...it eats out all my ipad space</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="un starred files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="313">
    <text>It's a great app especially for iphone users since they can't add storage to their phones but any time u send a email to a friend inviting them to get it they give you more memory</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="email to a friend inviting them to get it give you"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iphone users storage"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="314">
    <text>Is Dropbox design for iOS 7, but is still the same more or less. Air Drop is the only new thing in this update (for iPhone) I think. 
4 out of 5 because still can't rename files...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new design iOS 7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="rename files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="315">
    <text>Dropbox works great. I can access files anywhere. Highly recommend.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" access files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="316">
    <text>Simple, just what I needed to make transferring certain photos from phone to computer and vice versa simple. Thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Transferring certain photos from phone to computer"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="317">
    <text>This is the greatest app invented to man. Dropbox is already a great idea. On the phone, even better.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Dropbox On the phone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="318">
    <text>I like this app i just reallyy wish it could support zip files as well if that was changed i would so give it a 5star rating :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="support zip files"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="319">
    <text>Updated to the latest version and...now all my Microsoft word documents won't open in the app, so I can't view anything.  Also lost the ability to export into pages for editing.  Hoping this is just a glitch that gets fixed fast, but really problematic for me since I use this almost exclusively for work.  Please fix cause I love Dropbox!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="export into pages "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Microsoft word document open"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="320">
    <text>Nice design refresh. Looks great. 

I love this app. Dropbox totally saved me at work. I had to email a bunch of large files and the work email system wouldn't take it. 

Dropbox worked flawlessly. Not only did they get links to download the files, but they could also view content right in their web browser. PDFs, Word docs, and videos all were viewable in the browser for them. It made presentations a breeze! 

I now use Dropbox for personal use too. Love it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="download files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="view PDFs, Word docs, and videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="321">
    <text>Caught in a loop forever after trying to load a video and also forever looping in the initial how to adobe file. Very sad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="load a video"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="322">
    <text>Background gps keeps active and is draining my battery</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Background gps"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="323">
    <text>Won't let me view my excel spread sheets from my iPhone. Please fix it other than that love the app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="view my excel spread sheets"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="1">
    <text>I love the fact that Evernote allows me to sync my notes between each of my devices and computers. I use it everyday to keep everything right in front of me. I wish the interface a bit different. Maybe the option of colored notes?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface a bit different"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync my notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="colored notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tool"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="2">
    <text>Perhaps the most-used app on my mobile devices.  Well organized, easy to use.  Great product.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy to use"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="mobile devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="3">
    <text>Evernote is a great way to store pictures &amp; notes online, to your computer to your cellphone, I always found myself using it to store notes I would lose.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="store notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="store pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="4">
    <text>The app was awesome until the latest update.  I lost a weeks worth of class notes, can't even open the program without it crashing unless I'm connected to wifi, and a complete notebook just disappeared after the password reset.  Everything was great before the update, now nothing works.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="password reset"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="crashing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="nothing works"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="5">
    <text>The apps is great, the only thing I run into is that it won't always save my voice records. I used to think I was just doing it wrong, but I've tried hitting the &quot;stop&quot; button before I hit save and most of the time the recording will just disappear. Some times it will save and work correctly, but most of the time it won't.  Anyway, it doesn't keep me from using the app, but I just definitely don't trust it with important voice recordings yet!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="voice records"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="6">
    <text>Much better place to store all those notes than your Gmail account.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Much better place to store all those notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="7">
    <text>It's great and all but I have all my work and school work on google drive and I wish that it could sync with google drive cuz I love taken notes in this!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync with google drive"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="8">
    <text>The sync process between my phone and computer can be cumbersome.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="9">
    <text>Worked great with Dolphin, until the last update. Now it is not.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="last update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Stopped working with dolphin"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="10">
    <text>PC, laptops , droid, tablet, two iPhones and one set of reference documents on all of them for myself and the wife. What the heck was I doing sending copies and updates in msgs and hand written notes, I'm so embarrassed I did not find this 3 years ago?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="PC, laptops , droid, tablet, two iPhones"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="11">
    <text>I love to write. Inspiration for words can come at the drop of a hat which why I absolutely love this app. I have the ability to record thoughts at my finger tips by having the app on my phone then can go back and work on the same pieces on my computer later at home. The instant syncing between computer and phone is fantastic!
It's perfect for writing, recipes, or absolutely anything really. Very satisfied!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="instant syncing between computer and phone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="12">
    <text>Impressed by its versatility in terms of the type of note one can take. It's great to have the ability to input URL, photos, audio, and text. And great that it has desktop integration for a computer.

The drawback that I've encountered is though it offers labels it doesn't offer folders. Editing and the dashboard in the app could use an easier interface. Still good app though.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="dashboard interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="input audio"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="input photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="input text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="input URL"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="desktop integration"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="labels"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="type of note"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="13">
    <text>Performs better than other services that I have tried.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="all platforms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="14">
    <text>Love the new interface. Quick access to my most used notes and tags makes the app so much more quick. The most beautiful app on my phone.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="most used notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="most used tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="15">
    <text>Editing ability and consistency on iPhone has improved with recent updates. Still some work to do to allow additional font sizes and such for items created on iPhone. Should get a 4.5 for that reason but it would be unfair to rate this a 4 b/c of those minor limitations. Robust editing on Mac, online allow workarounds.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="font sizes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="consistency"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="minor limitations"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="online allow workarounds"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="recent updates"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="16">
    <text>Wait 1 month then read reviews before risking an update.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="17">
    <text>The app present good features, but there is a lot of bugs and missing some hotkeys to make the writing easier.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="hotkeys"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="18">
    <text>It's been great and works on my iPad, iPhone and Mac.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="works on iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="wokrs on iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="works on Mac"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="19">
    <text>Ok what don't I use Evernote for? Nothing! I use for everything! Storing contacts, business cards, my son's artwork, recipes, food journals, workout logs, useful documents, receipts, magazine clippings..

In this new version I can finally edit notebooks on my phone. I'm 99% mobile. I love that you can access your notes from anywhere. 
My husband has the Evernote pen an takes notes during his meetings. He looses his notebooks but the pen syncs with Evernote and all his handwritten notes are there. Super cool!
I also use Evernote Food App (which syncs with Evernote). Awesome!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access your notes from anywhere"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="edit notebooks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Evernote pen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Food App"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pen syncs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="use for everything"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Evernote pen"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="20">
    <text>Overall good maneuverability. Love the connectivity. I hate how hard iris to put different notes into different notebooks, though!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="connectivity"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="put different notes into different notebooks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="maneuverability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="21">
    <text>I'd tried Evernote in the past and never stuck with it, but after using it for everything for the last six months, I don't know what is do without it. 

The app is fantastic. Works really smoothly and makes creating and retrieving notes easy.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="creating notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="retrieving notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="22">
    <text>iPhone, Mac, kindle... It's always there and once I get the hang of the updates, even better. 
Thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="kindle"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Mac"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="23">
    <text>I don't know who approved this, but they should be fired! Talk about a step backwards and a leadership failure... The user interface is hard to read and is now just a cluttered mess... I had to stop using it... It took me twice as long to find my notes... I catch myself just jotting notes on a sticky pad and leaving them on my desk... This is ridiculous...
Shame, I've been using evernote for years and here I am looking at alternatives...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="find my notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="UPDATE"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="user interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="jotting notes on a sticky pad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="24">
    <text>I absolutely love being able to save notes and organize them in notebooks. I use this app daily. Two of my most useful notebooks are: 1. Storing recipes 2. Medical info such as current meds. I also love that I can view it all on various devices. I do wish that when sharing the notes, they didn't look like garble when I use colors and formatting. Also, I haven't found an undo option on the app version so when I accidentally delete content, I have to do it over. The app still deserves 5 stars hands down though!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="save notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="undo option"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="various devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing the notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="organize them in notebooks"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="25">
    <text>This new layout is awesome. Use this app daily and love it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new layout"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="26">
    <text>I am so disappointed to see the turn that the ios app has taken. There's so much to dislike about this craptastic abomination that I'm not even going to try. 
I'm a long time premium user and am seriously considering other options.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="abomination"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="27">
    <text>I use it to keep track of recipes, make notes on hobbies, keep up with maintenance tasks</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="28">
    <text>I use my iPad to take notes for business meetings. It automatically synchs with my iPhone and laptop.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="synchs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="29">
    <text>Just for everyone to know if you install Evernote and your notes do not show up first you need to delete Evernote and reinstall and it will begin to sync again</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes do not show up"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="30">
    <text>Once I learned to use the notebook/multiple tag search I was very pleased with the new update.  I use Evernote for my GTD system and primarily work on iPad.  The new graphics are great.  Thanks for my most used app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="graphics"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notebook/multiple tag search"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="31">
    <text>Evernote for iOS 7 is beautiful built for apples latest toys. It's the best way to organize documents and images in one place.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="organize documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="organize images"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="32">
    <text>The new version of Evernote is okay. I would like it better if I was able to increase the text size
SUGGESTION-
Have an undo button. I just deleted an entire document when I meant to copy. This is bad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="increase the text size"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new version of Evernote"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="undo button"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="33">
    <text>I use evernote for most of my note taking, but now I have to pay 5 dollars a month just for a slightly longer note? Ridiculous!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="size limit"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="34">
    <text>This app has made my job and life so much easier! It is available on all platforms and syncs automatically. There are updates all of the time. I have been using this for about a year now and I have never had an issue with losing notes. I use this to write my notes for billing so that part is crucial. Thanks for making my life easier!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs automatically"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="35">
    <text>Seriously ready to stop paying for this monthly. It will now only work if I uninstall it then re-install it. It will only work once and then if I open it again it will be nothing but a black screen. Then I have to delete it and install it again for it to work only once. It was perfect before the last update. If it's not broken then don't fix it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="last update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open it"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="36">
    <text>The only reason I moved to iOS7 was to get the newest version of Evernote. Let me say, I have no idea what everyone is complaining about. Super easy to add notes still. No sync issues. Handy announcements from Evernote. The card view is still there, you just have to (gasp) look for a sec. 

If you are having issues, contact support before blasting the app. And take a deep breath folks. Life isn't that bad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy to add notes still"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Handy announcements"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="The card view "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="contact support"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="37">
    <text>Evernote is my daily Goto app for all of my actions and to dos. The file folder UI can be clunky but under the covers this app delivers.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="file folder UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="38">
    <text>That's it. Love it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="use it on four devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="39">
    <text>Not able to synchronise after a month of installing the program so unable to back up my info. 

Avoided updating the latest version becos during the last update, all the info which were not synchronized and backed up were swiped off!! All my precious info gone! I am also unable to email the existing info.

I am now searching for another better program.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="synchronise"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="unable to email "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="back up"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="40">
    <text>I probably am not using Evernote to its full capability, but I'm an avid note taker and list maker so this is one of my most-used aps. Would like to see a feature of putting Due Dates on some notes, so it becomes a task list too. Sometimes editing notes is slow, that's why I give 4 stars.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sometimes editing notes is slow"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="putting Due Dates on some notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="41">
    <text>New design is strange to navigate, tag lookup is slow, unintuitive is a pretty good word for some of the changes.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="tag lookup"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="42">
    <text>I find it very handy to be able to copy from penultimate straight to Evernote! I have yet to see another program that does this! If only Penultimate would support zooming in, it would be awesome!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="copy from penultimate straight to Evernote"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="zooming in"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="43">
    <text>This app will not down load or let me remove it. Why?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Can not be removed"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="44">
    <text>Had the app for so long and was a paid user as well.  The new update is just horrible.  All my notebooks are there but there aren't anymore notes in them. The design looks like a dog threw up on it also.  It's extremely annoying to navigate through everything now too.  You should go back to the original view you had before.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="navigate"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="45">
    <text>This is a wonderful app that enables users to write about whatever they need in a variety of ways on a variety of devices.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="on a variety of devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="write about whatever they need"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="46">
    <text>I find the interface to be awkward, but the biggest fault w this app is its poor syncing across devices. Even my supermarket app updates my shopping list instantly--if I add something on my ipad, it's there on my iPhone immediately. In Evernote, I have to manually refresh and if I make a change on one device then another without refreshing on the first device, I get a note that there was a &quot;conflicting&quot; edit. What is the point of a note app that isn't constantly saving and refreshing? And this isn't just the case over a few minutes' time; I've had notes not change over the course of weeks--I have to to go to the last device I made changes on, refresh, and then refresh again on the other device. Not good.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="47">
    <text>Hard to use; takes up big chunks of the screen trying to sell me crap.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="48">
    <text>this new update won't let me open the app anymore ???? please fix it! I use this app for everything and I really need it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Crashing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="49">
    <text>Great super helpful app. However, the positioning is glitchy. When I'm trying to type, the keyboard will often cover where I'm trying to type. So I can't see what I'm typing.. Thanks.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="positioning"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="keyboard will often cover where I'm trying to type"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="50">
    <text>I'm SO upset! I've been using this app for a year &amp; have patiently endured the slow process of improvement. It had really gotten quite good. Then this last bungled attempt has made the app virtually useless. Shame on Evernote's QC group (if they even have one?)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Last Update ios 7.0"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="QC"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="51">
    <text>Update: I really do not like the new tab-based interface. It's very slow and unwieldy on my iPhone 4. It's hard to tap and drag the headers. They're not very responsive, and the slow animation between tabs is just useless fluff that gets in the way of speedily making and finding notes. 

Also, using the same view in landscape mode is really ugly and wastes screen real estate. 

I still like many aspects of Evernote, but it is important that you keep the focus on usability and functionality, rather than cute interface magic. It is very frustrating to be watching slow animations when I want to make a quick note. 

Furthermore, too much key info is buried. Tags, location, etc. I have to go through too many menus and dialogs to change these and then go back back back to my notes. 

And now we also can't see our notes on the map filtered by tag. I can't look at just my cafes or restaurants or meetings on the map. That makes the map pretty useless (on top of apple maps being horrendous).

I appreciate the efforts to improve, but this interface was a step backwards actually. It constantly gets in my way and frustrates me. 

----------------------
Evernote, THANK YOU!

The latest update makes your app slick and quick. No more crashing, fast slick uploading, proper non-buggy text entry, and proper functioning of folders!!

In particular, the text entry is a BIG deal. I was very disappointed in the weird behavior previously with spaces and line breaks. I was getting worried about relying on Evernote for all my stuff..  

But you did it right this time. THANKS!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="location"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="animations"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="functioning of folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="key info"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new tab-based interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes on the map filtered by tag"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="quick"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="same view in landscape mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="slick"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text entry"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="uploading"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="52">
    <text>I am blown away by this application.  I don't just mean the iPhone or iPad versions, but rather the entire concept.  I've now ditched all of my task management systems and note systems in favor or this single system.  I can search pictures of business cards, agendas as well as meeting notes and I can do this from my iPad, iPhone, web or home computer app. I can tag items and move between folders which allow me to manage my daily tasks and set reminders if something has a due date.  

Also, I love the new interface.  Very easy to use and quick.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="move between folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tag items"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="53">
    <text>I've been using this for just over 6 weeks and have eliminated all paper notes. Even when I find myself at a meeting without a laptop or iPad, my paper notes easily get loaded in simply by snapping a photo. 

Additionally, classifying a note by notebook and adding tags makes it easy to organize among a couple different dimensions for easy retrieval at a later date.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="adding tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy retrieval"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="classifying"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="54">
    <text>From baby feeding and diaper changes to shopping lists and research papers - our family shares everything. 
Thanks Evernote!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="shares"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="55">
    <text>I'm loving the organization and ease Evernote brings to my life! It's new reminders feature has been amazing!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="56">
    <text>It's a lot of money for what a mounts to a great sorting system for notes if you're a flake like me. Looking back, I should just have kept those little slips of paper in my pocket.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="price $450"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="57">
    <text>A essential for any tablet user or ANY entrepreneur. It's capability and conveniences will make you wonder how you went without it (or how you used the Notes function so long)!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="58">
    <text>I am extremely excited about the possibilities for tracking my prospects and clients in a user friendly manner with evernotes.  The Tag and Search functions make it easy to recall prospects who are interested in specific models --- new and used.  I can order the searches to look at latest entries first which is very important in my business.  Many other applications work well, but I do have one observation that you should be aware of.  There seems to be a bug in the search function for notebooks, when you do a search in a specific notebook.  The all notebooks search works fine, as does the tag search breakdown.  All in all, this is a great program.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search function for notebooks"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Tag"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="look at latest entries first"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="59">
    <text>It's a great app for taking class notes on my tablet and still be able to access them via the internet.  Love it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access notes via the internet"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="taking class notes on tablet "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="60">
    <text>I lately found this app..simply amazing interface and many options</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="options"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Seamless integration"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="61">
    <text>The Evernote desktop version effectively ruined my windows 7 computer and brought to a halt my MS Office especially outlook.  Still trying to repair the effects of this program. Sadly haven't even got to really use the program.   If you use a Mac then maybe no issues, but it was a bad purchase for this windows computer user.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="bad purchase for this windows computer user"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="62">
    <text>Used to think it was acceptable at least, but after losing my notes a few days ago I cant give this app a good rating. Dont waste your time on it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="losing my notes "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="63">
    <text>That's basically all I have to say. The organization makes different notebooks inaccessible; I liked when I could slide tabs of folders and I'd love to be able to customize the tabs. 
For the longest time I couldn't find a single sync button anywhere. I wasn't sure if my notes were saving until I saw them in a list in the side bar. It shows an arrow on it but does let you sync from that arrow. That would be really convenient!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="customize the tabs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="slide tabs of folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync button"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="64">
    <text>Does almost everything except allowing me to make a quick diagram by hand.  But it does allow me to take a pic, and record voice, so that helps.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="quick diagram"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="record voice"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="take a pic"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="65">
    <text>I have a premium account and I use Evernote for business and personal items all day long and I am very frustrated about the new advertisement section I've been graced with despite paying not to have advertisements.  Also, there is no logic behind the new tag section. I really like the the tag section, but I want to organize what pops up there. I can't find a master list of reminders in the app or the desktop version. Maybe I haven't looked hard enough, but this seems to be a gaping oversight.  A calandra would be nifty as well.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="master list of reminders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="calender"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't find a master list of reminders in the deskt"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new tag section"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="premium new advertisement "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="66">
    <text>The new version is more difficult to use, not attractive, and the Evernote ads are really bad (I'm a premium member).</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new version"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="67">
    <text>Have been using Evernote forfiver a year now... very easy-to-use program, love the syncing with my desktop, phone, iPad, etc.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing with desktop"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing with iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing with phone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy-to-use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="68">
    <text>No more magazine clippings. One place for to do lists. Would love to see the ability to set alarms and send reminders. One of my favorite and most versatile apps.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="alarms"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="69">
    <text>Absolutely love this app. Found out about it from a fellow Southwestair flyer. Use it all the time for &quot;must saves&quot; from twitter &amp; the internet. Easy to use with folders &amp; tags. Can keep all of my daily notes &amp; thoughts close at hand.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tags"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="70">
    <text>I love that I can have post it notes without the post its. Love that I can take picture notes and get a memory jog just by looking at the &quot;post it&quot;. Good app I'll upgrade when I use up all the space :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="take picture notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="post it notes without the post its"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="71">
    <text>I really wanted a note system I could trust, but Evernote just lost all my notes on the upgrade.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="lost all my notes on the upgrade"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="72">
    <text>It seems Evernote did not understand the spirit of iOS 7. The design seems flat for the sake of flatness. Usability has been thrown out the door. It's very confusing to use the app. Simple actions are painfully slow.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="actions"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="73">
    <text>I frequently ask users of smart phones which application they love the most. Evernote is the most frequent response. I love it too. It really empowers me to write while on the go.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="write while on the go"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="74">
    <text>I love Evernote!  The convenience of saving web info, documents from airline itineraries to e-tickets to office documents to photos, etc. on my IPad or my computer is wonderful! The fact it works on pc platforms is a real bonus!  Put the info on one device and you have it on all your devices!  Thank you developers!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving web info"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving airline itineraries documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving e-tickets"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving office documents"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="works on pc platforms"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Put the info on one device and you have it on all "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="savig documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="75">
    <text>Great app for David Allen's 'Getting Things Done' organizational techniques. Syncs with iPhone, iPad and Mac immediately so you always have access to what you need wherever you are.

I use this app to keep track of everything from work tasks, household chores, shopping lists and ideas for the future without getting them mixed up.  Check out TheSecretWeapon.org for ideas on how to set up your Evernote to stay organized. 

Great app!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="keep track of everything"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="76">
    <text>I use thus app more than any of my other apps combined... from voice memos, notes, recipes... it can all be saved, filed and tagged for easy retrieval and viewing.  The fact that it is also compatible with so many other apps make it a daily resource and a valuable asset in my day to say life.  It will only keep getting better with each update and IMO is already a household software name like Office, etc.  Evernote is now even bridging the gap with social media options... BRAVO EVERNOTE!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy retrieval"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="viewing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="recipes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="voice memos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="77">
    <text>Love this product.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="product"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="78">
    <text>It's a app that you can do pretty much everything from making to do list to office papers. It's great for people that are on the go and can store almost anything and have it in the palm of their hand.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="store almost anything"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="79">
    <text>It's wonerful: I keep recipes, receipts, , knitting patterns, copies of postcards and greeting cards from friends, car maintenance records, appliance manuals, parts numbers for appliance parts., and many other things. I keep schedules for my favorite sports teams, information about attractions I would like to visit the next time I travel to various cities,. I keep business cards and journal articles that I use at work. Easy to search for information when I need it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Easy to search for information"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="80">
    <text>Still learning how to use the app.  Using it with GTD.  I used it some before the reminder system was added.  Now trying to convert to full time use.  We'll see.  Do wish it allowed all functions to exist in an Apple environment since I am cross-bred with my devices.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="allow all functions to exist in an Apple environme"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminder system"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="81">
    <text>Feels more fluid, controls are intuitive and exactly where I expect them to be. Design meshes perfectly with iOS 7

Great job on this update :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="controls"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="fluid"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="82">
    <text>How dirty! Who are you to say that I need to change my password! Especially since I was already creating a l-o-n-g note. Interrupted my work flow and then lost my note after changing my password!!!!!!!!!!!!!

...and you call this &quot;EVERnote&quot; ? Should be &quot;NEvER NOTE&quot;!
 I'd laugh but I am too busy cursing!

Waste of an entire morning... switching to another note taking app then deleting this app once I have time to transfer remaining notes to &quot;ELSEWHERE&quot; note app!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="change my password"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="83">
    <text>The more I use Evernote, the more ways I find to use it. Love the excellent and consistent multi-platform experience and sync.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="multi-platform"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="84">
    <text>Was never able to even start using this app. It kept insisting I log into some account or create an account. I have no desire to do either and I never could figure out how to bypass the startup login requirement and use it as a standalone note taking app.

Epic fail. Doesn't matter how good it is if I can't bypass the login requirement and start using it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="No standalone mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="startup login"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="85">
    <text>I did the update and they made me change my password. I logged in with my new password and ALL of my files are missing! And then I logged into my account through the website and no notes are there either... This is great since midterms are next week and all of my notes are gone.... :'(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="change my password"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="logged into account"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ALL of my files are missing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="website"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="86">
    <text>I find I must logon again each and every time I open the app on my iPad2 running iOS7. Curiously, this doesn't happen on my iPhone 4S. Grr...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="logon"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="87">
    <text>This is the best business productivity tool.  I wish I would have known about it sooner!!!!  Love, love it!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="productivity tool"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="88">
    <text>Good but notes are not available offline unless you favorite them which you cannot do on an ipad. Favorites can only be done on iPhone app. They seem to purposely make that fact buried or vague. It took some digging in the forums to find out. I guess it's a way to get you the purchase Premium.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="but notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="favorite"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ipad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="offline"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="89">
    <text>Very easy to use on any device or OS</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="90">
    <text>ITS ONE OF MY FAVORITE AND MOST USED APPS ON MY IPOD.  I USE IT TO WRITE JOURNAL ENTRIES, TAKE NOTES AT CHURCH, JOB MEETINGS, ETC.  ONE OF IF NOT THE BEST NOTETAKING APPS EVER HANDS DOWN.  (And believe me... I've tried a lot of them! )  :)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="TAKE NOTES"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="WRITE JOURNAL"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="91">
    <text>The most amazing app, for sure the most used on my iPad, however I liked some features of the older version, please bring back the option to make Paragraph headers and subsections. The typing could be faster but Still great app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Paragraph headers"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="typing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="subsections"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="92">
    <text>The app is missing a few things compared to the computer based version, but overall functionality is pretty good. The only reason I don't give the app 5 stars is because the new interface is absolutely ugly. Although this is just a personal opinion, I feel that the layout is slightly inconvenient and confusing. If this changes, I will give it 5 stars.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="layout"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="93">
    <text>This has made taking notes both fun and easy. The ability to access and take notes on my computer, phone or tablet is incredibly convenient. Being able to add voice memos, pictures and tags to notes is very helpful. Great app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="add voice memos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access and take notes on phone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access and take notes on tablet"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="94">
    <text>I love this! As a scatter-brained note taker, I always have to rewrite lists and reminders and plans because I am not in the same place as that lovely random pad of paper. No more! Thank you! I access all my entries on my iPad, iPhone, or computer. Updated in real time. Love the change in italics and boxes to check off. this rocks my socks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="boxes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="italics"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access all entries on computer"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access all entries on iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="access all entries on iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Updated in real time"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="95">
    <text>Great productivity app: syncs across all my devices without a problem.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs across all devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="96">
    <text>One day, after using this program for months, I find that all of my previously accessible notes can only be accessed online unless I pay $50 for blackmail, I mean premium. Thanks for completely screwing up my workday while I search for a note-taking app which won't pull the rug out from under me. The only reason my language is still G rated is the hope that others will see this review and save themselves the time and suffering.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="premium"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="97">
    <text>Very handy, access notes from anywhere.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="access notes from anywhere"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="98">
    <text>There is always room for improvement but this app has replaced no less than 3 other apps, and now with reminders it is my go-to application for pretty much anything task or project related.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="99">
    <text>I love this app. It's like having Word on my iPad. I can even access it on a pc and on my iPhone. The way it updates it self is great! I love this app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="self updates"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="100">
    <text>Still freezing and quitting in iOS7. Worthless.  I take a lot of notes at work and now have been forced to go back to the Apple note app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="101">
    <text>It's an amazing app and I love it's features except for one little problem. The GPS feature is a bit off. I'm at home and when I want to make a quick note it gives me the wrong address. It would be great if this could get fixed</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="GPS"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="102">
    <text>Started with app not getting all notes. Deleted and reinstalled app. Fixed that. Now when I select all notes, it opens to a specific note and freezes when I try to go back. So here I am to try reinstalling again. iPhone 5 ios7.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="select all notes, it opens to a specific note and "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="103">
    <text>Good app for noting but too expensive to use it for poor students ... 60mb is not enough...could you make it more plz ?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="60mb"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="noting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="too expensive"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="104">
    <text>My dear friends, how could you?  Requiring iOS 7?  Really?  Please update your app to support iOS 6 as well. Thank you!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="support iOS 6"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Requiring iOS 7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="105">
    <text>Good product</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="product"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="106">
    <text>It is what it says it is, which is refreshing. A place to collect all the pieces of information that can clutter your life. Sure, it takes some work on your part to sort it all out but you have to get it in one place first. That is what Evernote does best. It's on my iPhone, iPad and MacBook. I use it everyday.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="used on iPad"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="used on iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="used on MacBook"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="collect all the pieces of information"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="in one place first"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone, iPad and MacBook"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="107">
    <text>I love it! All of my reminders, notes and receipts in one place. Thank goodness!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminders, notes and receipts in one place"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="108">
    <text>Ever spent an hour trying to find a user name that would be accepted?  This app is it!  What a freaking waste of my time!   I would give it a zero if it would allow me!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="user name that would be accepted"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="109">
    <text>But not anymore.  iOS 7 seems to be incompatible.  Too bad, so sad: uninstall</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="incompatible"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="110">
    <text>Simple, easy to use note taking app. Sometimes not all notes are available when not on wireless network.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy note taking"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="not on wireless network"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Simple note taking"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="111">
    <text>This app is, in a word, blissful. Seriously, everything I want and need to do and all the ways I want to take notes--annotated and tagged images clippings, articles, news reports, etc--offered in a nicely bound package that helps keep organized. Its like sticky notes, moleskins, pages, zotero, and Instagram all in one.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="annotated and tagged images clippings"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="articles"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="news reports"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="take notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="organized"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="112">
    <text>but i don't understand why we can't add a website even though it's an option. also, it'll be cool to add videos!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="add a website"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="add videos"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="113">
    <text>This is really a great app an tool to manage multiple projects and scattered notes. I just wish that there was a calendar integration and sub folders within stacks. 

Also in Evernote hello there is no categorizing. 

But make no mistake... I swear by this program.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="calendar integration"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="categorizing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sub folders within stacks"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="114">
    <text>Frequently crashes and does not allow local storage of personal notes, which are automatically stored on painfully slow Evernote servers.  Personal notes and passwords have been compromised by hackers once already.  Hope you did not have anything sensitive in your notes!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="local storage of personal notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="slow Evernote servers"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="insecure"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="passwords"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Personal notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="115">
    <text>I am using this to reduce paper clutter in my house. So far, so good. Notes from the kids' school and organizations get photographed and organized in one notebook. Notes for parties in another. Ideas for the house are organized too, including pictures from home and garden magazines. Love it so far. I am a little worried, however, that I need access to the Internet for it. Not sure if this will work then.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Ideas"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="organized in one notebook"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="116">
    <text>I dislike the latest version. My notes randomly disappear. They are listed under the wrong name (usually by the one that is actually above it.) I LOVED the version prior to this one. This version is making me lose my confidence that my notes are actually being saved!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes listed under the wrong name"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="version prior to this one"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="117">
    <text>I love Evernote and I use it everywhere and on various devices (iOS and desktop). I used to love the simplicity of the web interface, but the new one seems too cumbersome and I've had some really weird issues where it has overwritten my notes. Overall, I would rate the environment 4.5.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="web interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="overwritten notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new web interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="118">
    <text>Give these guys some credit. They completely resigned the app for iOS 7. There will be bugs. I have had a few but I know that they have a good vision. 

Evernote for life!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="resigned"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="119">
    <text>The app used to work great, but now it keeps freezing and I can't get into my  notes. It is very frustrating. I have to delete the app and download it again. What a pain!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't get into my  notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="120">
    <text>Update has bad UI and doesn't support all the 3GS iPhones that are still on contracts. Delete and use apple notes instead.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone 3GS support"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="121">
    <text>Update, EN performance has improved considerably (from 2 to 3 stars) since my last review, however the app remains pretty buggy. It constantly reports failure to synch, it freezes momentarily between all actions, it crashes here and thee, and the search function sometimes fails to find key words. I am borderline thinking of going premium, but also keeping an eye for alternatives. Note, some of my problems may be related with some incompatibility of iPad2 with iOS7.

Previous review,
After several months of daily use, and building about 1K pretty intensive notes, I was in the process to put a serious long-term commitment to EN- but I've had to seriously rethink this after the problems with the last upgrade. The problems I've experienced are not as severe as what others are reporting. Mine have been mostly with the iPad 2 version, while the desktop version w MacBook Air has continued to work OK. 

On the iPad things have actually improved quite a bit over the past week, in terms of less freezes, when trying to do a search- so for me it is wait and see, to see if EN can get it together. The searches have also become less efficient and clunky in all iPad &amp; Mac desktop versions. I am still working on EN, but will also be on stand-by, and looking for possible alternatives.

I don't have many concerns w the new design, as others do-- but I do hope that EN programmers can stay focused on the real issues.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="synch"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="performance"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="desktop version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPad2"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="122">
    <text>Evernote is no longer usable to me because I have not jumped on the iOS7 bandwagon. I never adopt a new OS until the kinks have been wrung out. Now I have lost the use of Evernote?and I used to use it a lot. Bad call! 

Now I will be looking for something else to use, and will let my Premium subscription expire.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="minimum iOS"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="123">
    <text>Good notes app, nicely organized and clean to edit and read.  Highly recommend.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="edit"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="read"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="124">
    <text>It is overwriting my notes with outdated versions. The complaints about syncing issues with the iOS 7 update are spot on. Stay with the iOS6 version if possible!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing issues"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 Update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="125">
    <text>Downloaded app.  Wrote important document.  Tried to save it.  Lost it instead,  Glad I didn't buy the upgrade.  Was easy to use up until I was through with the document and ready to save it!? (pretty critical point in the process). Now I have to start over.  Pretty disappointed.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="save document"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="wrote document"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="126">
    <text>I would like to say that I do not like the fact that the password has to be reset.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="password has to be reset"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="127">
    <text>Both the application and the browser version on my iPad 2 are crashing, burning, and totally failing. Work cannot get done. Woops!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPad 2"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="128">
    <text>It is my most important work tool. Keep the updates coming.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="tool"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="129">
    <text>I really enjoy this app but during my use, I just wish I could format my notes a little more nicely - by that I mean more functions like the ones in InDesign, or apps similar to it. I also realized that when you start numbering your content, you kind of have to keep going and not have a paragraph in-between. If you stop numbering at, say, 5, when you start again, it's back to 1 again. Also, I think it would be really fun if you incorporate a doodling function in Evernote. What do you say?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="format notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="numbering"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="incorporate a doodling"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="doodling function"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="130">
    <text>I love pasting notes to ever note. I paste my passwords I paste copies of receipts and anything that I need to locate later and I can easily find it in one location the search option is very handy as well. I WISH THE INSTRUCTIONS WERE CLEARER</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pasting notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="INSTRUCTIONS"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="locate"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="131">
    <text>Great app for business purposes.  Eliminated all handwritten notes and sticky note reminders.  Great for tagging and clipping important websites and urls.  Would love to see option to color code notes for us visual organizers.  Great for checklists and idea sharing with others.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="color code notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="clipping urls"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="clipping websites"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tagging websites"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="132">
    <text>Awful. Like other users have reported, when you open the app it freezes and you have to double-click home to kill it off. Useless. If you can get it to run (there are tricks) then you have to deal with the ridiculous interface - like scrolling to the bottom to see a square list that has a couple of notebooks listed, not all. And then a few more taps to get to your notes. It's a lot of clicking to do something as simple as review your notes. There are so many other design metaphors available, it's crazy why they went this way. Anyhow, I miss Catch and some others. This app as is I would say is near a waste of time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="lot of clicking"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="miss Catch"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="133">
    <text>Upgraded to latest version (iOS 7) and lost all but three of my notes. I've tried the Sync Now several times and nothing. Fortunately all my notes are still on my laptop, but still? . 
And I don't need to be reminded to go Premium on every screen, thank you very much.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="134">
    <text>I loved the app, but ever since I installed iOS 7 and updated the app, it does not start. Please fix it</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="start"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="135">
    <text>Okay Evernote, I hope you are listening. You had a great idea. But &quot;note&quot; should not be in your name. Call it Eversomething. The text formatting makes it virtually impossible to create a note with any form of rich text, bullets, numbered lists, indentation, etc. Maybe the underlying code base or architecture makes it difficult to create rich text with proper formatting. I don't know, but until this is fixed it is not useful. And man I've really tried to like Evernote. The synching ability among so many platforms was great. But I have to go back to OneNote now. Who knows if you will read this. But I really wish you would understand this huge weakness in your product. And I have done a good amount of googling around to know that I'm not the only one around wanting better text capabilities. Please fix this. I really want / need a proper Evernote!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="rich text with proper formatting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="synching ability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="bullets"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="indentation"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="numbered lists"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text capabilities"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text formatting"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="136">
    <text>Evernote is an excellent service, and this is an awesome app!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="service"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="137">
    <text>I loved Evernotes...that is Until I download iOS7. With their new and improved look they also did away with everything you ever had saved.  They did however manage to maintain the notebook names...unfortunately all of the notes within those notebooks were erased.  I used this app for work and personal business...all files gone!  Be sure to only use this app for unimportant notes.  Very disappointed. :-(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="all of the notes within those notebooks were erase"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new and improved look"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="138">
    <text>After I downloaded this it just sat on my desktop for a million years. Then I got the bright idea of taking a screen snapshot of an Expedia itinerary. Wow! Suddenly I am off and running, saving and accessing info on everything from learning disabilities to salad dressings. I would like it better if there were multi- layer nesting available for the notebooks, but it is pretty cool. 
Btw, I use the skitch add-on for editing,reformatting, *bold* print, etc.  It's great.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="multi- layer nesting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="accessing info"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reformatting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="saving info"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="skitch add-on"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="139">
    <text>Third &quot;upgrade&quot; in two days. Two of them including this one stop me getting into the app. Lousy work by the Evernote team.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="140">
    <text>First time I tried to use it, it locked up. Tried again, same result (iPad 2). Featured in Time magazine for some reason. I deleted it and don't think I'll miss it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="locked up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPad 2"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="141">
    <text>I love this app so much. I love that it syncs with my computer. This app is such a great thing for beginning writers like myself. I recommend it completely.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="142">
    <text>Evernote is now virtually unusable. I was simply trying to toggle check marks in my grocery list yesterday, and it would take three or more attempts to acknowledge me, and then suddenly the keyboard would pop up without any reason and the screen and cursor would jump to the bottom of the list. When the program did finally acknowledge me, the check marks would be delayed by about 2 seconds each as if it had to stop and sync between every gesture.

Do people even test apps before release any more? Who thought &quot;Oh, yeah, this looks perfect,&quot; should be fired.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="check marks delayed by 2 seconds "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="keyboard would pop up without any reason"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="the screen and cursor would jump to the bottom of "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="toggle check mark"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="143">
    <text>I'm a writer and so I was always constantly using the original notes app that comes with apple products. But it strangely deleted all my notes, twice! So I decided I needed something better. I went through many different note taking apps but none sufficed. Then I found Evernote and was so pleased! Thank you guys so much! You make note taking fun and easy!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="note"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="144">
    <text>Was a great app that I use every day before. Update with reminders makes it that much better. Evernote keeps me organized!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="reminders"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="145">
    <text>For some reason, I kept waiting for Yojimbo to get its act together and do a companion iOS app. After using Evernote for 3 months, I'm hooked. It just works. When you put them all together, the desktop, web and mobile apps are an impressive solution for just about any productivity challenge.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="desktop"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="146">
    <text>I use Evernote for so many things:
Note taking, Recording meetings, to do lists, web clipping, reading PDFs - and everything syncs to all devices i use.  Love the app.  It's must have for the iPhone and iPad and desktop PC (or Mac).</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Note taking"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reading PDFs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Recording"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs to all devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="to do lists"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web clipping"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="147">
    <text>I have over 200 notes in Evernote (verified in the Mac version and on Evernote.com), but only 4 of them appeared in the new version of this app until I deleted and reinstalled it. Logging out and logging back in didn't work. The new UI will take some getting used to but feels cleaner and faster than before.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new UI"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Logging out and logging back"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="148">
    <text>Love it. Haven't gotten too much in place yet, but already I've come to depend on this. Few things to make it &quot;The One&quot; for my organizing heart, in the most drool-inducing order. 1. Ability to swipe through notes, like flipping pages in a books. 2. Sub-folders/notebook. 3. Ability to highlight (re-positionable sticky notes are a dream). 4. Colors! I get cross-eyed hunting through a long list of same 
colored notebooks. The ability to sort and organize by color would be wonderful. I'd know exactly what section to go to rather quickly.

This has let me collect my notes from my Palm, Blackberry, iPhone, PC...wherever, and put them in one place. I feel so un-scattered. Amazing how much information we and Evernote can hold.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Ability to highlight"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Ability to swipe through notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Colors"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sub-folders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sub-notebook"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="The ability to sort and organize by color"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="collect notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sort by color"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="149">
    <text>I have to say that Evernote is in the top 3 ranking of my productivity apps, if not number 1. So simple to use. I use it to store all sorts of data that I need to be able to recall quickly. 
Great for note taking, recipes, software keys, wifi settings... Endless uses.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="store all sorts of data"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="simple to use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="150">
    <text>I have had this program for over a year now. I use it for all my note taking. No more pads! Easy to share information with staff with a few key strokes. A great app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="share information"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="note"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="program"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="151">
    <text>The last version had a &quot;wow &quot; factor to it, this version is ugly IMHO.  Still like what it does for me though.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="service"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="152">
    <text>Afterr trying many organizers over the last year I am settling on Evernote. Is easiest and most intuitive to use, syncs so easily to laptop.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="153">
    <text>Used to be great. Now looks terrible. Wish I could go back to previous version. Time to start phasing it out.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="looks terrible"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="154">
    <text>This is a very useful and helpful app. In my opinion, the only thing it's missing is video handling. You can add pictures and audio to your notes, and I think you should be able to add videos, too.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="add audio"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="add pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="missing video handling"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="155">
    <text>Is the badest UI i have ever seen. Is very hard to use and no nice visual and no good to look. I dont like at all. Whats happen Evernote???</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="156">
    <text>Today's update, dated March 1, 2013 is horrible!  Every single time I open up the App, it defaults to the &quot;Updated&quot; view of all my notes. Then, when I select either &quot;Title&quot;, which is how I REALLY WANT to organize my notes, in alphabetical order, or I select &quot;Created,&quot;, the App immediately crashes and closes.  I have tried this over 50 times! I tried rebooting my iPad...no to avail.  I tried deleting the App all together, and then reloaded it, but still the same problem!  This HAS TO BE FIXED ASAP PLEASE!!!!!!!  I can't effectively use my notes...it's too much of a hassle to try to look in each month for a note created, and even each month is not in alphabetical order.  THERE IS NO RYTHME OR REASON TO THIS UPDATE!!!!  I have always been one of your biggest advocates and proponents.  If this bug isn't fixed pronto, I will have to delete Evernote permanently, and use a different App!  ARGHHHHHH!!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="use my notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="157">
    <text>I use this app almost every day. It really helps keep me on track. There is one thing I find very irritating however.  When I open it I hate having to wait so long on the green elephant screen! I wish so much I could just tap and make it go away so I could access what I need to and be done!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="wait so long to open it"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="green elephant screen"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="wait"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="158">
    <text>I use Evernote every day for both work and personal note-taking; glad the crash on launch was fixed so quickly! Would like to see complete parity (on formatting and some other features) between desktop and iPad versions, but it's getting really close.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="formatting"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="159">
    <text>After this latest update I can't even get into my account on either my iPhone or iPad it says incorrect password!!! What a freakin joke of an update! Do they even test before sending out these updates or what?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't even get into my account"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="160">
    <text>its a good app but i think there should be daily reminders or just like the alarms that are already on the devices you can set the days ...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="daily reminders"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="alarms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="161">
    <text>I love, love, love Evernote! It is the only way I remember anything. Their generous monthly allotment of new storage space is incredible!

The new interface seems to have buried things I want most. Such as Sync Now and Search. Sync seems to be broken regardless.

I am also unhappy with the iOS version of Evernote using my location as the default new note title instead of doing it like the desktop version does, using my first sentence. 

Another new(?) annoyance is Search now ignores which folder you are in. Always searching every note in your Evernote history is not efficient. If I know a note I am searching for is in a certain folder I should not have to search through search hits from all my other folders. Again, working like the desktop version would be better here.

Finally, it would be nice if tag searching worked like it does on the web version of Evernote, evaluating the entire tag. Not just the first word in the tag.

The iOS version is a bit buggy but that may be all iOS 7's fault. It is the buggiest iOS I can remember.

I'm not mad. Just frustrated. 2 stars is a reflection on the iOS version, not the Evernote across platforms.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tag searching"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="desktop version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sync Now"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new storage space"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="162">
    <text>even with the latest glitches, evernote is  still one of the only apps on my phone i use daily. best program to keep up with my life, super glad it is on the iphone!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest glitches"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="163">
    <text>I love, love this app! Evernote is so easy to use and very functional when surfing the web. It's like having a mini-assistant helping take notes!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="tool"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="take notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="164">
    <text>A genuine 'must have' app. I have it on all my devices to note ideas down, clip web articles and can search through everything.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="all my devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="note"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="165">
    <text>Wait for the bugs to get fixed. Better yet. Look for an alternative app.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Current Version"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="166">
    <text>Evernote is my go to for everything - whether lists, meeting notes, just things to remember etc.  The only thing that I wish it had is a date driven &quot;to-do&quot; or reminder.  Then it would be the only app I would ever use for all things productivity.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="date driven &quot;to-do&quot; or reminder"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="167">
    <text>?The highlighting of words works but the menu that pops up to copy, cut, paste etc.. Won't stay open long enough to be used.
?When placing the cursor over text when the keyboard is open makes the text jump every where but where you want the cursor to be.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 glitches"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="menu pops up won't stay open long enough"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="placing cursor over text"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="168">
    <text>I like the UI improvements with the new version. The old UI was hideous and I usually used En via another app like drafts or IFTTT. 

But the fact that I cannot add recent photos from my album!?!?!!? This is the main function for me of Evernote. This must be fixed!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cannot add recent photos from my album"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="UI new version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera album"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="169">
    <text>As stated in the title I am a new user. Even though I've only been using Evernote for about two months, I have come to greatly depend on it. It is fabulous to be able to record a meeting and take notes at the same time. I can't imagine anything better. I hope to find out all the other ways I can use it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="record a meeting "/>
      <aspectTerm label1=" take notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="170">
    <text>Agree with recent reviewers - this update completely ruined this excellent app for the iPhone on IOS7. Doesn?t work AT ALL. Opens, then freezes completely and can?t even open any of my notes or create new ones.
Doesn?t anyone test these apps before releasing them??  Please fix ASAP!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="IOS7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Doesn?t work AT ALL"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="171">
    <text>As recently as last week, I used this as almost my central control for everything.  After the latest upgrades, there were issues and now it crashes and I cannot access anything.  I am left in a very difficult situation.  Please fix it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cannot access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrades"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="172">
    <text>Recent upgrade is causing the app to crash on iPad. Needs fixed. I have tried to delete and reinstall but that didn't fix the problem.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="upgrade"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="173">
    <text>I like the concept and automation using the subject line.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="automation"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="subject line"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="174">
    <text>It allows me to record daily notes that aid in medical evaluations. It feel almost like cheating my memory.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="175">
    <text>Evernote is a great application. I use it across platforms and it always works without a glitch.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="platforms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="176">
    <text>I use this app more than any of the others, regardless of category. I love the ability to sync on all of my computers so I am always up to speed.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync on all of computers"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="177">
    <text>It was a little overwhelming to set up Evernote initially. Now that I've got things the way I want, I really enjoy it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="product"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="set up"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="178">
    <text>A wonderful substitute for loss of brain function in middle age. It remembers everything for me across platforms....!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="across platforms"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="179">
    <text>Continuous improvement keeps this complete cross-platform system well ahead and above the alternatives.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cross-platform"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Continuous improvement"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="180">
    <text>Great tool to consolidate your notes</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="consolidate your notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="181">
    <text>Great tool. The iOS app though, has issues. At the moment, you can't copy/paste text, many users (myself included) have reported a typing bug where the cursor jumps when you try to type, rendering the note taking part useless. 

On design flaws: you can't create a new notebook in the app mode, the interface is quite rigid and doesn't flow like the rest if apples iOS, you can't add notebooks to the shortcut section (though you can delete them..), and so on. I personally think it should be easier to manage your Evernote on a phone without accessing a computer. 

Still, get the app if you don't have it. It's an essential and probably one of the best in its category. Just be aware of the pitfalls that I'm sure the team is trying to fix...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't add notebooks to the shortcut section"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't create a new notebook in the app mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="copy/paste text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface is rigid"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="typing bug "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tool"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="182">
    <text>As a writer/daydreamer, I'm constantly in my head thinking up new ideas, and having a tool that allows me to access my material pretty much anywhere is fantastic. Instead of just jotting down a note (which I can't always do) and referring to it later on once I've gotten home, logged onto a computer, &amp; opened up a Word document, it's so much easier and convenient to do it on this app. I've even used Evernote for school stuff, essays mostly, so there's no need for emailing documents to myself. There are only a few errors/glitches that I've encountered but nothing that makes me want to stop using this app. I love it too much!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="note"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="183">
    <text>I use this app all the time to keep track of notes, recipes, general info, favorite restaurants, etc.  I do some organizing up front, but the real benefit is everything is then searchable and available on both my computers, phone and tablet.  Excellent and useful!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="availability on computers"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="availability on phone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="availability on tablet"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="available on computers, phone and tablet"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="184">
    <text>Green interface doesn't look, or feel good. Nor is it more useful. Maximizing space to type in should be the goal, however, it doesn't feel like it. The app still works. It's clunky and advertising too much. It probably isn't even an issue they may have rolled out the advertisements at the wrong time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="advertising"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Maximizing space"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Green interface usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="185">
    <text>I use it for everything from grocery lists to creative writing to notes on strange dreams that wake me at 2 am. Evernote's only limitations derive from the user's imaginative shortcomings.

The way it travels seamlessly between my devices allows me to jot down the vaguest impression of a thought and expand on it later.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="travels seamlessly between my devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="186">
    <text>I love Evernote and frankly don't know how I'd live without it. I have it installed on my desktop, iPhone and iPad.  It's a lifesaver. For newbies you might not be sure how to use this app. Head to their website and they have user guides which will give you some ideas. Once you incorporate it you'll start seeing the value right away.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="user guides"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="187">
    <text>These guys really don't seem to test their releases before sending them out.  This is not the first time that it took several releases to get it right.  When they DO get it right, this is a 5 start app. But now it crashes if you select &quot;Created&quot; or &quot;Title&quot; for the viewing mode.  Save yourself some headache and NEVER update Evernote until the reviews indicate that they got the bugs fixed.  And that would NOT be version 5.2.1.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Created&quot; or &quot;Title&quot; for the viewing mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest version (5.2.1)"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="188">
    <text>The search function isn't working and I have to sign in every time I open it. Evernote needs to fix this. Other than that, I love Evernote.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sign in"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="189">
    <text>I love Evernote. I use it on my Mac and I use it on my iPhone. I love the Evernote app but ever since the last update, which was a few days ago, this app has been giving me nothing but problems. Sometimes it just doesn't open. All I keep seeing is a blank screen. Sometimes it opens up but then while going back and forth between notes or notebooks it simply gets stuck and doesn't respond to any finger taps or actions. I hope the Evernote people improve this app and fix these bugs because I truly love Evernote and would like to keep using it. But lately I have encountered nothing but serious quality problems with Evernote.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="doesn't open"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="going back and forth between notes or notebooks it"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="190">
    <text>This is a great app for organizing notes, recipes, etc across devices.  I use it both at home and work.  I will enter info on my iphone, ipad, or on my PC.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="organizing notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="across devices"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="191">
    <text>You've got to be kidding!  I'm an Evernote premium user, but NEVER update my iOS on the first go round.  If I had known, I would not have updated Evernote?  Crap - I use EN for everything!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="IOS6"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="192">
    <text>I love Evernote and have become very reliant on it, one of the apps I can't do without however I am without it now because it crashes on open and will not open on iPhone.  DO NOT load the Dec 12 update!  Evernote please fix.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="193">
    <text>I love using Evernote for its simplicity, ease of use and effectiveness. I use this tool for work and personal purposes. Mainly for taking notes at work meetings, eliminating the paper clutter (both work and personal). I really like its integration with other SaaS tools. Recently switched my wife to Evernote for storing scanned documents.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="integration with other SaaS tools"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="194">
    <text>You guys need to fix this now!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="195">
    <text>I just struggle to find a use for it, and when I do, I often want PDFs out, which I struggle to acquire at work where it's all Windows all the time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="PDFs out"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="196">
    <text>Whatever feature I think ought to be included eventually gets included: hi-lighting, sorting options, converting to plain text AND simplified HTML, ...</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="converting to plain text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="hi-lighting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="simplified HTML"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sorting options"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="197">
    <text>But it works on all computers, including Mac.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="works on all computers"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="198">
    <text>I started to use evernote since high school, but didn't feel that useful. Now i am a college student, I use evernote in every life. I love the highlight section, but wish there is more color than yellow. Moreover, I enjoy the website version as well. It is organized and sophistic. Thank you for providing this application. It is so convenience.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="website version"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="wish more color"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="highlight section"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="199">
    <text>The app has been unbelievably buggy since the last update. Cannot trust using it on iPhone (only desktop and iPad).</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Cannot trust using it on iPhone "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="last update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="200">
    <text>I use Evernote a lot. It is my primary note app. The redesign is interesting. I think it will something I will really enjoy once I get used to it. 

That is if I can find out how to indent. There used to be a format option/tab above the keyboard in the earlier version. This provided the ability to do many formatting changes to notes you take. Some of these options remain, but not all. 

I heavily used the indent option to organize my notes. If this option is truly removed then I will really have to rethink how I take my notes. I hope it is still possible, but I just can't find it (or they add it in a patch). I know there is an outline feature (with either dots or numbers, this is not the feature I commonly use. I just want to indent). 

I still like the app and do not think it deserves a low review, but one of my most used features might have just been removed. I cannot give this update a 5. I hope this gets resolved soon.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="format option/tab"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="redesign"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="indent"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="option tab"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="outline"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="201">
    <text>$50 bucks a year to use this? iCloud is FREE. Why do we have to pay so much money to get access?

Is there a rule in our iTunes account that we have to like whatever junk they tell us to like?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="pay money to get access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="price"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="202">
    <text>Awesome app, allows you to easily create and share notes, pictures, diagrams and ideas between devices in a highly organized fashion. This is good if you're a scatter brain like me and never know when inspiration will strike but would lose it if if wasn't easy to categorize (ie traditional postit note model where they don't end up helping because they're everywhere)</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="create notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="create pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="share pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="diagrams"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="203">
    <text>a very good app. It's easy-using.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy-using"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="204">
    <text>I use EN constantly through the day for various productivity tasks. It performs well and all my devices are always in sync, so my files and notes are always handy. No crashes or complaints with the new design. It just works and I love it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="performs well and all my devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="205">
    <text>Constant crashes in iOS 7; 8 crashes in 30 minutes.  Evernote not really ready for new iOS.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Constant crashes in iOS 7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOs 8 crashes in 30 minutes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="206">
    <text>Evernote has been a mainstay in my life for the past years, and it pains me to say that there's a major bug in current ver. 
Once I get into webview, I'm unable to go back to Evernote. The Done button is not working. I tried quoting the app and it won't work either. Now I'm re-downloading the app, cross fingers this will help.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Done button"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="go back"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="207">
    <text>Brilliant app but crashes on iPad and iPhone.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="crash on iPad and iPhone"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="208">
    <text>Easy to use for quick, concise note-taking.  Would be fantastic if you could freehand and if the compatibility with wireless keyboards was more efficient.

Example: Apple &quot;Command&quot; key cannot control bold/underlining/italics functions.  You still have to use screen.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="wireless keyboards"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="note-taking"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="209">
    <text>Evernote is my main way to keep my projects in order. The only reason 4 stars instead of 5 - lack of 3-4 editing choices when entering text on my Iphone (features available in other apps,   i.e. change text color, etc.) Perhaps some or all are there, if so, not easy to find. The syncing is great. Great app!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="4 editing choices when entering text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text color"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="210">
    <text>The latest updates are really frustrating me. Because I am used to writing large amounts of text per note, it makes it extremely difficult to get the entirety of each note to load, and then to enter type mode. I have inadvertently deleted entire notes because of the new layout, which is slow and barely functional. Before the iOS 7 updates, Evernote was perfect. Then, with each update, the app got slower and slower and frankly, uglier and uglier. I am thoroughly disappointed in what used to be my go to writing app. I certainly hope the loads of poor reviews left for these past few updates are reaching you, because it doesn't appear that way. Please fix things!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="difficult to get the entirety of each note to load"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest updates"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="new layout"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="enter type mode"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="211">
    <text>My Mac OS X version is working fine, but the app does not upload my data until I soft reset the phone. Useless. iOS 7, iPhone 5.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="app does not upload my data until I soft reset the"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7, iPhone 5"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone 5"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Mac OS X version"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="212">
    <text>When this app worked, I'd give it 4 stars. But shortly after having it I got several errors about inability to sync. And then I couldn't open all my notes. And now it says trouble reaching evernote server. Btw the solution to that 1 (after I tried reinstalling and rebooting) is to log in using user name instead of email (or vice versa. Whatever you're having a problem w try the other). But annoying this happens at all. 

If it works for you, this is a pretty good app to help you keep all those notes you scribble down and email yourself in 1 place.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="opening notes  "/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="trouble reaching evernote server"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="log in"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="213">
    <text>I just downloaded it and can't open it on my iPad! And no I'm not an idiot. I looked on spotlight and it's not anywhere!! What gives?!?!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="can't open it on my iPad"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="214">
    <text>No notes showing up. All the notebooks are there but they are all empty. Boo</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="No notes showing up"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notebooks are empty"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="215">
    <text>Evernote is an excellent and indispensable service in my life. I'm happy to be a premium subscriber.

The mobile app, however, seems to be getting progressively worse. The latest version is clunky and buggy. Not to mention that &quot;announcements,&quot; which are essentially ads, now occupy the app's prime real estate. If there were an extra-premium subscription that would let me hide those and focus on my work, I'd subscribe!

I love the document photo feature. I use it daily. In the latest app iteration, though, this feature causes a crash. Arg!

I'm an Evernote evangelist, but I honestly could not recommend this mobile app.

???
ORIGINAL REVIEW:
Thanks for your hard work. Happy to be a premium subscriber.

Only suggestion: add ability to copy note links.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="document photo"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="announcements"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest version"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="216">
    <text>If you need to store lots of information and then be able to retrieve it through a number of different tags, you'll love Evernote.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="retrieve it through a number of different tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="store lots of information"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="217">
    <text>It's really useful now it just needs a dragon dictate so I can quit copy and pasting lol useful app though =]</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="dragon dictate"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="218">
    <text>Can't use on 4s with iOS 7. Freezes upon opening and can't use the app at all. Plus the new app is super confusing and difficult to use when it works on iPad. A massive step in the wrong direction.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Can't use on 4s with iOS 7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="219">
    <text>Don't Updated to iOS7 cause I noticed the paragraph section is missing the ability to create &quot;Section, subsection, paragraph and blockquote&quot; as I was able to in the previous version. It only allows me to select &quot; Simplify&quot; or &quot;Plain Text&quot;. I guess they are forcing us to pay for premium, find alternative, fellows!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="FORMATING function"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="missing the ability to create blockquote"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="missing the ability to create paragraph"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="missing the ability to create section"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="missing the ability to create subsection"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pay for premium"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Update to iOS7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="220">
    <text>Waited for this update, then we get this? EverNote is no longer for taking text notes. It is now obvious to me, and I have been in denial for over a year. 

There is no font control, editing is random and buggy, slow as molasses, and unreliable-- when you take time to write a paragraph, you want 100% confidence EverNote will not crash midway, or you get Synchronization Fail and thus lose your work. 

Note sorting and text-friendly organization (i.e., lists) have been thrown out the window for a shiny interface and lots of icons and flashy graphics. I can't write with the confidence that EverNote will not crash, but HEY, I can take a picture of my pancakes and keep it for posterity. Hey, EverFail, I quit. I am canceling my membership today. 

When you get serious about EverNote as a tool for work, send me an email. Actually, don't bother.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="font contro"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="graphics"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="icons"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="shiny interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Synchronization"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="taking text notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text-friendly organization"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="slow"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="take a picture"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="unreliable"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="221">
    <text>I love this thing, seriously. I use it for everything from project tracking to grocery lists to personal archive. Can't recommend it highly enough.

That said, I've got iOS7 on my phone, but have not upgraded my iPad; waiting for Apple to work some of the bugs out of the new OS for us tablet users. As a result, synching between devices is not always reliable right now - just a watch-out.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="synching"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="222">
    <text>Seems like the Evernote religion has passed me by. Perhaps there are handy tools that I am missing; trainings that are obvious to all but me. But, really! The notes, bullet points, spacing, numbering all fail when i transfer to Word and other systems. The resulting formatting problems take longer than just starting over and retyping notes. I also find that the left column flickers and the program crashes at every other use. About 1 in 4 syncs give an error message. 

All that aside, I like calling up notes on my phone, ipad, and desktop (almost) whenever I want. If this problematic version is intended to induce me to go for another version, it doesn't. In fact, if this version were more solid, I'd be tempted to buy the upgrade.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="calling up notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="syncs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="transfer to Word and other systems"/>
      <aspectTerm label1=" left column"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="bullet points"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="numbering"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="spacing"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="223">
    <text>I use it all the time.  I especially like the web clipper and then emailing right from Evernote</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="emailing right from Evernote"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web clipper"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Web clipping"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="224">
    <text>Great for taking personal notes.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="225">
    <text>Great for slow note takers I use it for all my classes wish there was a bullet option</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="bullet"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="226">
    <text>Try to up sell you but give few instructions or you can BUY A BOOK. Oh please.  Might like it better if I actually knew how to optimize its use and they were helpful in making the info you need easily available.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="instructions"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="making the info you need easily available"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="optimize its use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="227">
    <text>I have been a long-time user of google docs/drive and finally switched to Evernote for its vastly greater functionality. just as I was beginning to enjoy and appreciate the app, taking notes on a book I'm reading both textually and by taking pictures of passages, I accidentally touched the &quot;plain text&quot; format button. this move is apparently irreversible and I can no longer see the photos I took of passages from the book I have read, which I was planning to quote/cite later. I did not foresee such a drastic loss as possible, so I do not have these notes archived elsewhere. if I am to use an app that allows for this much thought and effort to be stored within it, I need to be able to trust that my work will not be lost with a simple touch screen selection error. This app has some very useful and convenient features, but I cannot continue to use it after such a loss. frustrating and disappointing.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="&quot;plain text&quot; format button"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="can no longer see the photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="taking notes on a book by taking pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="taking notes on a book textually"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="228">
    <text>Love the interface. Wish I remembered to use the app more!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="229">
    <text>Evernote is one of the few apps that I use everyday. It's a delight to use for recording ideas and notes.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="recording notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="230">
    <text>I hate giving this 3 stars, but know its just for the app interface, not Evernote itself, which I love. I find it difficult to navigate the app. It's ok, and I certainly understand the limited screen real estate they have to work with.  Still, it could be better.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iPhone UI"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="231">
    <text>Evernote has allowed me to organize all the notes and journal summaries for my MBA thesis seamlessly and everything is accessible whether I'm at home, work, or mobile. Love it!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="accessibility"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="232">
    <text>I've been using Evernote for 4 years and it just keeps getting better. Everything is easy to search and it has always worked flawlessly.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="robustness"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="233">
    <text>I can't believe you guys removed one of the most useful features of Evernote, which was the ability to style lines as either a section, subsection, paragraph or blockquote. That was the only way we could give some hierarchy to our notes.

Now all my notes are one dimensional and its impossible to organize my thoughts. How could the Evernote team consider that this feature was unnecessary? Do you guys not use your own app? How am I supposed to outline my notes? This is really a big let down to an otherwise great update. But it's too big an omission for me too be happy about anything else. That's why I give it 2 stars.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="styling as paragraph or section"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="style lines"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="234">
    <text>I love Evernote and have used it for the past few years. Good for quick word processing and keeping track of all kinds of stuff. I use it as my daily journal, too!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="keeping track of all kinds of stuff"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="word processing "/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="235">
    <text>I love Evernote and feel so organized now. I like being able to take pictures and use it often for business cards. I have recommended to friends. I can't live without my Evernote.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="take pictures"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="236">
    <text>Updated and lost all my notes. Great work guys. Do all your fans a favor - fire all your current programmers, offer the 2011 version as an update, and then call it a day.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="2011 version as an update"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="237">
    <text>Keeps all your information in one place. A must have</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="information in one place"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Keeps information"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="238">
    <text>Multi platform support is flawless</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Multi platform support"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="239">
    <text>Syncs great with desktop. Allowing me to keep my thoughts organized and accessible.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="240">
    <text>Syncs well and wonderful for projects at work and home.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Syncs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="241">
    <text>I love the do-anything note capabilities: text, inline photos, audio files, web-clips (which I have yet to become proficient with, but will)!

The cross-platform access to your notes on the cloud is brilliant and a HUGE time saver!

This app, combined with the inexpensive bluetooth keyboard that I bought recently have given me a power mobile information gathering and organizing capability.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="cross-platform access to your notes on the cloud"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="audio files"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="inline photos"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web-clips"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="242">
    <text>This has become my main notes program.  Wish I could do handwriting on it.  Love how can I can put outlook emails in it.   Using more than my other note apps in the iPad.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="handwriting"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="put outlook emails in it"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="243">
    <text>Been using Evernote for over a year.  I'm done with losing data.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Data"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="244">
    <text>Well organized, easy to use, and doesn't shove buying the upgrade in your face.  I use it here on my phone and on my laptop.  Great stuff!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easy to use"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="245">
    <text>Was just beginning to trust this app until 7 update. Quit working for all practical purposes.
Will watch for patches and post an updated review. I really was wanting this app to be effective. They have some silly new process to sell post it notes. Not!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="new process to sell post it notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="7 update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="246">
    <text>Love you it synchs!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="synchs"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="247">
    <text>I've used other note taking apps before, but this is my favorite. I haven't even begun to scratch the surface of all its capabilities, but I love the fact that it will sync across all my devices.  My notes are easy to find. It would've great if there was a way to hide some of my notebooks with a password for secure data. That's the only reason I gave it four stars instead of five.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync across all devices"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="hide notebooks with a password"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="password for secure data"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="248">
    <text>Opening some notes will cause app to crash :( please fix! This is beautifully designed but useless if it just keeps crashing :(</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Opening notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="249">
    <text>The new ver.7 won't sync with my account. 

I went back into the desktop app. Forced a sync then force quit the new iOS app and re-launched. Still nothing. 

This is the only thing this app is supposed to do. C'mon guys, it's broken.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sync"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="ver.7"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="250">
    <text>Just installed update and it's unusable now because it crashes 100% of the time upon startup.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="crashes 100% of the time upon startup"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="251">
    <text>the last v. its not good cuz if u wrote a wrong word the app. didn't set or draw a red line under the word so u will past with out correction. i want to come back it in next v. .......</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="spelling"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="252">
    <text>I use Evernote every day. It's more and more robust with each new edition.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="robustness"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="253">
    <text>This app is a must-have for those in the professional world. It is a great way to stay 'green' by storing documents rather than printing hard copies. The ability to search notes and PDFs makes old-fashioned pen and paper obsolete. The integration with Penultimate is pleasing for those who still wish to &quot;write&quot; rather than type.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="integration with Penultimate"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search PDFs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="storing documents"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="254">
    <text>Interfered with an app I already had and was happy with.  But then Evernote took over. Had to keep restring my password to try to use it.  A waste of time</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="password"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="user friendly"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="255">
    <text>Thanks, Evernote, for a great app!  I use it DAILY to keep my (gluten-free, dairy-free) recipes organized!

A tip: Please allow me to search ALL my notebooks - helpful to locate an ingredient - rather than searching within each notebook individually.

Also, I would love to pay a flat fee to be able to access my notes offline.  Thanks.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="offline access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="256">
    <text>I have tried a number of note taking apps, and it is fair to say that I am not a huge fan of any of them.  I tried Evernote because a couple folks recommended it.  

Good intentions, and probably the most functional of the apps I have tried.  But let's face it - they are all pretty clunky.   Evernote seems to build &quot;islands of stuff&quot; - text, pictures, URLs, etc.  editing any of that becomes problematic.  And when you email or cut&amp;paste into something else - it is a nightmare.  

One of the big reasons I looked at it is because I wanted to use bullets, numbers, outlining in my notes -- so I was SOOO happy to see those in the app.  BUT LET'S FACE IT - they basically don't work!!!!  They flake out, have irrational spacing, when you try to edit or move them they will most likely just disappear!!  Thank God for the un-do command.  

There seems to be quite a cult growing around this app - but I wish they would stop adding ancillary apps and JUST MAKE THE BASIC EVERNOTE APP WORK!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="bullets"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="cut&amp;paste"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="numbers"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="outlining"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="pictures"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="text"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="URLs"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="email"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="257">
    <text>I use this app constantly to log and recall business cards, notes, to do's, wine, art, inspiration, quotes...everything.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="258">
    <text>Notes app no longer needed with all these capabilities. Between my Mac, iPhone and work with IE and desktop app, it easy to save from the web and edit notes as needed. Can't do without</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="desktop app"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save from the web"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="work with IE"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="edit notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="259">
    <text>This app has been exactly what I need for note taking for both school and work. I would STRONGLY request the ability to change the text color in the iPad app like the desktop software. Thanks!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="text color"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="260">
    <text>Easy camera function allows for adding recipes right to notebook. Separate notebooks make keeping all pieces of a project together regardless of media. Used it for remodeling projects, and it's where I keep my collection of recipes, regardless of initial source. Have used it for about a year and unlike other apps, I'm still using it.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="camera function"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Separate notebooks"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="261">
    <text>There are some very real bugs in the updated Evernote!
1) It's very crash-prone, even after reinstalling and restarting the device. (iPad, iPhone 5, iOS 7)
2) When scrolling, if you're not careful, whatever file you're touching while scrolling tends to open accidentally.
I want to like Evernote. It has potential. But after this long, if they still can't figure it out, they're hopeless. A note app shouldn't be this cumbersome.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="crash-prone"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="scrolling"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="open file"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="262">
    <text>This app makeup so easy to take great notes and I really like being able to record audio of someone speaking wile I'm typing notes!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="record audio"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="263">
    <text>I love this ap. use it on the go but also to store travel info to easily access. Also like web integration.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="easily access"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web integration"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="264">
    <text>I would give this 5 stars if it had these two additional features:

Ability to use a scroll bar on iPad and iPhone rather than swipe, swipe, swipe and more swipe to get to the bottom of a note. 

Ability to keyword search AND GO TO THAT KEYWORD like you can on the laptop version. Having search feature for a word does me no good if I can't search within the note to find that word.

Can you do these two things for iOS please?</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="scroll bar"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="swipe"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="word search"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="265">
    <text>Great app that I have used regularly but seems a bit jerky since the iOS 7 update and update of app itself.  A bit off putting when trying to type!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS 7 update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="266">
    <text>Evernote is wonderful for organizing my notes! It's generally easy to use and convenient. 

My only gripe is that there seems to be no simple way of deleting a note. I've had to go into the note and delete it word by word. Perhaps I'm. Missing something.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="deleting a note"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Organizing Notes"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="267">
    <text>Scrolling through the note is very choppy. Please fix. Many seem to have same issue. iPhone like scrolling desired. What is the point of a beautiful interface if it is not smooth. Better keep animation simple but optimize scrolling. Thanks</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="scrolling"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="animation"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="interface"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="268">
    <text>Im on an original iPad mini and so maybe that's part of he deal but it seems like there are still little thins that need some work. For example the spell check doesn't work just right and the search is slow at times. Neither of these or any others will keep from giving this app a great rating. 

I also think that here are improvements I hope to see in the future. One is full screen mode. Maybe I'm missing this but the only time you get full screen is when you start a new note. I'd like this options when reading or editing too. 

Keep up the good work!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="full screen mode"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="search"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="spell check"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="editing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reading"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="start a new note"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="269">
    <text>Honestly, it took me some time to get used to using this application - web clipping, photo notes, sharing, etc., but now I find this app to be the &quot;deal killer&quot; - the one thing that MUST be on every device - 

The note scanning is so powerful it can read my scribbles (take notes in a meeting, take pics in evernote, throw them out!) ..

We are now exploring the business application - sky's the limit..</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="photo notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="web clipping"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="learning"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="note scanning"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="270">
    <text>I've been using Evernote since 2005 when I was in college. It's a wonderful service and up until the iOS7 redesign the apps have always worked great. 

But the design of this app is terrible.  It's jumbled, confusing and lots of advertising for their service add ons and &quot;news&quot; get in the way of core functionality. 

Please redesign the app.  Again.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="advertising"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="iOS7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="news"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="redesign"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="271">
    <text>Since updating to iOS7 and latest update of Evernote the spell check feature is not there any longer.  I utilize this for work, and rely on it for reports.  I figured give it a couple of weeks and they would fix it, but it's been over two months now and no fix.  Let's get it together Evernote team so I can give a 5 star review for this app again.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1=" latest update of Evernote iOS7"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="the spell check feature"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="latest update"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="272">
    <text>I love the app for allowing me to keep my notes organized and synchrd across devices. I also love the feature of sharing stuff with mates. The only thing I long for is collaboration on notes.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="collaboration"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="synchrd"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sharing stuff"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="273">
    <text>This version still has a marketplace  full of ads I can't hide, and the image attachment only shows me pics from September and earlier.. So it's pretty useless.

Quit trying to sell me stuff and fix your bugs!!!!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="ads"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="image attachment"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="274">
    <text>The only app I couldn't live without! Practical, easy to use, beautiful  design / user experience, use it multiple times per day.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="design"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="practicality"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="usability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="user experience"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="275">
    <text>I am enjoying this app and how I can place items that I want to review at a later time.    I use it to save recipes or articles of interest to read at a later time.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="place items that I want to review at a later time"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="save"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="276">
    <text>Convenient and easy to use. Great sync across several devices... BUT WISH THERE WAS A PASSCODE TO OPEN THE APP!!</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="PASSCODE"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="277">
    <text>Keeps track of any and everything and just keeps getting better. Whether it is a document or a picture it can be captured ether by email or snapping a photo and you then have it forever. Retrieving it is simple by tags or searching. It just makes life simpler.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="searching"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="tags"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Keeps track of any and everything"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="document"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="email"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="picture"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="278">
    <text>Was good until the cent updates. Now my notes vanish randomly and I keep getting a sync error. This app needs added features too.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="features needed"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="getting a sync error"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="notes vanish randomly"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="recent updates"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Sync"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
  <sentence id="279">
    <text>I use Evernote for work and personal use.  I was an early adopter and have found it to be an incredibly useful tool for productivity, personal reference, and as an idea-base. It is extremely reliable, intuitive, and something I use many times a day. 

I love it and highly recommend it to others.</text>
    <aspectTerms>
      <aspectTerm label1="intuition"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reliability"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="Tool"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="intuitive"/>
      <aspectTerm label1="reliable"/>
    </aspectTerms>
  </sentence>
</sentences>
